1
00:00:41,372 --> 00:00:45,331
你还记得关于那个生活在灰尘中的女孩的故事,
Do you remember the story
of a girl who lived a life of cinders,

2
00:00:45,409 --> 00:00:49,641
以及她如何凭着心中那美好的梦找到自己的真爱?
and how she found true love because
she kept a beautiful dream in her heart?

3
00:00:51,282 --> 00:00:54,376
当然需要她的那些会缝纫的老鼠朋友的帮助,
Of course it helped that she had
mouse friends who could sew

4
00:00:54,452 --> 00:00:57,649
还有靠她那个无所不能的仙母.
and a Fairy Godmother
who could do wonders with pumpkins.

5
00:00:57,722 --> 00:01:01,123
那个女孩就是我.
Well, that girl is me.

6
00:01:07,298 --> 00:01:11,257
多么美好的生活
童话故事也变成了现实
What a perfectly perfect life
It's a fairy-tale come true

7
00:01:11,335 --> 00:01:15,101
我是一个公主也是一个妻子
只是因为我能穿进去那只鞋
I'm a princess and a wife
all because I fit a shoe

8
00:01:15,172 --> 00:01:19,734
当我梦想真爱的时候
谁又能猜到我现在是如此的快乐
When I dreamed of love
who'd have guessed I'd end up here

9
00:01:19,810 --> 00:01:22,301
多么美好的年尾
At the end of a perfectly perfect year

10
00:01:22,379 --> 00:01:26,611
那么我这个完美无比的妻子可不可以
把她那完美无比的鞋子穿上呢?
 Would my perfectly perfect
wife put on her perfectly fitting shoes?

11
00:01:26,684 --> 00:01:28,345
你找到我的鞋了.
You found my shoes.

12
00:01:30,054 --> 00:01:32,386
最好快点.
仙母在等着呢.
Better hurry.
Fairy Godmother's waiting.

13
00:01:32,456 --> 00:01:34,856
这次那群老鼠把它用来当什么了?
What were the mice
using them for this time?

14
00:01:34,925 --> 00:01:36,085
小船.
Boats.

15
00:01:36,160 --> 00:01:37,149
来.
There.

16
00:01:41,699 --> 00:01:46,363
噢, 真是完美的美妙的一年啊!
Oh, what a wonderfully
perfectly perfect year!

17
00:01:50,474 --> 00:01:52,465
我们为什么应该做这些累活?
Why should we have to do the chores?

18
00:01:52,544 --> 00:01:54,375
我宁愿在监狱中腐烂
I would rather rot in jail

19
00:01:54,446 --> 00:01:58,280
-  洗餐具还要擦地板
-  太好了, 我弄断了一个指甲
-  Washing dishes and scrubbing floors
-  That's just great, I broke a nail

20
00:01:58,350 --> 00:02:01,979
灰姑娘现在过着奢华的生活
Cinderella is in the palace
living a life of luxury

21
00:02:02,053 --> 00:02:04,920
而我们再没有被邀请去舞会
And we've not once
been invited to a ball

22
00:02:04,990 --> 00:02:05,979
甚至下午茶
Or even tea

23
00:02:06,057 --> 00:02:10,426
为什么我没有快乐的结局?
那个会娶我的王子在哪里?
Why don't I get a happy ending?
Where's the Prince who'll marry me?

24
00:02:10,495 --> 00:02:15,296
什么时候我们的恶梦般生活才能结束?
When will this horrible
nightmare disappear?

25
00:02:15,767 --> 00:02:17,496
可悲.
Pathetic.

26
00:02:18,236 --> 00:02:23,071
噢, 多么悲惨的糟糕的一年啊!
Oh, what a perfectly
miserably awful year

27
00:02:24,676 --> 00:02:26,234
把手给我.
Give me your hand.

28
00:02:36,588 --> 00:02:38,988
我知道一定有个地方
Somewhere there must be

29
00:02:39,057 --> 00:02:41,116
那里有个人会爱上我
Someone who'll love me

30
00:02:41,193 --> 00:02:45,186
他会向我展示我从没有见过的世界
And show me a world that I never knew

31
00:02:45,263 --> 00:02:47,060
他会牵起我的手
He'll ask for my hand

32
00:02:47,132 --> 00:02:49,259
而我会说'我愿意'
And I'll say "I do"

33
00:02:49,334 --> 00:02:53,065
哦, 这样的事情多么美好
Oh, wouldn't it be finer than fine

34
00:02:53,138 --> 00:02:56,972
如果那个美妙的真爱
If that perfectly perfect love

35
00:02:57,042 --> 00:03:01,274
能降临到我的身边
Were mine

36
00:03:07,220 --> 00:03:09,120
他是个很迷人的王子
He's a perfectly charming Prince

37
00:03:09,188 --> 00:03:11,053
她是个很迷人的少女
She's a charmingly perfect lass

38
00:03:11,123 --> 00:03:14,217
他们永远幸福地生活在一起
They've lived happily ever
since she fit the slipper

39
00:03:14,293 --> 00:03:15,920
因为她穿上了那只玻璃鞋
Made of glass

40
00:03:17,196 --> 00:03:18,629
各就各位,伙计们
Take your places everyone

41
00:03:18,698 --> 00:03:22,828
该是我们庆祝这无比美妙
The time is drawing near to celebrate

42
00:03:22,902 --> 00:03:26,065
 的一年的时候了
A perfectly perfect year

43
00:03:27,707 --> 00:03:28,799
惊喜!
Surprise!

44
00:03:36,082 --> 00:03:39,245
我们为你们准备了美妙的周年庆祝晚会
A perfect anniversary party
that we planned for you

45
00:03:39,318 --> 00:03:40,683
而我会施展一些魔法
And I threw in some magic

46
00:03:40,753 --> 00:03:43,051
'奇妙大变身'
With a bibbidi-bobbidi-boo

47
00:03:43,122 --> 00:03:46,990
就像那晚我送你去舞会
Just like the night
I sent you to the ball

48
00:03:47,059 --> 00:03:50,654
原来灰姑娘靠的是这个, 魔法.
So that's how Cinderella did it. Magic.

49
00:03:50,730 --> 00:03:54,257
在这完美的一天
空气中充满了魔法
On this perfectly perfect day
there is magic in the air

50
00:03:54,333 --> 00:03:58,167
我想知道那个老女人有没有多余的魔棒
Gee, I wonder if that old lady
has a wand that she could spare

51
00:03:58,237 --> 00:04:00,364
什么能够阻挡我们?
What could ever come between us?

52
00:04:00,439 --> 00:04:02,703
我将非常愿意自荐
I would gladly volunteer

53
00:04:02,775 --> 00:04:06,643
而对于未来, 将是一片光明
And as for
the future, well, it's perfectly clear

54
00:04:06,712 --> 00:04:09,875
将会是魔术般的
It's sure to be
another magically

55
00:04:09,949 --> 00:04:11,211
悲剧般的
Tragically

56
00:04:11,284 --> 00:04:16,813
完美的一年
Perfectly perfect year

57
00:04:16,890 --> 00:04:18,084
太好了!
Perfect!

58
00:04:24,197 --> 00:04:26,597
妈妈! 妈妈!
Mother! Mother!

59
00:04:27,768 --> 00:04:28,757
妈妈!
Mother!

60
00:04:28,835 --> 00:04:31,895
- 阿纳斯塔西娅, 你去哪里了?
- 又去偷懒了.
- Anastasia, where have you been?
- Slacking off again.

61
00:04:31,972 --> 00:04:34,941
妈妈, 我们的困难结束了!
Mother, our troubles are over!

62
00:04:36,376 --> 00:04:38,105
一根棍子?
A stick?

63
00:04:38,178 --> 00:04:39,975
哦! 我们用它来教训她.
Ooh! Let's beat her with it.

64
00:04:40,047 --> 00:04:42,038
不, 不, 不, 不是棍子.
No, no, no, no. Not a stick.

65
00:04:42,115 --> 00:04:44,379
是一个魔杖.
A magic wand.

66
00:04:44,451 --> 00:04:46,749
她终于崩溃了.
Well, she finally cracked.

67
00:04:46,820 --> 00:04:48,811
我看到了那个有点胖的老女人!
I saw this nutty old woman and zap!

68
00:04:48,889 --> 00:04:53,451
她给了灰姑娘一套晚礼服, 哦, 王子啊.
She gave Cinderella the beautiful gown
and, oh, the Prince.

69
00:04:53,527 --> 00:04:57,361
- 还是快去做家务吧.
- 哦, 我证明给你看.
- I blame the housework.
- Oh, I'll prove it to you.

70
00:04:57,431 --> 00:05:01,231
嗯, 咒语是什么来着?
'快点给我变'?
Oh, what were those words again?
Wappity-pappity-poo?

71
00:05:01,301 --> 00:05:04,099
'变啊变啊变'?
我知道的, 我知道的, 真的.
Skip-skip-scadoo?
No, I know it. I know it. I think.

72
00:05:04,171 --> 00:05:07,766
哦, 我想起来了, 我想起来了.
'神奇大变...
Oh, no I've got it. I've got it.
Bibbidi-bobbidi...

73
00:05:07,841 --> 00:05:09,308
哦, 在这里!
Oh! There it is!

74
00:05:09,376 --> 00:05:11,435
孩子, 把它放下来!
Child, put that down!

75
00:05:11,511 --> 00:05:15,777
魔杖使用不当的话是很危险的.
In the wrong hands that wand
could be extremely dangerous.

76
00:05:15,849 --> 00:05:19,012
现在, 把它给我, 你这个小蠢猪.
Now, now give it back
to me you silly little goose.

77
00:05:19,086 --> 00:05:22,283
决不, 老太太.
'神奇大变身'!
No way, Grandma.
Bibbidi-bobbidi boo!

78
00:05:36,037 --> 00:05:38,597
看你都干了啥.
Look what you've done.

79
00:05:38,673 --> 00:05:40,732
现在把魔杖还给我.
Now give me back my wand.

80
00:05:40,808 --> 00:05:43,641
不, 我需要它,
你这个又老又笨的老女人!
No, I need it,
you silly old garden gnome!

81
00:05:43,711 --> 00:05:45,372
'神奇大变身'!
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo!

82
00:05:53,788 --> 00:05:55,187
噢!
Oh!

83
00:05:55,256 --> 00:05:56,723
哦.
Oh-oh.

84
00:05:56,791 --> 00:05:59,658
嗨? 嗨, 嗨, 老奶奶?
Hello? Hello, hello, Grandma?

85
00:05:59,727 --> 00:06:01,752
哦! 哦!!
Oooh! Oh!

86
00:06:01,829 --> 00:06:05,196
我... 对不起.
我不是故意要伤害你的.
I... I'm sorry.
Oh, I didn't mean to hurt you.

87
00:06:05,266 --> 00:06:09,760
那么灰姑娘就是这么干的了.
真是讽刺啊.
So this is how Cinderella did it.
What delicious irony.

88
00:06:09,837 --> 00:06:12,499
你们意识到这代表着什么么, 姑娘们?
Do you realize what this means, girls?

89
00:06:12,573 --> 00:06:15,167
是的! 不用洗衣了!
Yes! No more laundry!

90
00:06:16,811 --> 00:06:21,874
它代表了力量, 财富,
It means power, riches,

91
00:06:21,949 --> 00:06:23,883
复仇.
revenge.

92
00:06:25,887 --> 00:06:27,718
哦.
Oh.

93
00:06:27,789 --> 00:06:29,984
我要纸醉金迷般的富有!
I wanna be dirty, filthy, stinking rich!

94
00:06:30,058 --> 00:06:32,049
哦, 我要一个自己的王子!
Oh, I want a Prince of my own!

95
00:06:32,126 --> 00:06:33,650
哦, 拜托, 拜托, 拜托.
Oh please, please, please.

96
00:06:33,728 --> 00:06:35,559
- 给我!
- 不, 给我!
- Give it to me!
- No, give it to me!

97
00:06:35,631 --> 00:06:37,360
安静! 姑娘们!
Girls! Girls!

98
00:06:37,433 --> 00:06:40,334
一件一件来.
First things first.

99
00:06:40,402 --> 00:06:42,768
首先, 灰姑娘,
Now, Cinderella,

100
00:06:42,838 --> 00:06:46,501
取消你因为欺骗所得到的,
然后归还给我们应该得到的,
to undo your trickery
and take what's rightfully ours,

101
00:06:46,575 --> 00:06:50,238
宇宙啊, 赐予我力量吧!
I call upon
all the forces of the universe!

102
00:06:50,312 --> 00:06:53,179
'神奇大变身'!
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo!

103
00:07:11,366 --> 00:07:16,065
颠倒太阳和月亮,
让时间倒流,
Reverse the moon and sun,
turn back tide and time,

104
00:07:16,138 --> 00:07:19,699
在我的苦难开始的那一刻
unravel Cinderella's happily ever after

105
00:07:19,775 --> 00:07:23,142
夺走灰姑娘的快乐吧!
to the moment my troubles began!

106
00:07:57,013 --> 00:07:58,674
停!
Stop!

107
00:08:03,720 --> 00:08:05,984
哇.
Wow.

108
00:08:09,259 --> 00:08:12,660
- 大公爵!
- The Grand Duke!

109
00:08:14,197 --> 00:08:15,391
真的有用.
It worked.

110
00:08:15,465 --> 00:08:20,061
棒极了!
除了我们没有其他人知道.
Magnificent!
And no one knows except us.

111
00:08:20,136 --> 00:08:22,331
好好把握. 这是你们的第二次机会.
Get ready. This is your second chance.

112
00:08:22,405 --> 00:08:24,032
不要浪费了.
Don't waste it.

113
00:08:24,107 --> 00:08:25,335
灰姑娘在哪里?
Where's Cinderella?

114
00:08:25,408 --> 00:08:28,138
她在她一开始在的地方.
She's exactly
where she was the first time.

115
00:08:28,211 --> 00:08:29,769
灰姑娘!
Cinderelly!

116
00:08:33,216 --> 00:08:34,877
大公爵!
The Grand Duke!

117
00:08:34,951 --> 00:08:36,248
尊敬的大公爵.
Your Excellence.

118
00:08:36,319 --> 00:08:37,513
大公爵阁下.
Your Grace.

119
00:08:37,587 --> 00:08:40,147
阁下将会宣布他的皇家...
His Grace will now
read the royal procla...

120
00:08:40,223 --> 00:08:43,124
打扰一下, 我们都知道他要干什么.
Pardon me, but we're all aware
of his grace's purpose.

121
00:08:43,193 --> 00:08:45,559
也许...你继续就好.
Perhaps we should just...
get on with it.

122
00:08:46,329 --> 00:08:49,628
很好, 女士. 很好.
Quite, Madame. Quite.

123
00:08:58,609 --> 00:09:00,270
哦.
Ooh.

124
00:09:07,418 --> 00:09:09,386
'神奇大变身'.
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo.

125
00:09:13,057 --> 00:09:16,185
合脚!
It fits!

126
00:09:16,260 --> 00:09:17,522
合脚?
It fits?

127
00:09:18,028 --> 00:09:19,791
合脚!
It fits!

128
00:09:21,765 --> 00:09:23,062
妈妈, 很合脚.
Mother, it fits.

129
00:09:23,133 --> 00:09:25,363
切. 我真感到怀疑.
Gee. I wonder if it fits.

130
00:09:25,436 --> 00:09:27,870
- 合脚, 合脚! 哦, 妈妈!
- It fits, it fits! Oh, Mother!

131
00:09:27,938 --> 00:09:29,929
我就要得到我的王子了!
I'm gonna get my Prince!

132
00:09:30,007 --> 00:09:31,668
啊哈!
Woo-hoo!

133
00:09:32,776 --> 00:09:35,142
保持优美姿态, 亲爱的!
Grace and poise, my dear!

134
00:09:38,415 --> 00:09:41,145
我现在宣布
I hereby declare

135
00:09:41,218 --> 00:09:45,621
我们找到了王子的准新娘.
that we have found
the Prince's bride-to-be.

136
00:09:48,592 --> 00:09:51,288
- 我们马上回宫!
- We must return to the palace at once!
- 

137
00:09:53,831 --> 00:09:55,196
不, 这不可能.
No. It can't be.

138
00:09:55,699 --> 00:09:57,860
可以稍等一下么?
Would Your Grace excuse me?

139
00:09:57,935 --> 00:10:01,234
我想和我的... 女佣说几句话.
I must have a word with my... maid.

140
00:10:03,240 --> 00:10:04,229
走!
Oof!

141
00:10:06,611 --> 00:10:09,580
你看起来很迷惑, 亲爱的.
You look confused, dear.

142
00:10:09,648 --> 00:10:12,310
为什么阿纳斯塔西娅能穿上那只鞋?
How could the slipper
have fit Anastasia?

143
00:10:12,384 --> 00:10:15,114
是我和王子跳的舞.
那是我的舞鞋.
I danced with the Prince.
That was my slipper.

144
00:10:15,186 --> 00:10:18,644
看, 我还有另外一只.
我才是他要找的人.
Here, I have the other one.
I'm the one he's looking for.

145
00:10:18,723 --> 00:10:22,523
也许你和他跳过舞.
你甚至想过这就是爱情.
You may have danced with him.
You may even have thought it was love.

146
00:10:22,594 --> 00:10:27,497
但是阿纳斯塔西娅穿上了舞鞋,
她将会嫁给王子.
But the slipper fits Anastasia,
and that's who he's marrying.

147
00:10:27,565 --> 00:10:31,433
昨晚发生的一切都只是一个梦.
Whatever you think happened
last night was a dream.

148
00:10:36,908 --> 00:10:41,106
我不管你去哪里
我也不管你做什么,
I don't care where you go
or what you do,

149
00:10:41,179 --> 00:10:43,704
但是离皇宫远点.
but you stay away from the palace.

150
00:10:43,782 --> 00:10:46,842
离王子远点.
Stay away from the Prince.

151
00:10:50,755 --> 00:10:54,350
哦, 还有, 把碎玻璃清理干净.
Oh and... clean up that broken glass.

152
00:11:19,051 --> 00:11:21,679
刚才到底怎么了?
Duh... what just a-happened?

153
00:11:22,788 --> 00:11:26,053
我, 我不明白.
I... I don't understand.

154
00:11:26,959 --> 00:11:28,426
我...
I've...

155
00:11:29,428 --> 00:11:31,862
我一直在梦想
I've always dreamed

156
00:11:31,931 --> 00:11:34,661
我的生活能像
That my life could be

157
00:11:34,734 --> 00:11:36,895
童话故事一样
Like a fairy-tale

158
00:11:36,969 --> 00:11:40,063
完美而动人
A perfect fantasy

159
00:11:40,139 --> 00:11:42,164
每天都是新的探险
Every day a new adventure

160
00:11:42,742 --> 00:11:45,540
在未知的海滩上
On some undiscovered shore

161
00:11:45,611 --> 00:11:47,670
难道那些
Was it nothing more

162
00:11:47,747 --> 00:11:49,146
都只能是个梦?
Than a dream?

163
00:11:50,449 --> 00:11:52,815
然后那个梦幻般的夜晚
Then one magic night

164
00:11:52,885 --> 00:11:55,945
只是一只舞
With a single dance

165
00:11:56,021 --> 00:12:01,323
我发现除了故事书以外的浪漫
I found more than
just a storybook romance

166
00:12:01,394 --> 00:12:03,885
这次我感觉到了生活的快乐
And for once my life was perfect

167
00:12:03,963 --> 00:12:06,523
我们在大厅里滑翔
As we glided 'cross the floor

168
00:12:06,599 --> 00:12:09,466
看起来完全不是
And it was so much more

169
00:12:09,535 --> 00:12:14,632
仅仅做梦而已
So much more than a dream

170
00:12:14,707 --> 00:12:16,732
我希望它从没有发生
I could say it never happened

171
00:12:17,209 --> 00:12:19,404
从一开始就是个梦
Just a dream from the start

172
00:12:19,478 --> 00:12:22,242
但是从此我将
But then I'd live my life

173
00:12:22,314 --> 00:12:24,373
带着一颗受伤的心生活...
With a broken heart...

174
00:12:24,450 --> 00:12:27,214
- 别, 别. 别哭, 格斯, 格斯.
- No, no. No cry, Gus Gus.

175
00:12:27,287 --> 00:12:29,585
王子知道和他跳舞的是灰姑娘.
Princey knows he danced with Cinderelly.

176
00:12:31,091 --> 00:12:33,924
对, 他当然知道.
Yes, of course he does.

177
00:12:34,494 --> 00:12:36,485
如果我能再见他...
Oh, if I just see him again...

178
00:12:36,563 --> 00:12:38,588
对, 对, 去见王子!
Yeah, yeah, see Princey!

179
00:12:38,665 --> 00:12:41,133
不错... 一切就会好起来.
Yes... everything will be alright.

180
00:12:41,201 --> 00:12:45,035
- 一切都会好起来.
- 就是, 就是!
- Everything will be alright.
- Duh... yeah, yeah!

181
00:12:45,639 --> 00:12:50,702
因为在王子的怀里
我找到了我无法抗拒的爱情
'Cause in a Prince's arms
I've found a love I can't deny

182
00:12:50,777 --> 00:12:53,405
如果有机会能证明真相
If there's any chance
to set things right

183
00:12:53,480 --> 00:12:56,711
我会不顾一切地去尝试
I've simply got to try

184
00:12:57,484 --> 00:13:00,248
所以我要相信我自己
So I'll trust my heart

185
00:13:00,353 --> 00:13:02,651
我还能做什么呢?
What else can I do?

186
00:13:02,689 --> 00:13:05,214
我不能活在梦中
I can't live in dreams

187
00:13:05,292 --> 00:13:07,920
如果我的梦能够成真
If my dreams are to come true

188
00:13:07,994 --> 00:13:10,224
将会有更好的生活等着我
There's a better life that's waiting

189
00:13:10,297 --> 00:13:12,959
即使跋山涉水
Past the mountains I must climb

190
00:13:13,033 --> 00:13:18,903
我也要争取一试, 赢得属于我的一切
I will take a chance on love
to get my once upon a time

191
00:13:23,543 --> 00:13:26,740
我想要的不仅仅
Oh, I want so much more

192
00:13:26,813 --> 00:13:29,976
不仅仅
So much more

193
00:13:30,050 --> 00:13:34,987
只是一个梦
Than a dream

194
00:13:47,802 --> 00:13:50,327
灰姑娘, 前面有守卫.
Cinderelly, big blue guards.

195
00:13:50,404 --> 00:13:55,103
交给格斯好了.
让我去! 让我去!
Gus Gus handle 'em.
Let me at 'em! Let me at 'em!

196
00:13:56,644 --> 00:14:00,045
嗯... 让我们先试试下人通道.
Um... Let's try
the servant's entrance first.

197
00:14:04,352 --> 00:14:06,980
- 早上好, 阁下.
- 早上好.
Good morning, sir.
Good morning.

198
00:14:07,054 --> 00:14:08,783
- 国王要的洋葱.
- 干得好.
- Onions for the King.
- Well done.

199
00:14:08,856 --> 00:14:09,880
草莓.
Strawberries.

200
00:14:09,957 --> 00:14:12,221
- 快躲起来.
- Keep out of sight.

201
00:14:12,293 --> 00:14:15,524
国王在等着呢. 给你.
The King is waiting. There you are.

202
00:14:15,596 --> 00:14:18,360
- 国王会很喜欢的.
- 这些是他的最爱.
- The King will enjoy them.
- They're his favorite.

203
00:14:22,403 --> 00:14:23,563
嗯?
Hmm?

204
00:14:44,926 --> 00:14:48,020
现在, 我们只要找到他然后一切就...
Now, all we have to do
is find him and everything will be...

205
00:14:48,096 --> 00:14:49,563
站住! 别动.
Stop! You there.

206
00:14:50,399 --> 00:14:52,799
你是谁?
你在这里干什么?
Who are you?
What are you doing here?

207
00:14:52,868 --> 00:14:54,028
我...
I...

208
00:14:54,102 --> 00:14:56,662
我负责管理这个城堡的所有下人,
I'm in charge of all
the servants in this castle,

209
00:14:56,738 --> 00:14:58,672
不过我从没有见过你.
and I've never seen you before.

210
00:14:59,441 --> 00:15:01,432
你来干什么?
What is your purpose?

211
00:15:01,510 --> 00:15:05,412
我来... 嗯... 我...
My purpose. Well... um... I...

212
00:15:05,480 --> 00:15:06,538
我...
I...

213
00:15:07,049 --> 00:15:09,882
- 我是皇家捕鼠员.
- I'm the royal mouse catcher.

214
00:15:09,952 --> 00:15:13,786
皇家捕鼠员? 荒谬.
Royal mouse catcher? Preposterous.

215
00:15:13,855 --> 00:15:16,016
一个都不放过.
那是我的座右铭.
Snap 'em and trap 'em.
That's my motto.

216
00:15:16,091 --> 00:15:17,285
哦, 不!
Oh, no!

217
00:15:18,060 --> 00:15:21,518
在我管理这座城堡的...
In the 30 years
that I have supervised...

218
00:15:21,597 --> 00:15:24,191
30年中,
...this castle,

219
00:15:24,266 --> 00:15:28,032
我敢打包票这里根本连一个...
I can assure you there has never
ever been a single, solitary...

220
00:15:28,103 --> 00:15:30,094
- 有老鼠!
Mouse!

221
00:15:31,540 --> 00:15:32,973
- 在哪里?
- 老鼠!
- Where is it?
- Mice!

222
00:15:39,781 --> 00:15:41,612
哦, 拜托, 让我帮忙吧.
Oh, please, let me help.

223
00:15:42,451 --> 00:15:45,887
这是我的厨房.
一切由我做主!
This is my kitchen.
I'll take care of it!

224
00:15:46,622 --> 00:15:50,058
叫你跑! 往哪儿跑! 该死的家伙!
Take that! And that! Vile vermin!

225
00:15:50,125 --> 00:15:51,558
来吧, 我可以搞定的!
Please, I can handle this!

226
00:15:51,627 --> 00:15:53,117
现在不行!
Not now!

227
00:15:53,195 --> 00:15:54,628
我就要抓到它们了!
I've got them on the run!

228
00:15:55,464 --> 00:15:57,295
真的, 我能帮忙的.
Really, I can help.

229
00:16:04,040 --> 00:16:06,804
它在那儿! 我抓到它了! 我抓到它了!
There he is! I got him! I got him!

230
00:16:09,779 --> 00:16:12,839
那么, 我现在去抓那些老鼠了.
So then, I'll just go get those mice.

231
00:16:20,657 --> 00:16:22,522
过来, 伙计们.
Come on, guys.

232
00:16:22,592 --> 00:16:24,355
- 干得好.
- Nice work.

233
00:16:24,427 --> 00:16:26,827
如果我们分头找的话,
我们就能很快找到王子.
If we split up,
we'll find the Prince faster.

234
00:16:26,896 --> 00:16:28,363
分头! 好的!
Split up! Righty-o!

235
00:16:28,431 --> 00:16:31,696
- 但是, 父亲...
- 那些不是借口s!
- But, Dad...
- Those aren't reasons!

236
00:16:31,768 --> 00:16:35,329
有教养, 文雅!
Breeding, refinement!

237
00:16:35,405 --> 00:16:37,737
这些是娶某人的理由.
These are the reasons to marry someone.

238
00:16:37,807 --> 00:16:40,867
不能只看能不能穿玻璃鞋!
Not their choice
in transparent footwear!

239
00:16:43,346 --> 00:16:45,712
哦! 躲得好.
Ooh! Nice parry.

240
00:16:45,782 --> 00:16:46,771
谢谢.
Thanks.

241
00:16:48,885 --> 00:16:52,150
不是舞鞋的问题.
是穿舞鞋的那个女孩.
It's not about the slipper.
It's the girl in the slipper.

242
00:16:53,489 --> 00:16:56,219
她是... 她是...
She was... Well, she was...

243
00:16:56,292 --> 00:16:58,624
她是什么?
She was what?

244
00:16:58,695 --> 00:17:01,960
她就是我想娶的.
Well, she was the one.

245
00:17:02,031 --> 00:17:03,623
我知道.
I know it.

246
00:17:07,103 --> 00:17:09,833
你以为整个王国就她一个女孩
You think there's only
one woman in the kingdom

247
00:17:09,907 --> 00:17:11,966
穿四号半的鞋子么?
who wears a size four and a half?

248
00:17:12,376 --> 00:17:13,866
我觉得就是.
It's all I have to go on here.

249
00:17:13,944 --> 00:17:15,571
哦, 真是胡说八道!
Oh, poppycock!

250
00:17:25,556 --> 00:17:27,547
你还记得你见到我的母亲的时候么?
You remember when you met Mom?

251
00:17:30,828 --> 00:17:33,661
你说你第一次摸到她的手...
You said the first time
you touched her hand...

252
00:17:33,731 --> 00:17:35,926
...你立刻... 就知道了.
...you just knew... instantly.

253
00:17:37,568 --> 00:17:41,937
嗯. 那晚的星星都比较亮.
Mmm. The stars were brighter that night.

254
00:17:42,005 --> 00:17:45,133
爸爸, 你找到了真爱.
Dad, you found true love.

255
00:17:45,209 --> 00:17:47,336
那也是我要的.
That's all I want.

256
00:17:47,411 --> 00:17:50,437
噢! 他们找到她了!
- Oh! They found her!

257
00:18:01,458 --> 00:18:03,619
吱吱!
 Zug-zug!

258
00:18:06,396 --> 00:18:10,196
现在, 请你们女士们先坐一下,
Now, if you ladies
would please have a seat,

259
00:18:10,267 --> 00:18:12,735
王子很快就过来.
the Prince will be right with you.

260
00:18:17,674 --> 00:18:19,403
王子!
My Prince!

261
00:18:21,846 --> 00:18:23,279
尊敬的王子殿下!
Your Highness!

262
00:18:23,348 --> 00:18:26,112
哦, 嗨.
Oh, hello.

263
00:18:26,184 --> 00:18:30,746
我是不是进错房间了?
显然没有进错. 嗯...
Am I in the right room?
Of course I'm in the right room. Um...

264
00:18:30,822 --> 00:18:33,950
那么... 看起来...
好像有点混乱.
Well there... There seems to be...
a little mix-up here.

265
00:18:34,692 --> 00:18:38,890
我能保证, 尊敬的王子殿下,
这只舞鞋很合我女儿的脚.
I assure you, Your Highness,
the slipper fits my daughter's foot.

266
00:18:38,963 --> 00:18:40,954
看见没? 看见没?
See? See?

267
00:18:41,032 --> 00:18:42,727
他怎么可能看不见?
Huh. How could he miss it?

268
00:18:42,801 --> 00:18:45,429
哦, 是的, 嗯...
Oh, yeah, I see. Um...

269
00:18:45,503 --> 00:18:49,803
只是因为...
我觉得是另外一个人.
It's just that I was expecting...
Well, someone else.

270
00:18:49,874 --> 00:18:52,468
真的感到很抱歉.
I really do feel awful about this.

271
00:18:52,544 --> 00:18:54,739
但是你们的圣旨已经宣布...
But the royal proclamation declared...

272
00:18:54,813 --> 00:18:59,409
是的, 但是看起来, 好像不只一个女孩
Yes, but it would appear that,
uh, more than one girl

273
00:18:59,484 --> 00:19:02,282
可以穿上这只舞鞋.
actually fits the... the slipper.

274
00:19:02,353 --> 00:19:05,720
很抱歉麻烦你们了. 嗯...
I'm very sorry
to have inconvenienced you. Um...

275
00:19:05,790 --> 00:19:10,090
要不我让大公爵护送你们回家.
Why don't I have the Grand Duke
escort you home safely.

276
00:19:10,161 --> 00:19:12,857
那么失陪了.
- If you'll please excuse me.

277
00:19:12,931 --> 00:19:14,421
呦!
Phew!

278
00:19:15,433 --> 00:19:17,162
- 但是... 但是...
- 安静!
- But... but...
- Quiet!

279
00:19:18,670 --> 00:19:21,195
你将忘记和你在舞厅跳舞的那个女孩,
You will forget who you
danced with at the ball,

280
00:19:21,272 --> 00:19:23,763
今晚你将迎娶眼前这个穿上舞鞋的女孩...
and marry the girl
who fits the slipper...

281
00:19:23,842 --> 00:19:26,640
'神奇大变身'.
...tonight. Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo.

282
00:19:48,200 --> 00:19:50,998
等下, 我想起来了!
Wait. Hold the trumpet!

283
00:19:51,070 --> 00:19:52,731
我都想起来了.
It's all coming back.

284
00:19:54,940 --> 00:19:56,237
是你.
It is you.

285
00:19:58,143 --> 00:20:00,338
拜托, 请你告诉我你的名字.
Please. Please tell me your name.

286
00:20:00,880 --> 00:20:03,644
是阿纳斯塔西娅.
It's... Anastasia.

287
00:20:03,716 --> 00:20:05,547
阿纳斯塔西娅.
Anastasia.

288
00:20:06,652 --> 00:20:10,213
我...我知道这很突然,
但是你愿意嫁给我么?
Well, I... I know it's sudden,
but will you marry me?

289
00:20:10,289 --> 00:20:12,189
是的! 耶!
Yes! Yippee!

290
00:20:23,535 --> 00:20:24,934
啊!
Ah!

291
00:20:30,442 --> 00:20:31,431
是的. 呃...
Yes. Er...

292
00:20:31,510 --> 00:20:36,072
我是说, 是的, 我愿意.
I... I mean, yes. Definitely yes.

293
00:20:36,148 --> 00:20:38,844
我愿意嫁给你.
I will marry you.

294
00:20:38,918 --> 00:20:42,854
太好了. 婚礼今晚举行.
Excellent. The ceremony
will take place tonight.

295
00:20:42,923 --> 00:20:45,756
我相信你不会反对的, 殿下.
I trust that meets
with your approval, sire.

296
00:20:45,825 --> 00:20:47,759
越快越好.
The sooner the better.

297
00:20:47,827 --> 00:20:51,627
很好, 今晚我们将会有一个新的公主.
Splendid. Then tonight
we will have a new princess.

298
00:20:51,698 --> 00:20:53,723
棒极了, 我去告诉我的父王.
Wonderful. I'll go tell my father.

299
00:20:53,800 --> 00:20:56,997
不妙! 我们要找到灰姑娘, 格斯, 格斯!
Not good! We have
to find Cinderelly, Gus Gus!

300
00:21:12,686 --> 00:21:15,883
我感觉好多了.
I feel better already.

301
00:21:15,956 --> 00:21:21,588
保持优雅端庄, 姑娘们.
记住, 优雅端庄.
Grace and poise, girls.
Just remember, grace and poise.

302
00:21:21,661 --> 00:21:24,721
不错. 优雅端庄.
Right. Grace and poise.

303
00:21:24,798 --> 00:21:27,028
看, 一个竖琴.
- Oh, look, a harp.

304
00:21:38,178 --> 00:21:41,079
露西弗?
Lucifer?

305
00:21:48,021 --> 00:21:49,488
露西弗?
Lucifer?

306
00:21:55,763 --> 00:21:59,096
露西弗! 过来!
- Lucifer! Come here!

307
00:22:09,543 --> 00:22:12,444
呼~~.
Phew.

308
00:22:16,517 --> 00:22:18,382
殿下.
Your Highness.

309
00:22:18,452 --> 00:22:19,749
嗯?
Yes?

310
00:22:19,820 --> 00:22:22,118
嗨. 
Hello. 

311
00:22:22,189 --> 00:22:24,555
嗯... 嗨.
Um... Hello.

312
00:22:24,625 --> 00:22:26,991
能再次见到你真好.
It's wonderful to see you again.

313
00:22:27,061 --> 00:22:30,861
嗯... 不好意思, 我们见过么?
Um... I'm sorry, have we met?

314
00:22:32,733 --> 00:22:35,998
我们昨晚在舞会上跳舞的啊.
I believe we danced
last night at the ball.

315
00:22:37,805 --> 00:22:42,469
嗯, 也许你把我跟其他的王子弄混了.
Well, uh... maybe you've
mistaken me for some other prince.

316
00:22:45,713 --> 00:22:47,476
我不这么认为.
I don't think so.

317
00:22:47,548 --> 00:22:49,413
你跳得非常棒.
You are quite the dancer.

318
00:22:49,483 --> 00:22:50,916
那不只是因为我.
Well, it wasn't just me.

319
00:22:50,985 --> 00:22:54,580
还因为那个和我...
It was the lady I was...

320
00:22:54,655 --> 00:22:56,520
...跳舞的女士.
...dancing with.

321
00:23:04,933 --> 00:23:06,764
哦, 殿下.
Oh, Your Highness.

322
00:23:06,835 --> 00:23:10,828
事实上, 我将会和她结婚.
Uh... As a matter of fact,
I'm gonna marry her.

323
00:23:10,906 --> 00:23:13,067
结婚? 真的?
Marry? Really?

324
00:23:13,141 --> 00:23:14,768
是的! 今晚.
Yes! Tonight.

325
00:23:14,843 --> 00:23:16,105
今晚?
Tonight?

326
00:23:16,178 --> 00:23:18,612
一旦你和像阿纳斯塔西娅这样的女孩跳过舞,
Once you dance
with someone like Anastasia,

327
00:23:18,680 --> 00:23:20,511
你不会不着急着和她结婚.
you don't want to waste any time.

328
00:23:20,582 --> 00:23:22,550
你是说阿纳斯塔西娅?
Did you say Anastasia?

329
00:23:22,617 --> 00:23:23,709
是的.
Yes.

330
00:23:24,319 --> 00:23:25,581
但是...
But...

331
00:23:30,826 --> 00:23:34,284
我想我得走了.
Well... I guess I better be going.

332
00:23:34,362 --> 00:23:35,795
我要去告诉我的父王.
I've got to tell my father.

333
00:23:35,864 --> 00:23:38,025
- 但这样不对.
- 你说什么?
- But that's not right.
- I'm sorry?

334
00:23:38,100 --> 00:23:41,263
你在这儿. 皇家捕鼠员!
我需要你...
You there. Royal mouse catcher!
I need you this...

335
00:23:41,336 --> 00:23:45,773
哦, 对不起, 殿下. 我没注意到...
Oh. Oh, I'm sorry,
Your Grace. I didn't realize...

336
00:23:45,841 --> 00:23:46,933
是我才对...
I was the one...

337
00:23:47,008 --> 00:23:50,102
我需要她, 马上!
你能把她给我带走么, 殿下?
I need her this instant!
Please excuse us, Your Highness?

338
00:23:50,178 --> 00:23:52,169
拜托, 抱歉, 就一会儿.
Please. I'm sorry, just one moment.

339
00:23:52,247 --> 00:23:55,011
不, 不, 不, 没关系.
看出来你很忙.
No, no, no. Of course,
I can see you're busy.

340
00:23:55,083 --> 00:23:57,278
我... 我同意让你走.
I'll... I'll let you go.

341
00:23:58,286 --> 00:24:01,778
但是... 应该是我.
But... it was me.

342
00:24:18,474 --> 00:24:22,342
现在开始! 我要整个城堡在婚礼的时候
Start here! I want this castle
completely rodent-free

343
00:24:22,411 --> 00:24:24,402
完全没有那些该死的小动物.
in time for the wedding.

344
00:24:47,236 --> 00:24:48,931
灰姑娘! 灰姑娘!
Cinderelly! Cinderelly!

345
00:24:49,005 --> 00:24:50,302
格斯?
Gus?

346
00:24:50,373 --> 00:24:51,704
灰姑娘!
Cinderelly!

347
00:24:51,774 --> 00:24:53,332
哇!
Whoa!

348
00:24:53,409 --> 00:24:54,876
我们找到了王子!
We found Princey!

349
00:24:54,944 --> 00:24:58,846
我也是. 但是他根本不认识我.
I did too. But he doesn't
even know who I am.

350
00:24:59,749 --> 00:25:00,807
不, 不, 不!
No, no, no!

351
00:25:01,584 --> 00:25:03,347
是魔法.
It's a magic.

352
00:25:03,419 --> 00:25:05,353
什么? 你在说什么?
What? What are you talking about?

353
00:25:10,459 --> 00:25:11,790
继母?
Stepmother?

354
00:25:13,629 --> 00:25:16,598
- 仙母?
- 神奇大变身.
- Fairy Godmother?
- Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo.

355
00:25:16,666 --> 00:25:17,860
她偷了它?
She stole it?

356
00:25:17,934 --> 00:25:19,834
让你看看王子!
- I show Princey!

357
00:25:20,770 --> 00:25:22,431
王子! 王子!
Princey! Princey!

358
00:25:24,041 --> 00:25:25,975
我的灰姑娘在等我.
My Cinderelly awaits.

359
00:25:26,043 --> 00:25:29,012
王子, 你将会娶阿纳斯塔西娅.
Princey, you will marry Anastasia.

360
00:25:29,079 --> 00:25:30,569
阿纳斯塔西娅.
Anesthesia.

361
00:25:30,647 --> 00:25:33,172
'神奇大变身'.
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo.

362
00:25:33,784 --> 00:25:37,220
她让他忘记了我.
She made him forget who I am.

363
00:25:38,889 --> 00:25:42,655
魔法! 这样就能解释了.
Magic! That explains it.

364
00:25:44,461 --> 00:25:47,021
伙计们, 我们得拿到那根魔杖!
Boys, we have to get that wand!

365
00:25:47,497 --> 00:25:50,523
太太, 国王指示我
Madame, the King himself
has instructed me

366
00:25:50,601 --> 00:25:53,331
全权负责此次婚礼.
to be solely in charge of this affair.

367
00:25:53,403 --> 00:25:56,839
我向你保证一切都在我的掌握之下.
I assure you
I have it entirely under control.

368
00:25:56,907 --> 00:25:58,602
哦, 真的么?
Oh, really?

369
00:26:03,413 --> 00:26:05,074
看看这个!
Look at that!

370
00:26:05,148 --> 00:26:07,048
太棒了!
It's perfect!

371
00:26:14,124 --> 00:26:16,115
真香啊.
They smell lovely.

372
00:26:16,193 --> 00:26:18,286
马上把这些玫瑰花扔掉.
Dispose of those roses at once.

373
00:26:18,362 --> 00:26:20,193
阿纳斯塔西娅的健康很...
Anastasia's health is quite...

374
00:26:20,264 --> 00:26:21,697
啊嚏!
Ah-choo!

375
00:26:23,300 --> 00:26:24,631
...重要.
...delicate.

376
00:26:24,701 --> 00:26:27,135
我确定我跟你说过.
I'm quite sure
I mentioned that to you.

377
00:26:27,204 --> 00:26:30,867
- 太太, 我没有...
- 很确定.
- Madame, I do not...
- Quite sure.

378
00:26:31,908 --> 00:26:32,897
好的.
Yes.

379
00:26:32,977 --> 00:26:38,040
也许年轻的小姐们愿意尝一下点心.
Well, perhaps the young ladies
would like to sample the hors d'oeuvres.

380
00:26:40,918 --> 00:26:42,909
听着, 一句话.
Your Grace, a word.

381
00:26:44,422 --> 00:26:47,585
这种准备完全不合格.
These preparations
are entirely unacceptable.

382
00:26:49,961 --> 00:26:51,656
跟猪一样!
What a pig!

383
00:26:54,799 --> 00:26:56,426
现在谁是猪了?
Who's the pig now?

384
00:27:01,172 --> 00:27:03,163
你把这叫做蛋糕?
 You call this a cake?

385
00:27:06,477 --> 00:27:09,173
婚礼必须反映出我女儿的尊贵.
This wedding must reflect
my daughter's elegance.

386
00:27:10,148 --> 00:27:12,946
德瑞拉将会在婚礼上演唱.
Drizella will be singing
in the ceremony.

387
00:27:13,017 --> 00:27:15,008
你确定这是个好主意?
Are you sure that's a good idea?

388
00:27:19,557 --> 00:27:22,526
哦, 当你见到她的时候.
你就知道她多么完美.
Oh, wait till you meet her, Dad.
She has everything.

389
00:27:22,593 --> 00:27:25,892
- 有教养, 典雅...
- 是的, 是的.
- Breeding, refinement...
- Yes, yes.

390
00:27:29,434 --> 00:27:30,799
不!
No!

391
00:27:34,706 --> 00:27:36,697
我们没走错房间吧?
Are we in the right room?

392
00:27:36,774 --> 00:27:39,174
你! 你是怎么搞得这儿一团糟?
You! How could you let this happen?

393
00:27:39,243 --> 00:27:41,768
别介意.
Don't mind this.

394
00:27:41,846 --> 00:27:44,337
我马上就清理干净.
I shall have it cleaned up in no time.

395
00:27:44,416 --> 00:27:46,281
看你干得好事!
See that you do!

396
00:27:46,352 --> 00:27:49,947
我不要这次婚礼有任何差池.
I want this wedding
to go off without a hitch.

397
00:27:50,022 --> 00:27:52,456
如果有的话...
And if it doesn't...

398
00:27:53,559 --> 00:27:55,527
哦, 不! 拜托, 陛下...
Oh, no! Please, sire...

399
00:27:55,594 --> 00:27:57,494
我能解释的. 我, 你看...
I can explain. I well, you see...

400
00:27:57,563 --> 00:28:02,091
爸爸, 让我给你介绍我的准新娘, 阿纳斯塔西娅.
Father, allow me to introduce
my bride-to-be, Anastasia.

401
00:28:02,201 --> 00:28:05,500
阿纳斯塔西娅, 这是我的父亲.
Anastasia, this is my dad.

402
00:28:05,537 --> 00:28:08,438
真是荣幸之至, 陛下.
It is an honor, Your Majesty.

403
00:28:08,507 --> 00:28:11,203
迷人的小姐.
Charmed, I'm sure.

404
00:28:18,917 --> 00:28:22,250
那么谁想跳舞么?
So who's up for a dance?

405
00:28:23,222 --> 00:28:27,249
你的一点出格的行为会毁了一切!
 Your little escapade back
there could have cost us everything!

406
00:28:27,326 --> 00:28:28,884
别搞砸了!
Don't ruin this!

407
00:28:28,961 --> 00:28:30,929
去找他吧, 大脚趾小姐.
Go get him, twinkle toes.

408
00:28:39,938 --> 00:28:43,169
嗯, 我不是经常跳舞的.
Oh, I don't dance much.

409
00:28:43,242 --> 00:28:46,678
你太谦虚了.
我们就是这样见面的, 还记得么?
You're too modest.
That's how we met, remember?

410
00:28:46,745 --> 00:28:48,940
哦, 对, 当然.
Oh, right. Of course.

411
00:28:49,014 --> 00:28:51,744
我永远不会忘记我第一次...
I'll never forget
when I first touched...

412
00:28:52,785 --> 00:28:54,377
...握住你的手.
...your hand.

413
00:29:09,803 --> 00:29:11,361
哦, 对不起.
- Oh! I'm sorry.

414
00:29:11,438 --> 00:29:12,905
这不会再发生了.
It won't happen again.

415
00:29:17,477 --> 00:29:19,911
对不起, 对不起.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.

416
00:29:21,948 --> 00:29:24,473
对不起, 对不起.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.

417
00:29:25,852 --> 00:29:29,253
对不起, 对不起.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.

418
00:29:29,322 --> 00:29:31,153
哦!
- Oh!

419
00:29:38,631 --> 00:29:39,723
对不起.
I'm sorry.

420
00:29:40,900 --> 00:29:44,597
哦, 天哪.
Oh, dear. 

421
00:29:49,809 --> 00:29:51,470
嗯... 你还好么?
Um... Are you OK?

422
00:29:52,745 --> 00:29:56,613
哦, 对不起, 这些不是我的舞鞋.
Oh! Oh, sorry, these aren't my shoes.

423
00:29:56,683 --> 00:30:00,050
我是说, 我到底在说什么?
当然这些是我的鞋.
I mean, what am I saying?
Of course they're my shoes.

424
00:30:00,119 --> 00:30:03,577
哦, 我只是不知道我今天怎么了.
Oh, I just don't know
what's wrong with me today.

425
00:30:03,657 --> 00:30:05,818
哦, 不, 不, 是我的错.
Oh, no, no, it was my fault.

426
00:30:05,893 --> 00:30:09,192
是我不是太熟练最新的舞步.
I'm afraid I'm just not up-to-date
on the latest dance steps.

427
00:30:09,263 --> 00:30:13,359
殿下, 打扰一下, 你要试穿新衣.
Sire, if I may, um, your fitting.

428
00:30:13,434 --> 00:30:17,837
哦, 哦, 是的.
很有趣. 谢谢.
Oh. Oh, yes.
This was fun. Thank you.

429
00:30:17,905 --> 00:30:20,567
那么我先失陪一下.
Well, if you'll please excuse me.

430
00:30:22,276 --> 00:30:24,574
呃, 这边走, 殿下.
 Um, come along, sire.

431
00:30:24,645 --> 00:30:27,944
你试穿之后,
我们得去看看那个牛油雕塑.
And after the fitting,
we must approve the butter sculpture.

432
00:30:28,015 --> 00:30:30,108
我觉得那个棒极了.
I think it's a stunning likeness.

433
00:30:30,184 --> 00:30:32,846
拉拉拉拉拉...
La-la-la-la-la-la...

434
00:30:32,920 --> 00:30:35,684
没有教养, 没有仪态.
Well, no grace, no poise.

435
00:30:35,756 --> 00:30:38,486
除此之外, 都很不错.
Other than that, it was lovely.

436
00:30:38,559 --> 00:30:41,289
他对我很好.
He was nice to me.

437
00:30:41,362 --> 00:30:44,297
那是因为咒语的缘故.
That's because
he's under a spell.

438
00:30:44,365 --> 00:30:47,528
他必须得这样, 爱上你.
He'd have to be, to fall for you.

439
00:30:49,336 --> 00:30:50,633
不只这个.
It's more than that.

440
00:30:50,704 --> 00:30:52,069
女士们!
Ladies!

441
00:30:54,441 --> 00:30:56,466
陛下!
 Your Majesty!

442
00:30:56,544 --> 00:31:01,504
我需要立刻跟我未来的儿媳妇说几句话.
I need to speak with my future
daughter-in-law immediately.

443
00:31:03,617 --> 00:31:05,312
她一个人!
Alone!

444
00:31:11,458 --> 00:31:14,052
在我们还能的时候我们干净逃走吧.
Let's make a run for it while we can.

445
00:31:14,129 --> 00:31:18,532
不, 殿下, 殿下, 我马上会派很多舞蹈老师过来.
No, sire, sire, I'll have a dozen
dance instructors sent in immediately.

446
00:31:18,600 --> 00:31:19,931
有些不对劲.
Something's wrong.

447
00:31:20,001 --> 00:31:22,299
一整队的舞蹈老师.
An army of dance instructors.

448
00:31:22,370 --> 00:31:23,632
不, 不.
No, no.

449
00:31:23,705 --> 00:31:27,334
我以为... 为什么, 我确定昨晚是阿纳斯塔西娅.
I thought... Why, I was sure
it was Anastasia last night.

450
00:31:27,409 --> 00:31:29,570
但是...
But...

451
00:31:29,644 --> 00:31:32,204
...刚才当我握着她的手的时候...
...well, just now when
I touched her hand...

452
00:31:33,582 --> 00:31:35,243
...我一点感觉...
...I felt...

453
00:31:36,618 --> 00:31:38,085
...都没有.
...nothing.

454
00:31:39,154 --> 00:31:41,554
一切我都能解释, 陛下.
Oh, I can explain everything,
Your Majesty.

455
00:31:41,623 --> 00:31:44,057
我有这个内耳的问题, 而且...
I have this,
this inner ear thing and, and...

456
00:31:44,125 --> 00:31:47,822
你, 亲爱的, 舞跳得很惊人.
You, my dear, are a dreadful dancer.

457
00:31:48,797 --> 00:31:51,527
是的, 我知道, 陛下.
Yes, I know, Your Majesty.

458
00:31:51,600 --> 00:31:53,761
这让我想起了我的皇后.
Reminds me of my queen.

459
00:31:53,835 --> 00:31:56,395
她也踩我的脚.
She trod on my feet too.

460
00:31:57,472 --> 00:32:01,431
但是她对我很用心.
But she took very good care of my heart.

461
00:32:02,811 --> 00:32:04,608
来这边, 亲爱的.
 Come here, my dear.

462
00:32:05,714 --> 00:32:08,342
我想给你看些东西.
I want to show you something.

463
00:32:11,219 --> 00:32:14,086
一个公主将会被赐予很多财富.
A princess is bestowed with many riches.

464
00:32:15,390 --> 00:32:18,587
土地, 珠宝, 马匹.
Land, jewels, horses.

465
00:32:20,028 --> 00:32:24,294
但是今天我想给你更有价值的东西.
But today I wish to give you
something much more valuable.

466
00:32:27,937 --> 00:32:28,926
哦.
Oh.

467
00:32:29,005 --> 00:32:30,666
很可爱对吧?
Isn't it lovely?

468
00:32:31,641 --> 00:32:33,370
一个贝壳?
A seashell?

469
00:32:33,442 --> 00:32:37,902
这个贝壳是皇后最珍爱的物品.
This shell was the queen's
most treasured possession.

470
00:32:37,980 --> 00:32:42,679
我们在我们第一次见面的海边发现的.
We found it while
walking by the water the day we met.

471
00:32:42,752 --> 00:32:45,516
我们同时伸手去捡,
You see, we reached
for it at the same moment,

472
00:32:45,588 --> 00:32:49,115
当我们的手碰到一起的时候... 
and when our hands touched... 

473
00:32:49,191 --> 00:32:52,991
...我知道我找到了真爱.
...that's when I knew
I had found true love.

474
00:32:54,263 --> 00:32:57,494
你的感觉只是通过碰到手?
You knew that just by touching her hand?

475
00:32:57,566 --> 00:33:03,505
世界上没有什么比真爱更强大的力量了.
There's no more powerful
force in the world than true love.

476
00:33:09,111 --> 00:33:12,774
那么, 就这样了. 退下吧.
Well, that's all. Run along, now.

477
00:33:12,848 --> 00:33:16,340
- 退下吧.
- 谢谢你, 陛下.
- Run along.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.

478
00:33:16,852 --> 00:33:19,116
我愿意.
I do.

479
00:33:19,188 --> 00:33:20,678
哦, 我愿意.
Oh, I do.

480
00:33:21,924 --> 00:33:25,621
我愿意.
I do. I do.

481
00:33:25,695 --> 00:33:27,890
我真的愿意.
I really do.

482
00:33:30,833 --> 00:33:32,357
哦!
 Oh!

483
00:33:35,539 --> 00:33:36,699
哦, 我愿意.
Oh, I do.

484
00:33:40,310 --> 00:33:44,974
 现在终于有人爱上我
 Now there is finally
someone to love me

485
00:33:45,048 --> 00:33:49,542
 他将给我展示我从没有见过的世界
 He'll show me a world
that I never knew

486
00:33:49,619 --> 00:33:54,750
 只是两个词,
我的梦想立刻成真
 With two simple words,
all my dreams will come true

487
00:33:54,825 --> 00:33:56,656
 我愿意
 I do

488
00:33:56,727 --> 00:34:01,494
 我愿意 
 I do 

489
00:34:18,048 --> 00:34:20,243
你去把王子找来.
You go get the Prince.

490
00:34:20,317 --> 00:34:22,478
大一点!
Bigger!

491
00:34:22,552 --> 00:34:24,520
哦, 我们试试这个!
Ooh, let's try this!

492
00:34:25,822 --> 00:34:27,551
哦, 真好看.
Oh, that's gorgeous.

493
00:34:32,262 --> 00:34:33,752
好看.
Lovely.

494
00:34:33,830 --> 00:34:36,856
德瑞拉, 马上给我停下来!
Drizella, stop that this instant!

495
00:34:38,435 --> 00:34:41,131
这个魔杖不是玩具.
This wand is not a toy.

496
00:34:41,204 --> 00:34:44,139
在梳妆台里.
钥匙在她口袋里.
It's in the dresser.
Key's in her pocket.

497
00:34:48,346 --> 00:34:49,711
我得进去.
I've got to get in there.

498
00:34:49,781 --> 00:34:51,408
灰姑娘! 她们会发现你的!
Cinderelly! They'll see you!

499
00:34:51,482 --> 00:34:53,211
- 是的, 太危险了.
- 但是我...
- Yeah, too dangerous.
- But I...

500
00:34:53,284 --> 00:34:54,808
交给我们好了!
We'll take care of it!

501
00:34:54,886 --> 00:34:56,251
我愿意.
I do.

502
00:34:56,320 --> 00:34:58,686
我愿意.
I do.

503
00:34:58,790 --> 00:35:00,087
我愿意.
I do.

504
00:35:00,792 --> 00:35:04,592
我愿意, 哦, 我愿意.
I do. Oh, I do.

505
00:35:12,103 --> 00:35:16,267
好吧, 不管你们干什么,
离路西弗远点.
Alright, but whatever you do,
stay clear of Lucifer.

506
00:35:16,340 --> 00:35:18,706
吱吱. 躲着路西弗.
Zug-zug. No Lucifee.

507
00:35:19,677 --> 00:35:21,440
怎么了? 国王说什么?
What happened?
What'd the King say?

508
00:35:22,847 --> 00:35:24,906
他真的是好人.
He's really very nice.

509
00:35:24,982 --> 00:35:27,746
他把最珍贵的东西给我了.
He gave me his most prized possession.

510
00:35:27,819 --> 00:35:30,287
一个贝壳?
A seashell?

511
00:35:30,354 --> 00:35:32,083
代表着真爱.
It's a symbol of true love.

512
00:35:33,391 --> 00:35:35,757
哦, 拜托.
Oh, please.

513
00:35:35,827 --> 00:35:40,855
- 真的很特别啊.
- 他说他的心...
- How special.
- He said that his heart...

514
00:35:40,932 --> 00:35:44,561
爱情跟我们的魔杖比起来怎么样?
 What's love compared
to the power we hold with the wand?

515
00:35:44,635 --> 00:35:46,762
你很快就知道了.
You will learn that soon enough.

516
00:35:48,239 --> 00:35:50,469
我希望王子能爱上我.
I want the Prince to love me.

517
00:35:50,541 --> 00:35:52,509
我觉得他会的.
I think he could.

518
00:35:52,577 --> 00:35:55,842
你是认真的.
Oh, you're serious.

519
00:35:55,914 --> 00:35:58,439
国王也很喜欢我.
Well, the King likes me too.

520
00:35:58,517 --> 00:36:02,317
他把我当成自己的女儿.
也许我们不应该这么干.
He treated me like his own daughter.
Maybe we shouldn't be doing this.

521
00:36:02,821 --> 00:36:05,654
也许应该是我穿上那只舞鞋.
Maybe I should
have put on the slipper.

522
00:36:06,792 --> 00:36:09,226
也许我们根本就不需要魔杖.
Maybe we don't
even need the wand.

523
00:36:16,034 --> 00:36:17,092
哦!
Oh!

524
00:36:18,136 --> 00:36:20,730
来人把猫赶走!
Oh! Somebody put out the cat!

525
00:36:23,375 --> 00:36:26,970
路西弗! 站住! 停下来!
Lucifer!
Oh, hold still! Stop!

526
00:36:38,090 --> 00:36:39,921
路西弗!
- Lucifer!

527
00:36:40,492 --> 00:36:43,393
谁把管家叫来.
Someone fetch the housekeeper.

528
00:36:46,765 --> 00:36:48,562
整理房间.
Housekeeping.

529
00:36:52,404 --> 00:36:54,736
你真的是很快啊.
Well, you certainly came quickly.

530
00:36:54,806 --> 00:36:57,604
我们是最棒的.
We're very good.

531
00:37:02,347 --> 00:37:06,545
把这里清理干净. 
我的女儿在晚上婚礼前要好好睡上一觉.
Clean this up. My daughter needs her
beauty sleep before tonight's wedding.

532
00:37:06,619 --> 00:37:09,213
时间够么?
Think that'll be enough time?

533
00:37:24,771 --> 00:37:27,763
离女佣远点.
Keep out of the maid's way, girls.

534
00:37:27,840 --> 00:37:30,775
婚礼前还有很多事情要做.
There's a lot to do before the wedding.

535
00:37:31,644 --> 00:37:33,544
嗯?
Hmm?

536
00:37:37,283 --> 00:37:40,377
对不对啊, 灰姑娘?
Isn't that right, Cinderella?

537
00:37:41,521 --> 00:37:44,285
我不知道你在这里工作.
 I didn't know you worked here.

538
00:37:46,426 --> 00:37:48,758
你真比我想的要执着得多.
You're far more persistent
than I thought.

539
00:37:48,828 --> 00:37:50,728
我不会让你得逞的.
I won't let you get away with this.

540
00:37:50,797 --> 00:37:53,789
- 我们已经得逞了.
- 我不这么认为.
- We already have.
- I don't think so.

541
00:37:53,866 --> 00:37:55,458
杰克! 格斯!
Jaq! Gus!

542
00:37:58,571 --> 00:38:00,505
魔杖!
- The wand!

543
00:38:02,208 --> 00:38:03,800
我们来了, 灰姑娘!
Us coming, Cinderelly!

544
00:38:07,347 --> 00:38:09,542
耶! 哇喔!
Yeah! Whoo-hoo!

545
00:38:10,183 --> 00:38:13,152
那个女仆是个小偷! 抓住她!
That servant girl is a thief! Get her!

546
00:38:15,254 --> 00:38:16,619
吱吱.
Zug-zug.

547
00:38:18,592 --> 00:38:20,287
'神奇大变身'.
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo.

548
00:38:31,839 --> 00:38:33,670
站住! 小偷!
Stop! Thief!

549
00:38:33,741 --> 00:38:36,369
- 马上抓住她!
- 别动! 站住!
- Seize her at once!
- Don't move! Hold it!

550
00:38:36,443 --> 00:38:37,933
以国王的名义, 马上站住!
Halt in the name of the King!

551
00:38:43,183 --> 00:38:44,946
哇!
Whoa!

552
00:38:46,787 --> 00:38:48,721
你们这群笨蛋!
You incompetent fools!

553
00:38:52,459 --> 00:38:53,721
哇!
Whoa!

554
00:38:56,096 --> 00:38:58,826
'神奇大变身'!
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo!

555
00:39:06,240 --> 00:39:08,174
格斯!
Gus Gus!

556
00:39:17,718 --> 00:39:19,549
跑, 格斯!
Run, Gus Gus!

557
00:39:19,620 --> 00:39:21,144
神奇大变身!
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo!

558
00:39:32,167 --> 00:39:34,328
她在那儿! 我们抓住她了.
There she is! We've got her.

559
00:39:34,402 --> 00:39:35,835
你, 站住!
You there, halt!

560
00:39:35,904 --> 00:39:37,838
站住!
Halt!

561
00:39:39,074 --> 00:39:41,065
以国王的名义, 开门!
Open up in the name of the King!

562
00:39:43,778 --> 00:39:45,837
哦, 嗨.
Oh, hello.

563
00:39:45,914 --> 00:39:48,405
哦! 嘿! 发生什么事了?
Oh! Hey! What's going on?

564
00:39:49,951 --> 00:39:51,009
嗯.
Hmm.

565
00:39:51,086 --> 00:39:54,078
呃... 好吧, 我来了.
Uh... Alright, I'm coming.

566
00:39:54,155 --> 00:39:55,554
灰姑娘!
Cinderelly!

567
00:39:55,623 --> 00:39:57,215
开门, 我说的!
Open up, I say!

568
00:39:57,292 --> 00:39:58,953
格斯!
Gus Gus!

569
00:40:01,863 --> 00:40:03,194
接着.
Catch.

570
00:40:06,134 --> 00:40:08,068
快开门!
Open up in the name of the King!

571
00:40:09,637 --> 00:40:11,764
解除咒语. 让他记起来.
Lift the spell. Let him remember.

572
00:40:12,440 --> 00:40:14,533
'神奇大变身'!
Bibbidi-bobbidi!

573
00:40:15,643 --> 00:40:17,133
噢!
Ooh!

574
00:40:18,713 --> 00:40:20,374
不!
No!

575
00:40:20,448 --> 00:40:22,541
- 发生什么事了?
- 很抱歉.
- What's going on?
- My apologies.

576
00:40:22,617 --> 00:40:24,608
是我的女仆的问题.
It's a problem with my maid.

577
00:40:24,686 --> 00:40:27,120
- 已经没事了.
- 你还好么?
- It's under control.
- Are you OK?

578
00:40:27,188 --> 00:40:30,248
- 这个女的是个小偷.
- 我不是小偷.
- This servant girl is a thief.
- I am not a thief.

579
00:40:30,325 --> 00:40:33,783
你被下了咒语. 
所以你不记得我了, 拜托!
You're under a spell. That's why
you don't remember me. Please!

580
00:40:33,862 --> 00:40:34,954
相信我!
Just listen!

581
00:40:40,703 --> 00:40:43,604
我们走!
Let go!

582
00:40:43,672 --> 00:40:47,836
可怜的孩子.
很显然精神有点失常.
Poor child.
Obviously out of her mind.

583
00:40:47,910 --> 00:40:49,571
我希望她会很好.
I hope she'll be alright.

584
00:40:49,645 --> 00:40:52,637
你知道么, 当我见到她的时候她还是个好女孩.
She seemed, you know,
nice when I met her.

585
00:40:52,715 --> 00:40:55,240
可能只是误会,
Well, maybe a little confused, but,

586
00:40:55,317 --> 00:40:57,444
但是我总觉得她...
still there's something about her...

587
00:40:57,520 --> 00:41:00,819
哦, 别给自己找麻烦了, 殿下.
Oh, don't trouble yourself,
Your Highness.

588
00:41:00,923 --> 00:41:05,360
我会亲自过问的, 保证她得到所有她要的帮助.
I'll see to it, personally,
that she gets all the help she needs.

589
00:41:05,394 --> 00:41:09,490
干得好, 但是我们赢了!
Nice try, but we won! 

590
00:41:09,565 --> 00:41:11,999
你赢了? 什么意思?
You won? What do you mean?

591
00:41:12,635 --> 00:41:16,071
呃...这个...
Uh... Well...

592
00:41:16,138 --> 00:41:17,605
...没什么.
...nothing.

593
00:41:18,541 --> 00:41:21,271
喔... 呃...
I... um...

594
00:41:21,343 --> 00:41:23,504
你会亲自照看她?
You'll see she's taken care of?

595
00:41:23,579 --> 00:41:25,911
是的, 殿下.
Personally, Your Highness.

596
00:41:29,084 --> 00:41:31,552
送她上下一班离开王国的船.
Put her on the next ship
leaving the kingdom.

597
00:41:31,620 --> 00:41:33,986
我要她永远消失.
I want her banished forever.

598
00:41:34,056 --> 00:41:35,523
嗯.
Mmm.

599
00:41:36,392 --> 00:41:37,984
而你...
And you...

600
00:41:38,060 --> 00:41:40,551
闭上你的嘴不然你就是下一个.
Keep your mouth shut or you're next.

601
00:41:41,530 --> 00:41:45,432
很合身.
 Quite fetching.

602
00:41:45,501 --> 00:41:46,593
啊!
- Ouch!

603
00:41:46,669 --> 00:41:48,660
小心那些别针.
Careful with those pins down there.

604
00:41:48,738 --> 00:41:51,764
爸爸, 我觉得很奇怪.
- Dad, something strange is going on.

605
00:41:51,841 --> 00:41:55,504
我会说.
我的儿子终于要结婚了.
I'll say.
My son is finally getting married.

606
00:41:55,579 --> 00:41:57,740
不, 不, 我是说有些事不对劲.
No. No, I mean something's wrong.

607
00:41:57,814 --> 00:42:02,148
哦, 胡说, 我的孩子. 
是你要找那个穿上舞鞋的女孩的.
Oh, nonsense, my boy. You wanted
the girl who fit the glass slipper.

608
00:42:02,252 --> 00:42:04,117
- 是的, 但是...
- 现在你找到她了.
- Yes, but...
- Now you've got her.

609
00:42:04,154 --> 00:42:05,519
嘿.
Hey.

610
00:42:05,589 --> 00:42:07,284
这就是我担心的.
That's what I'm worried about.

611
00:42:07,357 --> 00:42:09,552
嘿, 王子! 王子!
Psst! Hey, Princey! Prince!

612
00:42:09,626 --> 00:42:12,390
- 这里!
- 王子!
- Over here!
- Princey!

613
00:42:12,462 --> 00:42:14,259
王子!
Psst! Psst!

614
00:42:14,331 --> 00:42:17,357
- 我?
- 是的, 你. 我们走.
- Me?
- Yes, you. Let's go.

615
00:42:20,537 --> 00:42:24,405
OK, 先是小鸟, 现在又是老鼠.
OK, first birds, now mice.

616
00:42:24,474 --> 00:42:26,032
快点!
Come on!

617
00:42:41,224 --> 00:42:42,452
喂?
Hello?

618
00:42:46,763 --> 00:42:50,358
喂? 嗯... 小老鼠?
Hello? Uh... little mice?

619
00:42:53,303 --> 00:42:56,534
看来是真的了. 我精神出问题了.
Well, it's official. I've lost my mind.

620
00:42:56,606 --> 00:43:00,633
先是被小鸟劫持,
现在又看到了虚幻的老鼠.
First I was hijacked by birds,
and now I'm talking to imaginary mice.

621
00:43:03,214 --> 00:43:06,047
嘿, 王子! 在这里!
Hey, Prince Prince! Down here!

622
00:43:06,117 --> 00:43:07,482
好了
OK.

623
00:43:08,886 --> 00:43:10,979
也许又不是那么虚幻.
Maybe not so imaginary.

624
00:43:11,055 --> 00:43:14,422
继母得到了一根魔杖,
向你下了咒语. 愚弄了所有人.
Stepmother got a magic wand,
put spell on you. Fooled everyone.

625
00:43:14,492 --> 00:43:16,357
...到皇宫来和你结婚!
...came to the palace to marry you!

626
00:43:16,427 --> 00:43:19,521
等下, 等下.
我想我明白.
Wait, hold on. Hold on.
I think I understand.

627
00:43:21,032 --> 00:43:22,556
实际上, 我还是什么都不明白.
Actually, I got nothing.

628
00:43:24,268 --> 00:43:26,998
我们应该怎么做?
Duh... What should we gonna do?

629
00:43:27,605 --> 00:43:28,594
啊!
Ahh!

630
00:43:33,711 --> 00:43:35,906
 你曾和一个很美丽的女孩跳舞
 You were dancing
with a very pretty girl

631
00:43:35,980 --> 00:43:37,948
-  美丽的女孩
-  午夜时分她跑走了
-  Pretty girl
-  At midnight she ran off

632
00:43:38,015 --> 00:43:39,846
-  像这样急
-  像这样急
-  In such a whirl
-  Such a whirl

633
00:43:39,917 --> 00:43:42,715
 她名字叫灰姑娘
她是你见到的那个女仆
 Her name was Cinderelly
She's the servant girl you met

634
00:43:42,787 --> 00:43:44,379
 她才是你想娶的那个女孩
 She's the one you want to marry

635
00:43:44,455 --> 00:43:45,979
 不要忘记! 不要忘记!
 Don't forget! Don't forget!

636
00:43:46,057 --> 00:43:49,026
-  在舞会上, 在舞会上
-  在舞会上, 在舞会上
-  At the ball, at the ball
-  At the ball, at the ball

637
00:43:49,093 --> 00:43:51,789
 灰姑娘才是舞会的女主角
 Cinderelly was the maiden at the ball

638
00:43:51,862 --> 00:43:54,160
不, 我是和阿纳斯塔西娅跳的舞.
No, I danced with Anastasia at the ball.

639
00:43:54,231 --> 00:43:58,668
不, 不. 因为灰姑娘的继母王子才会这么想.
No, no. Princey only think that
because of Cinderelly's stepmother.

640
00:43:58,736 --> 00:44:00,203
对, 卑鄙的老女人.
Yeah, mean old lady.

641
00:44:01,072 --> 00:44:03,165
 用一根魔杖
她使用了邪恶的咒语
 With a magic wand
she cast a wicked spell

642
00:44:03,240 --> 00:44:04,229
 邪恶的咒语
 Wicked spell

643
00:44:04,308 --> 00:44:06,333
 所以让王子觉得不对劲
 Which is why Princey
isn't feeling well

644
00:44:06,410 --> 00:44:08,503
-  不对劲
-  你忘记了灰姑娘
-  Not well
-  You've forgotten Cinderelly

645
00:44:08,579 --> 00:44:10,376
 还有那晚的舞蹈
 And the dance you shared last night

646
00:44:10,449 --> 00:44:12,849
 但是我们知道补救一切还不是太迟
 But we know it's not too late
to set things right

647
00:44:12,918 --> 00:44:15,148
 因为在舞会上!
在舞会上! 在舞会上!
 'Cause at the ball!
At the ball! At the ball!

648
00:44:15,220 --> 00:44:16,209
 对, 在舞会上!
 Yeah, at the ball

649
00:44:16,288 --> 00:44:18,518
 灰姑娘才是舞会的女主角
 Cinderelly was the maiden at the ball

650
00:44:18,590 --> 00:44:19,887
等下, 等下!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Wait!

651
00:44:19,958 --> 00:44:22,222
你们是说我被下了咒语?
You're telling me
I'm under a magic spell?

652
00:44:22,294 --> 00:44:24,285
这才是最坏的地方.
And here's the worst part.

653
00:44:24,363 --> 00:44:26,763
 当灰姑娘努力要争取的时候
 When Cinderelly
tried her best to take a stand

654
00:44:26,832 --> 00:44:27,821
 努力争取
 Take a stand

655
00:44:27,899 --> 00:44:30,891
 卑鄙的老女人想要她从此消失...
 Mean old lady had her
banished from the land...

656
00:44:34,139 --> 00:44:36,039
格斯!
Gus Gus!

657
00:44:36,108 --> 00:44:37,166
对不起.
Sorry.

658
00:44:38,243 --> 00:44:41,041
 灰姑娘现在在那艘会送她去很远的地方的船上
 Cinderelly's on a ship
that's gonna sail her far away

659
00:44:41,113 --> 00:44:43,274
 需要王子才能救她
 It's up to Princey-Prince
to save the day

660
00:44:43,348 --> 00:44:45,009
 因为在舞会上, 在舞会上,
 'Cause at the ball, at the ball,

661
00:44:45,083 --> 00:44:46,778
-  在舞会上
-  在舞会上
-  At the ball
-  What a ball

662
00:44:46,852 --> 00:44:49,878
-  灰姑娘赢得了你的心
-  没有魔法能让你分开
-  Cinderelly won your heart
-  Now magic's keeping you apart

663
00:44:49,955 --> 00:44:53,391
-  而她很快就要永远离开
-  除非你能回忆起
-  And she'll soon be gone forever
-  Unless you can recall

664
00:44:53,458 --> 00:44:58,555
 那个灰姑娘才是舞会的女主角
 That Cinderelly
was the maiden at the ball

665
00:44:58,630 --> 00:45:00,029
 在舞会上! 
 At the ball! 

666
00:45:00,098 --> 00:45:01,895
魔法?
Magic?

667
00:45:01,967 --> 00:45:05,664
魔法让我以为阿纳斯塔西娅是舞会上的那个女孩?
Magic made me think
Anastasia was the girl at the ball?

668
00:45:07,639 --> 00:45:09,573
这就能解释一切了.
That would explain everything.

669
00:45:09,641 --> 00:45:11,268
对!
Yeah! 

670
00:45:21,287 --> 00:45:23,687
什么? 女仆?
What? The servant girl?

671
00:45:23,756 --> 00:45:27,453
那个灰姑娘? 这个是她的?
This Cinderelly? This belongs to her?

672
00:45:27,527 --> 00:45:30,087
- 是的! 是的!
- 我要去找她.
- Yeah! Yeah!
- I have to find her.

673
00:45:30,163 --> 00:45:33,098
- 对! 对!
- 棒极了!
- Yeah! Yeah!
- Yeah! Yeah!

674
00:45:34,634 --> 00:45:37,831
- 再来一次.
- 耶.
- One more time.
- Duh, yeah.

675
00:45:37,904 --> 00:45:39,804
 在舞会上! 在舞会上!
 At the ball! At the ball!

676
00:45:39,872 --> 00:45:41,863
 我们向王子展示了
 We showed ol' Princey after all

677
00:45:41,941 --> 00:45:45,775
 灰姑娘才是女主角
 That Cinderelly was the maiden

678
00:45:45,845 --> 00:45:49,337
 在舞会上!
 At the ball!

679
00:45:50,216 --> 00:45:52,150
 恰! 
 Cha! 

680
00:45:52,218 --> 00:45:54,379
哦... 谢谢.
- Oh... thanks.

681
00:45:54,454 --> 00:45:56,649
还有, 我很喜欢这首歌.
And loved the song.

682
00:45:56,722 --> 00:45:59,213
- 快走! 王子, 快去!
- 快去!
- Go! Go! Go, Princey! Shoo! Shoo!
- Go! Go!

683
00:46:01,461 --> 00:46:02,951
我得走了.
I have to go.

684
00:46:03,029 --> 00:46:06,123
走? 但是你很快要结婚了.
Go? But you're about to be married.

685
00:46:07,033 --> 00:46:09,661
但是那些会说话的老鼠说不是这个女孩.
But the talking mice
say she's the wrong girl.

686
00:46:09,735 --> 00:46:12,329
儿子, 等一下!
Son, wait!

687
00:46:13,239 --> 00:46:16,834
儿子! 会说话的老鼠? 儿子?
Son! Talking mice? Son?

688
00:46:16,909 --> 00:46:17,933
呜呼!
Whoo-hoo!

689
00:46:18,010 --> 00:46:20,410
- 还有两只蓝鸟.
- 会说话的蓝鸟?
- And two bluebirds.
- Talking bluebirds?

690
00:46:22,081 --> 00:46:24,982
不, 蓝鸟没有说话. 听着, 爸爸...
No, the bluebirds
weren't talking. Look, Dad...

691
00:46:25,051 --> 00:46:26,575
这太荒谬了.
This is ridiculous.

692
00:46:26,652 --> 00:46:29,177
是你答应要娶那个穿得上舞鞋的女孩.
You agreed to marry
the girl in the glass slipper.

693
00:46:29,255 --> 00:46:32,281
- 我完全同意你的决定.
- 而我也会的.
- I was completely with you on that one.
- And I will.

694
00:46:32,359 --> 00:46:34,657
- 嗯?
- 只是我要先找到她.
- Huh?
- Just as soon as I find her.

695
00:46:34,728 --> 00:46:39,256
我禁止你再往前走一步!
I forbid you to take
another step down these stairs!

696
00:46:41,434 --> 00:46:42,458
好吧
OK.

697
00:46:44,270 --> 00:46:47,000
儿子! 回来!
 Son! Come back!

698
00:46:47,073 --> 00:46:50,008
我们会帮你找个医生.
我们会给你治疗的.
We'll find you a doctor.
We'll have you leeched.

699
00:46:53,612 --> 00:46:55,944
我们得去找!
We've got to get!

700
00:46:56,015 --> 00:46:59,781
警卫!
Guards! 

701
00:46:59,852 --> 00:47:01,376
哎呦!
Aye!

702
00:47:01,454 --> 00:47:04,321
那个女仆. 她在哪里?
The servant girl. Where is she?

703
00:47:04,390 --> 00:47:07,382
警卫! 他完全疯掉了!
Guards! He's gone completely mad!

704
00:47:07,460 --> 00:47:09,257
- 陛下!
- 截住我的儿子.
- Your Majesty!
- Stop my son.

705
00:47:09,328 --> 00:47:11,353
你的血压!
Your blood pressure!

706
00:47:11,430 --> 00:47:13,489
停下! 停下!
- Stop! Stop!

707
00:47:13,566 --> 00:47:14,931
爸爸, 相信我.
Dad, trust me.

708
00:47:15,000 --> 00:47:18,128
爸爸! 我相信你.
Son! I do trust you.

709
00:47:18,204 --> 00:47:20,798
但是我不相信会说话的老鼠.
It's the talking mice I'm worried about.

710
00:47:22,541 --> 00:47:24,509
驾!
Hiyah!

711
00:47:24,577 --> 00:47:25,566
儿子!
Son!

712
00:47:25,644 --> 00:47:28,044
关上大门! 关上大门!
Close the gates! Close the gates!

713
00:47:35,888 --> 00:47:38,413
没关系的. 别往上看.
Lt'll be fine. Don't look up.

714
00:47:39,325 --> 00:47:40,690
驾! 驾!
Hiyah! Hiyah!

715
00:47:43,997 --> 00:47:45,897
好小子.
Good boy.

716
00:47:47,801 --> 00:47:50,235
- 耶!
- 去找到她, 小王子!
- Yeah!
- Go get her, Princey!

717
00:47:52,773 --> 00:47:55,640
我马上派军队去追他, 陛下.
I'll send the troops after him
at once, Your Majesty.

718
00:47:55,709 --> 00:47:57,768
不, 让他去吧.
No, let him go.

719
00:47:57,844 --> 00:48:00,039
但是... 但是, 陛下, 婚礼怎么办.
But... but, Your Majesty, the wedding.

720
00:48:00,113 --> 00:48:01,774
让他去吧.
Let him go.

721
00:48:19,966 --> 00:48:21,797
该启程了.
Time to go.

722
00:48:31,645 --> 00:48:34,079
都上甲板来.
All hands on deck.

723
00:48:55,203 --> 00:48:58,195
 我一直在梦想
 I've always dreamed

724
00:48:58,306 --> 00:49:01,503
 我的生活能像
 That my life could be

725
00:49:01,542 --> 00:49:03,942
 童话故事那样
 Like a fairy-tale

726
00:49:04,011 --> 00:49:07,777
 完美而甜蜜
 A perfect fantasy

727
00:49:14,088 --> 00:49:16,750
 但是这只能
 But it was nothing more

728
00:49:17,859 --> 00:49:20,487
 是一个梦 
 Than a dream 

729
00:49:20,561 --> 00:49:23,257
把帆放下来!
Loose the mainsail!

730
00:49:43,184 --> 00:49:44,515
驾!
Hiyah!

731
00:50:12,447 --> 00:50:14,813
加油, 小子! 你能行的.
Come on, boy! Nothing to it.

732
00:50:18,287 --> 00:50:20,721
驾!
- Hiyah!

733
00:50:53,989 --> 00:50:55,320
还记得我么?
Remember me?

734
00:51:23,052 --> 00:51:26,215
你愿意嫁给我么, 泥姑娘?
Will you marry me, Cinderelly?

735
00:51:26,289 --> 00:51:30,419
是的, 但是... 实际上,
Yes, but...  actually,

736
00:51:30,493 --> 00:51:32,290
是灰姑娘.
it's Cinderella.

737
00:51:32,362 --> 00:51:35,126
灰姑娘!
-  Cinderella!

738
00:51:35,298 --> 00:51:37,823
- 还没有结束!
- 什么?
- It's not over yet!
- What?

739
00:51:37,900 --> 00:51:40,767
他以为他能毁了我的计划.
He thinks he can ruin my plans.

740
00:51:40,837 --> 00:51:42,270
我不这么认为.
I think not.

741
00:51:42,338 --> 00:51:43,327
谁?
Who?

742
00:51:43,406 --> 00:51:46,534
王子. 他去追灰姑娘了.
The Prince. He's gone after Cinderella.

743
00:51:46,609 --> 00:51:50,272
- 但是我以为他爱我.
- 妈妈!
- But I thought he loved me.
- Mother!

744
00:52:03,693 --> 00:52:05,354
警卫! 警卫!
Guards! Guards!

745
00:52:10,033 --> 00:52:12,126
没有用. 魔法没有起作用.
It's no use. The magic didn't work.

746
00:52:12,201 --> 00:52:15,830
- 它比不过他们的...
- 你想要王子爱上你?
- It wasn't as powerful as their...
- You want the Prince to love you?

747
00:52:15,905 --> 00:52:16,929
开门!
Open up!

748
00:52:17,006 --> 00:52:18,633
是的, 当然我希望.
Well, yes. Yes, of course I do.

749
00:52:18,708 --> 00:52:20,608
- 非常地想.
- More than anything.

750
00:52:20,676 --> 00:52:23,338
- 那么就照我说的做.
- 开门!
- Then do exactly as I say.
- Open up!

751
00:52:23,414 --> 00:52:25,541
快点开门!
Open up in the name of the King!

752
00:52:27,751 --> 00:52:29,309
嗯?
Huh?

753
00:52:30,087 --> 00:52:31,679
嗯.
Hmm.

754
00:52:31,755 --> 00:52:35,350
在我儿子身上用魔法. 真大胆.
Using magic on my son. The nerve.

755
00:52:35,426 --> 00:52:38,987
陛下, 我们找遍了城堡的每一个角落.
Your Majesty, we've gone over
every inch of the castle.

756
00:52:39,063 --> 00:52:40,553
看起来她们好像跑掉了.
It appears they have fled.

757
00:52:41,465 --> 00:52:43,865
那么搜索整个王国!
Then search my entire kingdom!

758
00:52:43,934 --> 00:52:47,995
我要找到并逮捕她们, 马上!
I want them found and arrested,
immediately!

759
00:52:50,641 --> 00:52:52,632
请注意我是一个老人了
Keep in mind that I'm an old man

760
00:52:52,709 --> 00:52:55,678
我的心脏承受能力有限.
and my heart can only take so much.

761
00:52:55,746 --> 00:52:58,044
拜托, 拜托, 拜托,
Please, please, please,

762
00:52:58,115 --> 00:53:01,881
告诉我这个就是你想娶的那个女孩.
tell me that this is the girl
you intend to marry.

763
00:53:03,654 --> 00:53:08,421
天上的星星都亮了很多,
爸爸, 就像你说的.
All the stars are shining brighter,
Dad, just like you said.

764
00:53:08,492 --> 00:53:10,221
那么我们还在等什么?!
Then what are we waiting for?!

765
00:53:10,294 --> 00:53:14,993
把种花人找来!
烤一个更大的蛋糕.
Fetch the florist!
Bake an even bigger cake.

766
00:53:15,065 --> 00:53:17,932
婚礼就是今晚!
The wedding is on tonight!

767
00:53:20,404 --> 00:53:24,340
不. 像这样?
Duh, no. This a way?

768
00:53:24,408 --> 00:53:26,342
呃，呃，呃
Uh, uh, uh.

769
00:53:26,410 --> 00:53:28,344
不, 不, 往那边.
No, no, no, no... thatta way.

770
00:53:28,412 --> 00:53:29,572
对对!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!

771
00:53:30,347 --> 00:53:31,609
对.
Yes.

772
00:53:32,983 --> 00:53:34,678
谢谢你.
Thank you.

773
00:53:35,920 --> 00:53:38,218
你看起来真美啊, 亲爱的.
How lovely you look, my dear.

774
00:53:38,289 --> 00:53:39,620
继母?
Stepmother?

775
00:53:42,093 --> 00:53:44,118
咄
Duh.

776
00:53:53,471 --> 00:53:55,769
看起来你是对的, 灰姑娘.
It appears you were right, Cinderella.

777
00:53:56,374 --> 00:53:58,740
王子确实想和你结婚.
The Prince does want to marry you.

778
00:53:58,810 --> 00:54:01,904
和你白头偕老.
And marry you he shall.

779
00:54:01,980 --> 00:54:03,777
阿纳斯塔西娅.
Anastasia.

780
00:54:04,883 --> 00:54:05,941
阿纳斯塔西娅!
Anastasia!

781
00:54:19,164 --> 00:54:22,600
或者我应该说..."灰姑娘."
Or should I say..."Cinderella."

782
00:54:25,603 --> 00:54:27,264
你都干了什么?
What have you done?

783
00:54:27,338 --> 00:54:29,306
王子不会被骗到的.
The Prince won't be fooled.

784
00:54:29,374 --> 00:54:31,239
王子永远不会知道.
The Prince will never know.

785
00:54:31,309 --> 00:54:33,573
他将会很快乐.
He'll be perfectly happy.

786
00:54:34,846 --> 00:54:38,782
但是你呢, 阿纳斯塔西娅?
你会快乐么?
But will you, Anastasia?
Will you be happy?

787
00:54:38,850 --> 00:54:41,910
我想得到你有的.
I... I want what you had.

788
00:54:41,986 --> 00:54:44,477
但是你爱他么?
But do you even love him?

789
00:54:44,557 --> 00:54:47,856
- 我...
- 爱! 看看你自己都是什么样了.
- I...
- Love! Look where it's gotten you.

790
00:54:49,528 --> 00:54:51,291
灰姑娘!
Cinderelly!

791
00:55:02,875 --> 00:55:04,365
灰姑娘!
Cinderelly!

792
00:55:04,443 --> 00:55:06,604
怎么回事, 灰姑娘?
What's happened, Cinderelly?

793
00:55:24,897 --> 00:55:29,857
路西弗, 确保他们不会...
Lucifer, make absolutely certain
they don't come back...

794
00:55:29,935 --> 00:55:31,994
...活着回来.
...alive.

795
00:55:32,071 --> 00:55:33,971
'神奇大变身'.
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo.

796
00:55:41,513 --> 00:55:43,105
嗯?
Huh?

797
00:55:43,182 --> 00:55:45,844
路西弗?
- Lucifer?

798
00:55:46,952 --> 00:55:49,147
驾!
Hiyah!

799
00:56:04,537 --> 00:56:06,027
我们等把它停下来.
We need to stop this thing.

800
00:56:06,106 --> 00:56:08,199
马上照办, 灰姑娘.
Right away, Cinderelly.

801
00:56:08,275 --> 00:56:10,106
OK, OK. 快点快点.
OK, OK. Chop-chop.

802
00:56:15,649 --> 00:56:18,140
格斯, 你能拿掉那个栓么?
Gus, can you reach the pin?

803
00:56:18,218 --> 00:56:19,708
吱吱.
Zug-zug.

804
00:56:47,480 --> 00:56:49,141
格斯!
Gus Gus!

805
00:56:52,686 --> 00:56:53,675
杰克!
Jaq!

806
00:56:58,358 --> 00:57:00,724
格斯, 抓住!
Gus, hold on!

807
00:57:05,066 --> 00:57:06,966
路西弗!
Lucifer!

808
00:57:07,034 --> 00:57:08,763
放开它!
Let him go!

809
00:57:11,405 --> 00:57:13,134
格斯!
Gus!

810
00:57:19,647 --> 00:57:22,081
嗯? 
Huh? 

811
00:57:23,050 --> 00:57:24,278
坏猫!
Bad kitty!

812
00:57:36,364 --> 00:57:37,695
吼吼!
Whoo-hoo!

813
00:57:42,636 --> 00:57:44,604
杰克! 格斯!
Jaq! Gus!

814
00:58:24,913 --> 00:58:26,244
现在我们应该怎么做?
Now what are we gonna do?

815
00:58:26,782 --> 00:58:29,114
我可不想错过我自己的婚礼.
Well, I'm not gonna miss my own wedding.

816
00:58:29,184 --> 00:58:30,742
呜呼!
Whoo-hoo!

817
00:58:48,336 --> 00:58:50,702
哦, 谢谢你, 亲爱的.
Oh, thank you, my dear.

818
00:58:50,772 --> 00:58:53,900
这就是他的母亲和我一直想要的.
This is all his mother and I
have ever wanted.

819
00:58:53,975 --> 00:58:58,605
知道我们的儿子找到自己的真爱.
To know that our son
has found his true love.

820
00:58:58,680 --> 00:59:03,708
所以, 你知道那种一摸到某人的手就有爱的感觉, 对吧?
So, you know it's love
when you touch someone's hand, right?

821
00:59:03,785 --> 00:59:05,582
至少, 我是这么听说的.
At least, that's what I've heard.

822
00:59:05,654 --> 00:59:09,351
当然!我一直都是这么想的.
 Why, yes!
That's what I've always thought.

823
00:59:39,522 --> 00:59:41,217
呼呼!
Whoo-hoo!

824
01:00:05,081 --> 01:00:07,572
亲爱的情人们...
Dearly beloved...

825
01:00:07,650 --> 01:00:10,619
一切都还好, 对吧, 陛下?
So far, so good, Your Majesty. Hmm?

826
01:00:10,686 --> 01:00:12,586
他的婚礼还没有结束.
He's not married yet.

827
01:00:12,655 --> 01:00:15,624
... 这个男人和这个女人
... to join together this man

828
01:00:15,691 --> 01:00:17,682
走到一起...
and this woman...

829
01:00:17,760 --> 01:00:20,251
我心里只有你, 灰姑娘.
My one and only Cinderella.

830
01:00:20,329 --> 01:00:22,456
...举行婚礼.
...in matrimony.

831
01:00:25,334 --> 01:00:28,462
我们就要成功了.
We're almost there.

832
01:00:31,440 --> 01:00:32,429
哇!
Whoa!

833
01:00:37,180 --> 01:00:38,272
停下!
Halt!

834
01:00:38,348 --> 01:00:42,512
...灰姑娘,
你愿意让这个男人成为你合法
...Cinderella,
take this man as your lawfully

835
01:00:42,586 --> 01:00:44,213
的丈夫么?
wedded husband?

836
01:00:44,288 --> 01:00:47,519
你不明白,
我必须进去.
You don't understand,
I must get inside.

837
01:00:47,591 --> 01:00:50,560
- 拜托.
- 说出来, 说, "我愿意".
- Please.
- Just say it. Say, "I do."

838
01:00:50,627 --> 01:00:52,492
我...
I...

839
01:00:54,097 --> 01:00:55,997
咄
Duh.

840
01:01:01,305 --> 01:01:02,363
我...
I...

841
01:01:04,775 --> 01:01:05,764
...不愿意.
...don't.

842
01:01:07,611 --> 01:01:08,669
阿纳斯塔西娅.
Anastasia.

843
01:01:09,346 --> 01:01:10,472
灰姑娘.
Cinderella.

844
01:01:13,917 --> 01:01:16,579
计划被你搅了.
Spoiled little ingrate.

845
01:01:16,653 --> 01:01:19,747
我给了你一切你想要的, 阿纳斯塔西娅!
I've given you everything
you ever wanted, Anastasia!

846
01:01:19,823 --> 01:01:22,485
但是我想要有人爱我, 是我.
But I want someone to love me, for me.

847
01:01:22,559 --> 01:01:26,051
警卫! 警卫! 抓住那个女人!
Guards! Guards! Seize that woman!

848
01:01:28,465 --> 01:01:29,762
'神奇大变身'!
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo!

849
01:01:47,919 --> 01:01:52,049
- 现在到你了!
- 把她变成癞蛤蟆, 妈妈.
- And now for you!
- Turn her into a toad, Mother.

850
01:01:52,123 --> 01:01:54,387
停手! 停止吧!
Stop! No more!

851
01:01:54,459 --> 01:01:57,019
这样更好.
- 灰姑娘!
- Even better.
- Cinderella!

852
01:01:57,095 --> 01:01:58,619
'神奇大变身'!
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo!

853
01:01:59,364 --> 01:02:00,558
不!
No!

854
01:02:04,168 --> 01:02:05,658
不!
No!

855
01:02:20,885 --> 01:02:25,618
这才是真的灰姑娘,
你的真爱.
This is the real Cinderella,
your true love.

856
01:02:38,136 --> 01:02:40,036
是你.
It's you.

857
01:02:57,122 --> 01:03:00,091
'神奇大变身'.
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo.

858
01:03:06,932 --> 01:03:09,765
我再也受不了这种刺激了.
I can't take much more of this.

859
01:03:12,538 --> 01:03:13,869
阿纳斯塔西娅.
Anastasia.

860
01:03:21,113 --> 01:03:22,876
谢谢你.
Thank you.

861
01:03:25,617 --> 01:03:27,949
'神奇大...
Bibbidi-bobbidi...

862
01:03:29,088 --> 01:03:30,715
变身'.
Boo.

863
01:03:33,058 --> 01:03:37,324
哦, 天哪! 浑身都僵硬了.
Oh, goodness! I certainly am stiff.

864
01:03:39,164 --> 01:03:40,722
陛下...
Your Majesty...

865
01:03:41,467 --> 01:03:43,401
...我不配拥有这个.
...I don't deserve this.

866
01:03:48,974 --> 01:03:52,637
每个人都有资格拥有真爱.
Everyone deserves true love.

867
01:03:57,416 --> 01:03:59,111
哦!
Oh!

868
01:04:01,820 --> 01:04:04,311
神奇大变身
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boo

869
01:04:07,761 --> 01:04:09,194
谢谢你.
Thank you.

870
01:04:12,632 --> 01:04:16,227
你们想不想回到你们以前的生活?
Would you like me
to return you to your former lives?

871
01:04:17,370 --> 01:04:18,701
以前的生活?
Former lives?

872
01:04:18,772 --> 01:04:21,536
是的, 你看, 你们两个...
Why, yes. You see, you two...

873
01:04:21,608 --> 01:04:23,940
你们已经...
Well, you were already...

874
01:04:24,978 --> 01:04:26,673
哦, 算了吧.
Oh, never mind.

875
01:04:26,746 --> 01:04:30,045
那么?
有没有人愿意嫁给我的儿子?
Well?
Does anyone want to marry my son?

876
01:04:33,520 --> 01:04:35,181
我愿意.
I do.

877
01:04:36,790 --> 01:04:39,759
我现在宣布你们成为合法夫妻.
I now pronounce you husband and wife.

878
01:05:14,260 --> 01:05:17,923
然后他们又...
And they lived
happily ever after...

879
01:05:17,998 --> 01:05:19,989
...永远生活在一起了.
...again.

