1
00:00:46,906 --> 00:00:56,332
星际之门

2
00:03:03,960 --> 00:03:07,839
北非沙漠 公元前8000年

3
00:04:25,614 --> 00:04:28,889
埃及 吉萨 1928年

4
00:04:34,915 --> 00:04:35,716
教授！
Professor!

5
00:04:38,276 --> 00:04:39,145
凯瑟琳！
Catherine!

6
00:04:41,213 --> 00:04:42,782
教授！你好！
Professor! I hope you salaam.

7
00:04:42,873 --> 00:04:43,493
你好。
Salaam.

8
00:04:44,891 --> 00:04:45,808
留神脚下。
Watch your step. 

9
00:04:46,562 --> 00:04:47,793
我们发现了一些奇妙的东西。
We found something beautiful.

10
00:04:48,191 --> 00:04:48,562
什么？
Ja?

11
00:04:49,019 --> 00:04:51,737
难以置信的东西，绝对惊喜！
I don't believe it. Big, big, big surprise!

12
00:04:51,902 --> 00:04:54,194
是吗？ 我想马上看到！
Yeah? I can hardly wait.

13
00:05:02,787 --> 00:05:04,210
过来！过来！
Over here! Over here!

14
00:05:10,169 --> 00:05:11,754
兰福得博士，你好！

15
00:05:11,963 --> 00:05:13,673
我们在这里发现了什么？

16
00:05:15,425 --> 00:05:16,593
一个石盖。

17
00:05:16,801 --> 00:05:18,428
非常的精美。

18
00:05:27,343 --> 00:05:28,081
凯瑟琳，来这儿。
Catherina, come.

19
00:06:12,482 --> 00:06:14,859
上帝，这是什么？

20
00:06:15,068 --> 00:06:17,028
但愿我知道。

21
00:06:20,949 --> 00:06:21,908
看那！

22
00:06:22,367 --> 00:06:24,327
下面埋了一些东西。

23
00:06:24,833 --> 00:06:26,312
发生了什么？
What's going on?

24
00:06:26,350 --> 00:06:27,983
等等。嘿！等等。
Wait. Hey! Wait a second.

25
00:06:28,018 --> 00:06:29,080
凯瑟琳，在这等着。
Catherine, stay here.

26
00:06:48,184 --> 00:06:50,186
看上去像某种化石。

27
00:07:00,780 --> 00:07:03,449
现代

28
00:07:12,709 --> 00:07:15,753
上面记满了各种符号，
I mean, there are symbols painted everywhere...

29
00:07:15,837 --> 00:07:18,203
包括墓主的名字和地位以及祭品清单。
names, titles of owners, lists of offerings.

30
00:07:18,811 --> 00:07:21,254
而当时的其他主要建筑上，
Every other major architectural structure at the time

31
00:07:21,254 --> 00:07:23,417
则只有简单的象形文字。
was covered with detailed hieroglyphics.

32
00:07:23,636 --> 00:07:26,619
学术界要何时才能接受这个事实，
When is the academic community gonna accept the fact

33
00:07:26,890 --> 00:07:30,895
就是吉萨大金字塔绝非由第四王朝的法老所建立？
the pharaohs of the fourth dynasty did not build the Great Pyramid? 

34
00:07:32,020 --> 00:07:32,630
看，看，
Look. Look.

35
00:07:33,063 --> 00:07:36,652
纵观整个金字塔内部，他们在能建立起如此了不起建筑的同时，
Inside the pyramid, the most incredible structure ever erected

36
00:07:37,108 --> 00:07:39,447
却没有任何关于这奇迹般的建筑是如何建造的记载。
there are no writings whatsoever.

37
00:07:39,986 --> 00:07:42,037
杰克逊教授：你忽略了
Dr. Jackson. You've left out the fact

38
00:07:42,175 --> 00:07:45,366
维斯上校在金字塔内部发现的铭文…
that Colonel Vyse discovered quarrymen's...

39
00:07:45,366 --> 00:07:45,575
没错。
Right.

40
00:07:45,575 --> 00:07:50,181
上面记有法老胡夫的名字。
inscriptions of Khufu's name within the pyramid.

41
00:07:50,952 --> 00:07:52,175
他的发现是个骗局。
His discovery was a fraud.

42
00:07:52,449 --> 00:07:53,966
希望你能提出证据。
Well, I hope you can prove it.

43
00:07:54,947 --> 00:07:56,862
问题就是谁建立了大金字塔？
Well, who do you think built the pyramids?

44
00:08:01,807 --> 00:08:03,350
我也不知道谁建造了金字塔。
I don't have any idea who built them.

45
00:08:04,177 --> 00:08:06,923
亚特兰蒂人，还是玛雅人？
Men from Atlantis? Or Martians perhaps?

46
00:08:08,556 --> 00:08:11,525
问题的关键不在于谁建造了它们，而是它们是在何时被建造的。
The point is not who built them, the point is when they were built.

47
00:08:11,708 --> 00:08:14,853
我们都知道新的地质证据表明，
I mean, we all know new geological evidence

48
00:08:14,938 --> 00:08:17,189
狮身人面像的建造年代要远早于金字塔。
dates the Sphinx back to a much earlier period.

49
00:08:17,273 --> 00:08:21,401
我觉得我们有必要对过往所接受的历史重新研究，
And knowing this, I think we have to begin to re-evaluate

50
00:08:21,486 --> 00:08:24,183
我们应该客观地接受…
everything we've come to accept about...

51
00:08:25,782 --> 00:08:29,493
我能给大家展示一套使用于第一王朝或者以后的两个王朝的
I mean, I've been able to show a fully developed writing system

52
00:08:30,007 --> 00:08:32,431
成熟的古文字系统。
appeared in the first two dynasties.

53
00:08:33,306 --> 00:08:33,871
你们知道，那是
You know, which

54
00:08:35,083 --> 00:08:38,481
由更早的原型文字发展而来。
Almost as if it was based on an even earlier prototype.

55
00:08:40,771 --> 00:08:42,970
有给到会人员准备的午餐么？
Is there a lunch or something that everybody...

56
00:08:53,184 --> 00:08:53,981
出租车！
Taxi!

57
00:08:58,549 --> 00:08:59,301
杰克逊博士。
Dr. Jackson.

58
00:08:59,813 --> 00:09:00,960
什么事？
What? Yes?

59
00:09:01,526 --> 00:09:02,756
有人想和你谈谈。
Someone wants to speak with you.

60
00:09:03,965 --> 00:09:06,933
空军的人？这是怎么回事？
Air force? What's this? What is this?

61
00:09:07,073 --> 00:09:08,858
你能否上车再谈？
Could you step over to the car, please?

62
00:09:12,036 --> 00:09:12,531
长官？
Sir?

63
00:09:16,974 --> 00:09:17,864
要带我去哪里？
We going somewhere?

64
00:09:18,037 --> 00:09:18,944
不用担心。
You're gonna be fine.

65
00:09:19,355 --> 00:09:20,399
这些我们会保管的。
We'll take care of these.

66
00:09:27,093 --> 00:09:29,155
杰克逊，他们是你的父母？
Jackson. Those your parents?

67
00:09:33,743 --> 00:09:34,482
是养父母。
Foster parents.

68
00:09:37,437 --> 00:09:38,641
这是怎么回事？
What is this all about?

69
00:09:39,105 --> 00:09:39,987
一个工作。
A job.

70
00:09:41,111 --> 00:09:42,399
什么工作？
What kind of a job?

71
00:09:42,819 --> 00:09:46,575
翻译，古埃及象形文字。
Translation. Ancient Egyptian hieroglyphs.

72
00:09:50,366 --> 00:09:51,117
有兴趣吗？
Interested?

73
00:09:53,912 --> 00:09:54,619
我现在应该走了。
I'm gonna go now.

74
00:09:55,685 --> 00:09:56,328
去哪里？
Go where?

75
00:09:57,676 --> 00:09:59,773
你刚刚被赶出来，
I mean, you've just been evicted from your apartment.

76
00:10:00,283 --> 00:10:01,525
信用也已经破产，
Your grants have run out.

77
00:10:02,331 --> 00:10:04,897
你所有的财产就剩那两个行李箱了。
Everything you own are in those two bags.

78
00:10:06,823 --> 00:10:08,565
你需要证明你的理论是正确的。
You want to prove that your theories are right.

79
00:10:11,095 --> 00:10:12,031
机会就摆在你面前。
This is your chance.

80
00:10:16,100 --> 00:10:16,990
这是什么？
What's this?

81
00:10:17,352 --> 00:10:18,375
旅行计划。
Travel plans.

82
00:10:21,314 --> 00:10:21,821
先生？
Sir?

83
00:10:55,170 --> 00:10:55,777
奥尼尔太太？
Mrs. O'Neil?

84
00:10:58,226 --> 00:10:58,878
请进吧。
Come on in.

85
00:11:06,276 --> 00:11:07,575
奥尼尔太太，你丈夫在家吗？
Mrs. O'Neil, is your husband at home?

86
00:11:08,785 --> 00:11:09,325
是的。
Yes.

87
00:11:10,805 --> 00:11:12,409
能和他说几句话吗？
Do you think we might be able to speak with him?

88
00:11:14,659 --> 00:11:15,404
请便。
You can try.

89
00:11:49,527 --> 00:11:52,271
打扰了，奥尼尔上校。我们是威斯特将军派来的。
Excuse me, Colonel O'Neil. We're from General West's office.

90
00:11:58,161 --> 00:11:58,659
长官？
Sir?

91
00:12:01,331 --> 00:12:03,979
我们来此是通知您已经被复职了。
We're here to inform you that you've been reactivated.

92
00:12:10,265 --> 00:12:11,067
那家伙看起来很失落。
Guy's a mess.

93
00:12:15,399 --> 00:12:16,385
他怎么会变成这样的？
How did he get like that?

94
00:12:17,258 --> 00:12:18,116
他儿子死了，
His kid died.

95
00:12:19,182 --> 00:12:20,232
玩手枪意外走火。
Accidentally shot himself.

96
00:12:21,059 --> 00:12:21,561
天哪。
Jesus.

97
00:12:35,949 --> 00:12:40,787
科罗拉多州 克里克山 军事基地

98
00:12:45,641 --> 00:12:46,223
身份已验证
Cleared.

99
00:12:53,859 --> 00:12:54,409
感冒了？
Cold?

100
00:12:55,093 --> 00:12:55,819
是过敏，
Allergies.

101
00:12:58,126 --> 00:12:59,561
每次旅行都会这样。
Always happens when I travel.

102
00:13:02,375 --> 00:13:03,028
你先请。
There you go.

103
00:13:05,228 --> 00:13:06,234
- 嗨。 - 嗨。
-Hi. -Hi.

104
00:13:06,562 --> 00:13:07,298
杰克逊博士么？
Dr. Jackson? 

105
00:13:07,522 --> 00:13:07,956
你好。
Hello.

106
00:13:07,956 --> 00:13:08,600
我是加里·梅耶斯博士。
Dr. Gary Meyers.

107
00:13:08,600 --> 00:13:09,310
- 你好吗？ - 你好。
- How Are You? - Hello.

108
00:13:09,816 --> 00:13:10,938
这是什么地方？
What is this place?

109
00:13:11,401 --> 00:13:12,400
改造后的核弹发射井。
Nuclear missile silo.

110
00:13:12,485 --> 00:13:15,154
不过放心好了，没有辐射。
Now don't worry. It's been completely converted. Barbara Shore.

111
00:13:15,154 --> 00:13:15,533
你好。
Hello.

112
00:13:15,533 --> 00:13:15,864
你好。
Hi.

113
00:13:35,383 --> 00:13:36,210
杰克逊，
Okay, Jackson.

114
00:13:37,038 --> 00:13:38,277
- 欢迎来这里。 - 你好。
- Welcome to the well. - Hello.

115
00:13:39,398 --> 00:13:39,777
这是…
This is...

116
00:13:41,636 --> 00:13:42,399
你们是在哪里找到这个的？
Where did you find this?

117
00:13:43,437 --> 00:13:45,822
1928年在吉萨高原。
Giza Plateau, 1928.

118
00:13:46,978 --> 00:13:48,468
我未见过这样的符号。
I've never seen anything like this.

119
00:13:49,605 --> 00:13:52,266
你当然没见过，没人见过。
Of course you haven't. No one has.

120
00:13:52,374 --> 00:13:54,432
这些图形具有两种结构，
Now, there's two lines of hieroglyphs.

121
00:13:54,670 --> 00:13:56,640
内部的轨迹是古典的符号，
The inner track has the classic figures, 

122
00:13:56,863 --> 00:13:59,068
但外观像个汇聚中心的圆形徽章，
but the outer track is like the cartouche in the centre.

123
00:14:00,074 --> 00:14:02,345
这种构字方式不同于任何已知象形文字。
It's got writing unlike we've ever found before.

124
00:14:03,014 --> 00:14:04,090
那不是象形文字。
Those aren't hieroglyphics.

125
00:14:04,398 --> 00:14:07,113
也许是手写变体字或是楔形文字。
Might be Some form of hieratic or maybe cuneiform.

126
00:14:11,214 --> 00:14:13,832
内部的符号翻译完全错了，
Well, the translation of the inner track is wrong.

127
00:14:14,088 --> 00:14:15,191
必须变通一下。
Must have used budge.

128
00:14:15,256 --> 00:14:16,722
为什么有人会这样翻译。
I don't know why they keep reprinting his books.

129
00:14:17,592 --> 00:14:22,050
抱歉，这是我们利用所有已知材料翻译的。
Excuse me. What are you doing? We've used every known technique.

130
00:14:22,184 --> 00:14:23,946
这个词很有意思——“Gebeh”？
That's a curious word to use, Eh? "Gebeh."

131
00:14:24,299 --> 00:14:24,745
是的。
Yeah.

132
00:14:25,350 --> 00:14:26,912
然后是个副词，“sedjem-en-ef”。
Then an adverbial... "sedjem-en-ef."

133
00:14:26,912 --> 00:14:30,812
那就是“封印”和“埋藏”。
Now "Sealed And Buried."

134
00:14:31,082 --> 00:14:33,815
对不起！你在做什么？
Excuse Me! What are you doing?

135
00:14:33,900 --> 00:14:34,515
这个词不是“棺材”，
It's not "coffin."

136
00:14:37,236 --> 00:14:37,990
是“直到永远”。
"For All Time."

137
00:14:41,325 --> 00:14:42,660
这是哪个混蛋翻译的？
Who the hell translated this?

138
00:14:45,203 --> 00:14:46,266
呃，是我。
I did.

139
00:14:46,537 --> 00:14:49,998
那么这应该翻译为：“永恒，至高无上之太阳神
Well, this should Read, "A million years into the sky is Ra, sun god...

140
00:14:50,082 --> 00:14:51,725
永远将此封印和埋藏。”
sealed and buried for all Time."

141
00:14:52,293 --> 00:14:53,383
这句不是“通往天堂的门”，
It's not "door to heaven."

142
00:14:54,518 --> 00:14:55,393
而是
It's...

143
00:15:01,844 --> 00:15:02,410
“星际之门”
"Stargate."

144
00:15:05,765 --> 00:15:09,456
好了，军方怎么会对这些有五千年历史的埃及石碑感兴趣？
Well, so why is the milItary so interested in 5,000-year-old Egyptian tablets?

145
00:15:09,880 --> 00:15:11,572
给我的报告书中说这已有万年以上历史。
My report says 10,000.

146
00:15:12,770 --> 00:15:13,751
下午好，上校。
Afternoon, Colonel.

147
00:15:20,942 --> 00:15:21,619
请问阁下是？
Do I know you?

148
00:15:22,144 --> 00:15:24,491
我是威斯特将军派来的杰克·奥尼尔上校，
I'm Colonel Jack O'Neil from General West's office.

149
00:15:24,784 --> 00:15:26,203
我将负责管理这里的研究工作。
I'll be taking over from now on.

150
00:15:28,329 --> 00:15:30,101
说这有万年历史简直是滑天下之大稽，
This figure 10,000 is ludicrous. 

151
00:15:30,101 --> 00:15:31,877
那时候埃及文明甚至还不存在。
I mean, Egyptian culture didn't even exist.

152
00:15:31,877 --> 00:15:35,874
我们也知道，可放射碳探测结果就是如此。
We know, but the sonic and radiocarbon tests are conclusive.

153
00:15:36,170 --> 00:15:38,071
那么，这个石盖下面找到了坟墓？
Well, THese are Cover Stones. Was there a tomb underneath?

154
00:15:38,222 --> 00:15:42,074
没有，但我们找到更为有趣的东西。
No, No. But we found something a lot more interesting.

155
00:15:42,551 --> 00:15:45,945
抱歉，这信息被列为机密了。
Excuse me. This information has become classified.

156
00:15:48,474 --> 00:15:51,638
由现在起，任何信息都不能泄露给普通公众，
From now on, no information is to be passed on to non-military personnel...

157
00:15:51,638 --> 00:15:53,120
除非经过我的允许。
without my express permission.

158
00:15:57,232 --> 00:15:58,488
凯瑟琳，这是怎么了？
CatHerine, What's going on here?

159
00:15:59,400 --> 00:16:00,182
我也不知道。
I'm not sure.

160
00:16:04,282 --> 00:16:07,340
奥尼尔上校，我想你还未给我一个解释。
Colonel O'Neil. I think you owe me an explanation.

161
00:16:08,786 --> 00:16:11,550
这儿本该由我全权负责。
I was told I had complete autonomy.

162
00:16:12,052 --> 00:16:13,019
计划更改了。
Plans change.

163
00:16:14,417 --> 00:16:17,587
你为何被派来这里？他们派你参与计划有何目的？
Why are you here? Why did they bring you on this project?

164
00:16:21,132 --> 00:16:22,819
我来此并非阻挠研究。
I'm here in case you succeed.

165
00:16:29,849 --> 00:16:33,110
已经完全检索楔形字及其他史前象形文字，
Completed search of cuneiform and other predynastic hieroglyphics.

166
00:16:30,516 --> 00:16:32,727
两周后

167
00:16:33,110 --> 00:16:34,192
并未找到相近字形。
No matches whatsoever.

168
00:16:34,776 --> 00:16:38,106
我已感到疲惫不堪，尤其是校对这些资料和符号。
I've exhausted all reference material in comparing the symbols in the cartouche.

169
00:16:38,190 --> 00:16:41,323
纵览所有已知史前资料
Against all known writing samples from the period, pre and post.

170
00:16:42,570 --> 00:16:43,971
也找不到相近的。
Still no similarities.

171
00:16:45,231 --> 00:16:46,563
而且至今还未领到薪水
I'm never gonna get paid.

172
00:17:22,401 --> 00:17:23,162
能借我看看吗？
Can I borrow this?

173
00:17:47,025 --> 00:17:47,696
猎户座。
Orion.

174
00:18:26,763 --> 00:18:27,150
请坐这儿。
Right here.

175
00:18:27,612 --> 00:18:29,914
杰克逊，这位是威斯特将军。
Jackson. I'd like you to meet General West.

176
00:18:30,469 --> 00:18:32,538
哦，你好将军。
Hello. Right, General. Right.

177
00:18:33,305 --> 00:18:35,246
好了。
Hi. Okay.

178
00:18:35,891 --> 00:18:40,357
这么说，你花了14天的时间就破解了他们研究两年都毫无进展的迷题？
So you think you've solved in 14 days what they couldn't solve in two years?

179
00:18:41,814 --> 00:18:42,564
两年？
Two years?

180
00:18:47,194 --> 00:18:47,839
别耽搁时间了。
Anytime.

181
00:18:51,825 --> 00:18:53,635
先请大家过目些东西。
I have some stuff to look at.

182
00:18:54,743 --> 00:18:56,114
大家互相传阅一下。
If you just pass them down.

183
00:18:58,106 --> 00:18:59,897
你们可能需要共享一下，因为…
You'll have to share them because...

184
00:19:00,828 --> 00:19:02,863
抱歉，我带的不够多。
I'm sorry, I don't have enough of those.

185
00:19:02,863 --> 00:19:04,727
不过怎么说，好了。
But, Anyway... Okay. All right.

186
00:19:04,727 --> 00:19:07,228
我们现在看到的石盖上的图案。
We're obviously looking at a picture of the cover stones.

187
00:19:07,506 --> 00:19:08,620
最外面一圈的符号，
Now, on the outer track...

188
00:19:09,675 --> 00:19:13,595
大家都认为那是文字，
These figures that you would believe to be words to be translated...

189
00:19:13,679 --> 00:19:15,647
可事实上，
Well, in fact...

190
00:19:21,326 --> 00:19:25,134
抱歉，事实上…那是份星座坐标图。
Sorry about that... were, in fact, star constellations.

191
00:19:27,750 --> 00:19:30,612
把星座按照一定顺序组成一幅地图，
Now, these constellations were placed in a unique order...

192
00:19:30,696 --> 00:19:32,209
来表明特定场所的地址。
forming a map or an address of sorts.

193
00:19:32,781 --> 00:19:37,010
七个点描述了通往一个目的地的路线，
Seven points to outline a course to a position, and...

194
00:19:39,902 --> 00:19:45,124
在三维空间内，
To find a destination within any three-dimensional space...

195
00:19:45,689 --> 00:19:49,218
我们需要六个点
We need six points...

196
00:19:50,674 --> 00:19:54,675
来确定一精确的位置。
to determine the exact location.

197
00:19:55,265 --> 00:19:57,470
可你刚才是说七个点。
You said you needed seven points.

198
00:19:57,973 --> 00:19:59,908
不，六个点是确定目的地。
Well, no... six for the destination.

199
00:20:00,362 --> 00:20:02,316
不过画成路线图，你还需要
But to chart a course, you need...

200
00:20:04,759 --> 00:20:05,524
一个起点。
a point of origin.

201
00:20:06,565 --> 00:20:09,482
但我们在圈中只找到六点位置。
Except there's only six symbols in the cartouche.

202
00:20:10,152 --> 00:20:13,756
第七点并不在那儿，正在石碑的下方，
The seventh actually isn't inside the cartouche. It's just below it, here...

203
00:20:13,756 --> 00:20:17,259
由一个金字塔
designated by a little pyramid...

204
00:20:17,259 --> 00:20:20,412
和两个
with... two...

205
00:20:21,997 --> 00:20:22,572
有趣的、
funny...

206
00:20:24,250 --> 00:20:25,405
对称的小人所标明，
neat little guys...

207
00:20:25,793 --> 00:20:29,558
以及一条从顶端引出来的直线。
And funny little line coming out of the top.

208
00:20:33,771 --> 00:20:34,317
总之就是…
Anyway...

209
00:20:36,025 --> 00:20:37,209
他成功了。
Well, he did it.

210
00:20:38,430 --> 00:20:41,031
没有！装置上并没有那个符号。
No. That symbol isn't anywhere on the device.

211
00:20:42,285 --> 00:20:42,870
什么装置？
What device?

212
00:20:51,194 --> 00:20:51,985
带他去看。
Show him.

213
00:20:52,424 --> 00:20:53,061
是，长官。
Yes, Sir.

214
00:21:36,927 --> 00:21:37,578
那是什么？
What is that?

215
00:21:40,071 --> 00:21:41,548
就是你的“星际之门”。
It's your Stargate.

216
00:21:45,885 --> 00:21:46,585
跟我来，杰克逊。
Come, Jackson.

217
00:21:48,342 --> 00:21:51,081
技术人员请向指挥中心汇报。
Technical personnel, report to command centre.

218
00:21:55,790 --> 00:21:56,587
监视装置准备！
Monitors up!

219
00:21:57,384 --> 00:21:58,301
监视装置准备就绪！
Monitors are up.

220
00:21:58,385 --> 00:22:00,915
米奇，将细节放大至中央监视装置。
Mitch, you wanna bring up the details on the centre monitor, please.

221
00:22:01,055 --> 00:22:01,388
是。
Yeah.

222
00:22:03,766 --> 00:22:05,933
已完成。
I've got details on.

223
00:22:25,510 --> 00:22:27,080
停一下，等等。
Hold it. Wait.

224
00:22:29,166 --> 00:22:32,584
你有没有…这个，抱歉。
Do you have a... Here. Sorry.

225
00:22:33,523 --> 00:22:34,565
喂，不要乱画！
Hey, Hey, don't...

226
00:22:35,798 --> 00:22:38,177
两个小人各立一边，
Two figures on either side...

227
00:22:39,635 --> 00:22:43,304
向着金字塔祈祷，正上方是太阳。
Praying beside a pyramid with the sun directly above it.

228
00:22:44,733 --> 00:22:47,501
他是正确的,在我们面前的是完整的坐标。
He's right. It was in front of us the whole time.

229
00:22:49,006 --> 00:22:53,591
威斯特将军，杰克逊找到了第七个符号。
General West. Jackson has identified the seventh symbol.

230
00:22:53,732 --> 00:22:54,384
继续实验。
Go ahead.

231
00:22:54,942 --> 00:22:57,205
将第七符号记录入电脑。
Programming seventh symbol into computer.

232
00:22:58,278 --> 00:23:02,534
坐标一准备，坐标一锁定。
Chevron one is holding. Chevron one is locked in place.

233
00:23:03,075 --> 00:23:06,192
能量输出百分之二十三。
Power output at 23%.

234
00:23:14,878 --> 00:23:16,528
坐标二准备。
Chevron two is holding.

235
00:23:16,839 --> 00:23:17,631
运行中。
Engage.

236
00:23:17,840 --> 00:23:19,942
坐标二锁定位置
Chevron two is locked in place.

237
00:23:20,677 --> 00:23:22,109
能量百分之三十五。
We're at 35%.

238
00:23:22,813 --> 00:23:25,850
实验室进入红色警告状态。非技术人员疏散。
All right, we got a condition red at the gate. Evacuate all personnel.

239
00:23:27,766 --> 00:23:30,206
无关人员退出，封锁大门。
Clear the bay. Clear. Let's go.

240
00:23:32,415 --> 00:23:33,744
这就是石盖下面的东西？
It was under the cover stones?

241
00:23:34,006 --> 00:23:37,677
是的，是我父亲在1928年找到的。
Yes. My father found it. 1928.

242
00:23:38,065 --> 00:23:41,320
由一种和地球上所发现矿物不同的矿物质构成
Made out of a mineral unlike any found on earth.

243
00:23:42,322 --> 00:23:43,734
坐标五准备就绪。
Chevron five locked in place.

244
00:23:44,880 --> 00:23:46,617
百分之七十九。
Seventy-nine percent.

245
00:23:48,704 --> 00:23:50,289
坐标六准备就绪。
Chevron six is holding.

246
00:23:52,166 --> 00:23:53,934
坐标六锁定。
Chevron six is locked in place.

247
00:23:54,042 --> 00:23:57,404
这会让我们终生难忘。
This is as far as we have ever been able to get.

248
00:24:09,235 --> 00:24:11,279
- 坐标七无法锁定。 - 系统失去控制！
- Chevron seven. - Override manually.

249
00:24:13,645 --> 00:24:15,887
坐标七锁定。
Chevron seven is locked in place.

250
00:24:38,879 --> 00:24:39,981
送入探测器。
Send in the probe.

251
00:24:42,090 --> 00:24:42,807
快！快！
Let's Go. Let's Go.

252
00:24:47,304 --> 00:24:48,569
我们到了。检查。
We're here. check.

253
00:24:50,057 --> 00:24:50,476
是，长官？
Yes, sir.

254
00:24:51,197 --> 00:24:53,321
记录所有来自星门内的信息。
Record all information from the Stargate.

255
00:25:01,568 --> 00:25:03,130
研究室清场。
Clear inner silo for approach.

256
00:25:03,571 --> 00:25:04,660
所有人员退出！
Clear inner silo.

257
00:25:47,688 --> 00:25:48,682
自动导航系统启动。
It's guiding itself.

258
00:25:49,625 --> 00:25:50,460
你们能相信么？
Can you believe that?

259
00:26:09,225 --> 00:26:14,319
电波被锁定在了凯利姆星系的某个位置。
The beam has locked itself onto a point somewhere in the Kaliam galaxy.

260
00:26:15,153 --> 00:26:17,834
肯定是搞错了，也许是在月亮或是其他大型行星上。
It has mass. It could be a moon or a large asteroid.

261
00:26:18,507 --> 00:26:19,475
我们在地图上的哪里？
Where are we on that map?

262
00:26:20,096 --> 00:26:20,738
那个蓝点。
The blue dot.

263
00:26:30,221 --> 00:26:31,163
没错，杰克逊，
That's right, Jackson.

264
00:26:32,253 --> 00:26:35,663
它在已知宇宙的另一边。
It's on the other side of the known universe.

265
00:26:38,498 --> 00:26:39,707
失去讯号。
We're losing the signal.

266
00:26:45,000 --> 00:26:47,180
这是探测器发回的讯息。
This is the information the probe sent back to us.

267
00:26:49,694 --> 00:26:51,069
固定画面，放大。
Freeze and enhance.

268
00:26:52,262 --> 00:26:54,560
我们可以清楚看到门的另一边。
You can clearly see the gate on the other side.

269
00:26:55,223 --> 00:26:58,244
那两扇门互相联系形成一个不同世界间的通道。
Both gates must have functioned as a doorway between our worlds.

270
00:26:58,764 --> 00:27:01,134
这些数据表明空气条件与这里相符，
These readings tell us it's an atmospheric match.

271
00:27:03,982 --> 00:27:08,694
拥有近似气压、温度，还有氧气。
Barometric pressure, temperature and, most importantly, oxygen.

272
00:27:10,989 --> 00:27:15,308
但这些符号有点不同，和我们这端的门并不符合。
These markings are different. They don't match the symbols on our gate.

273
00:27:15,491 --> 00:27:16,999
也许我们该中止这个计划了。
That's why we may have to abort.

274
00:27:19,451 --> 00:27:22,014
若不进行探查，这个计划就不会有进展。
This project is for naught without a reconnaissance mission.

275
00:27:23,726 --> 00:27:27,074
一旦我们到达另一头，就可以破解门上的密语，
Once on the other side, You would have to decipher the markings on their gate...

276
00:27:27,714 --> 00:27:30,778
并依此把队伍带回来。
And, in essence, dial home in order to bring the team back.

277
00:27:31,202 --> 00:27:33,872
我真不知道我们还能再做些什么。
Based on this new information, I don't see how we can do that.

278
00:27:34,843 --> 00:27:35,754
我可以去。
Well, I could do that.

279
00:27:43,284 --> 00:27:44,140
你确定？
Are you sure?

280
00:27:51,142 --> 00:27:51,835
绝对肯定。
Positive.

281
00:27:59,579 --> 00:28:00,790
这家伙的脑子进水了。
He's full of shit.

282
00:28:03,621 --> 00:28:04,514
现在你是我们的成员了。
You're on the team.

283
00:28:49,552 --> 00:28:52,007
你必须明白，这事非常复杂。
You understand this complicates things.

284
00:28:56,249 --> 00:28:57,564
这就是为什么需要你的原因。
That's why I wanted you, Jack.

285
00:28:59,848 --> 00:29:02,670
我们打开了一扇通往未知世界的门。
We've opened a doorway to a world we know nothing about.

286
00:29:14,321 --> 00:29:14,864
杰克逊。
Jackson.

287
00:29:17,379 --> 00:29:18,444
哦，你好。
Hello. Hi.

288
00:29:20,160 --> 00:29:21,614
我有东西要给你。
I have something for you.

289
00:29:22,106 --> 00:29:22,804
不，我不能…
No, I...

290
00:29:23,587 --> 00:29:24,184
收下！
Yes.

291
00:29:26,416 --> 00:29:29,204
这是我小时候在星门附近找到的，
I found it with Stargate when I was a child.

292
00:29:29,753 --> 00:29:30,961
曾经带给我好运。
It has brought me luck.

293
00:29:36,093 --> 00:29:37,553
你可以回来的时候再还我。
You can bring It back to me.

294
00:29:54,069 --> 00:29:58,100
使用备用系统，储备电源开启。
Backup storage. Reserve power on.

295
00:29:58,198 --> 00:29:59,111
安全, 清场
Let's do it.

296
00:29:59,367 --> 00:29:59,886
我们走。
Let's get it down.

297
00:30:01,015 --> 00:30:03,140
监视设备启动…
Surveillance and monitoring...

298
00:30:04,120 --> 00:30:05,016
倒计时！
Ten-hut!

299
00:30:12,504 --> 00:30:15,084
要交代什么的趁现在说。
If anybody has anything to say, now's the time to say it.

300
00:30:23,431 --> 00:30:24,796
矢量追踪仪设置完成。
Vector tracking set.

301
00:32:01,436 --> 00:32:04,174
进行分子解构。
Molecular deconstruction in progress.

302
00:33:20,118 --> 00:33:22,144
杰克逊，没事了，已经到了。
Jackson. It's all right. It's over.

303
00:33:22,694 --> 00:33:23,364
照看他一下。
Stay whth him.

304
00:33:24,079 --> 00:33:25,405
杰克逊，快起来吧。
Jackson. Just listen to me. Keep moving.

305
00:33:26,082 --> 00:33:27,066
走吧。
It wears off in a minute.

306
00:33:29,013 --> 00:33:29,770
好家伙。
What a rush.

307
00:33:34,237 --> 00:33:34,842
全体整装，准备出发。
Prepare to move out.

308
00:33:54,559 --> 00:33:55,389
分三组行动。
Three teams. Let's Go.

309
00:33:56,020 --> 00:33:56,941
白队，出发。
White team, go.

310
00:34:13,703 --> 00:34:14,964
准备好了吗？
Ready? Okay.

311
00:34:28,551 --> 00:34:29,753
二队行动。
Team two, move up.

312
00:34:41,314 --> 00:34:42,329
确认安全。
Clear. No contact.

313
00:34:56,121 --> 00:34:57,886
氧气比率稳定。
O2 ratio stable.

314
00:34:58,249 --> 00:34:59,881
外面的情况相同。
Conditions are similar to inside.

315
00:35:00,270 --> 00:35:01,746
去外面瞧瞧。
I'm gonna take a look around.

316
00:35:02,418 --> 00:35:03,784
卡瓦斯基，费瑞提。
Kawalsky. Feretti.

317
00:35:45,295 --> 00:35:46,623
到达位置。
Move up there. Good.

318
00:36:18,328 --> 00:36:19,064
我明白了。
I knew it.

319
00:36:23,124 --> 00:36:24,848
1-3-3-2

320
00:36:28,200 --> 00:36:28,822
报告。
Report.

321
00:36:28,991 --> 00:36:31,900
我们周围四分之一英里范围几乎全是相同的地形。
A Quarter-mile perimeter survey is just about complete, sir.

322
00:36:37,680 --> 00:36:39,422
把这个收起来, 所有人退回去。
Wrap this up. Get everybody Back inside.

323
00:36:39,826 --> 00:36:41,891
一小时后准备通过星门返回。
I want all you people back through the Stargate within the hour.

324
00:36:43,921 --> 00:36:45,096
你跟我们一起回去吧，上校？
You're coming with us, aren't you, Colonel?

325
00:36:47,649 --> 00:36:48,276
长官？
Sir?

326
00:36:48,473 --> 00:36:48,976
杰克逊，
Jackson.

327
00:36:49,822 --> 00:36:50,984
准备启动星际之门。
Start working on the Stargate.

328
00:36:51,865 --> 00:36:52,824
那都是干什么的？
What's that all about?

329
00:36:53,768 --> 00:36:54,612
我也不知道，费瑞提。
I don't know, Feretti.

330
00:36:54,822 --> 00:36:55,990
我需要一些时间。
I'm gonna need more time.

331
00:36:56,991 --> 00:36:59,085
附近应该还有其他建筑物，
I mean, there's bound to be more structures here...

332
00:36:59,202 --> 00:37:01,508
或是其他文明的遗迹。
or some other traces of civilization.

333
00:37:02,183 --> 00:37:04,838
这趟不急着调查，只需返回汇报情况就可。
Not this trip. Just get back in there and re-establish contact.

334
00:37:05,833 --> 00:37:08,372
没有这么简单。这里就像是吉萨金字塔的复制品，
Well, it's not that easy. This is a replica of the Great Pyramid of Giza.

335
00:37:09,045 --> 00:37:12,547
我们不打算发现一些象形文字或者雕刻吗？
We're not gonna find any hieroglyphic inscriptions or carved relief.

336
00:37:12,632 --> 00:37:15,300
最好还是去周围瞧瞧。
I mean, we really need to look around more.

337
00:37:15,385 --> 00:37:19,056
你来这儿的任务是重新启动星门，行还是不行?
Your job here is to realign the Stargate. Can you do that or not?

338
00:37:22,141 --> 00:37:22,700
我不能。
I can't.

339
00:37:26,646 --> 00:37:28,128
是你不能，还是不愿意？
You can't or you won't?

340
00:37:28,648 --> 00:37:32,178
我能破解星门上的密语，但启动还需要重新组序。
I can decipher the symbols on the Stargate, but I need an order of alignment.

341
00:37:33,038 --> 00:37:35,258
我只是需要找到一些和地球上的石盖一样的东西，
Now, those Coordinates were marked on tablets back on Earth...

342
00:37:35,321 --> 00:37:36,594
肯定就在这里附近。
And there must be something like that here.

343
00:37:37,198 --> 00:37:39,866
找的到就万事大吉。
And I just need to find it.

344
00:37:42,704 --> 00:37:45,122
找？你这是什么意思？
Find it? What do you mean, find it?

345
00:37:45,206 --> 00:37:46,866
你没有说过还有这么回事。
You didn't say anything about finding anything.

346
00:37:47,333 --> 00:37:49,517
好吧，我只是假定它一定会在这里。
Well, I assumed the tablets would be here. I mean, right here.

347
00:37:50,169 --> 00:37:50,900
你假定？
You assumed?

348
00:37:51,544 --> 00:37:53,258
你这个说谎的混蛋！
You're a lying son of a bitch!

349
00:37:53,258 --> 00:37:55,596
你从就没说过还要寻找东西！
You didn't say a word about finding anything!

350
00:37:56,600 --> 00:37:57,164
卡瓦斯基，
Kawalsky.

351
00:37:59,304 --> 00:38:02,356
带兄弟们就地扎营，整理补给品。
Set up a camp down here. Organize our supplies.

352
00:38:03,308 --> 00:38:03,517
长官？
Sir?

353
00:38:03,517 --> 00:38:04,496
你已经听到命令了。
You've got your orders.

354
00:38:17,999 --> 00:38:19,866
真不敢相信，我们被困在这里了。
You know, I can't believe we're stuck here.

355
00:38:20,241 --> 00:38:21,777
不要说这种不吉利的话，费瑞提。
Don't be such a doomsayer, Feretti.

356
00:38:22,101 --> 00:38:23,012
来休息一下。
Yeah, give it a rest.

357
00:38:23,286 --> 00:38:24,572
请。
Yes, Please.

358
00:38:25,226 --> 00:38:28,206
如果我们没有迅速返回的话，他们就会从另一端把门打开。
If we're not back soon, they'll just turn on the gate from the other side.

359
00:38:28,291 --> 00:38:30,634
不是那么回事，
Oh, No. It doesn't work that way.

360
00:38:30,960 --> 00:38:35,269
如果不能从这端打开，我们就真正的被困在这儿了，明白？
You see, If you don't turn it on from here, we're screwed, okay?

361
00:38:35,269 --> 00:38:38,122
所以我和你们说，我们哪儿也去不了
So I'm telling you guys, we're not going anywhere.

362
00:38:38,760 --> 00:38:39,502
闭嘴！
Shut up.

363
00:38:41,304 --> 00:38:42,335
这个帐篷真漂亮。
This is a nice tent.

364
00:38:44,258 --> 00:38:46,228
大家都有自己的帐篷，真好。
We each get a tent. That's nice.

365
00:39:11,626 --> 00:39:12,616
那是什么？
What the hell is that?

366
00:39:13,669 --> 00:39:15,283
电热毯？才用不上这个。
Thermal blanket. I don't need that.

367
00:39:15,556 --> 00:39:16,434
去和他谈谈。
Talk to him.

368
00:39:21,109 --> 00:39:22,472
什么都有，怎么就缺太阳镜。
I got everything here but sunblock.

369
00:39:23,744 --> 00:39:25,222
嗨，嘿。
Hey. Hi.

370
00:39:26,015 --> 00:39:26,444
嗨。
Hey.

371
00:39:27,558 --> 00:39:29,102
你现在是否该干些什么？
Isn't there something you should be doing right now...

372
00:39:29,951 --> 00:39:31,510
例如把我们从这鬼地方带回去？
Like getting us out of here?

373
00:39:39,904 --> 00:39:41,990
爽足粉, 好极了。
Foot powder. Great.

374
00:39:45,034 --> 00:39:46,528
老兄, 够酷的
Now that's cold.

375
00:40:15,592 --> 00:40:16,694
长官，营地搭建完毕。
Base camp is up, sir.

376
00:41:16,937 --> 00:41:17,575
杰克逊在哪儿？
Where's Jackson?

377
00:41:31,933 --> 00:41:33,760
没事的，没事的。
It's okay. It's okay.

378
00:41:36,562 --> 00:41:37,412
好孩子。
That's a good boy.

379
00:41:41,526 --> 00:41:44,378
别怕，好孩子。
It's okay. Good boy.

380
00:41:46,078 --> 00:41:49,848
怎么？你想要？你也想要尝尝？
What? What do you want? You want some of this?

381
00:41:52,078 --> 00:41:53,469
给，喜欢么？
Here you go. You like that?

382
00:41:54,006 --> 00:41:56,496
慢慢吃，慢慢吃。
There you go. There you go.

383
00:41:56,666 --> 00:41:58,055
换了我就不会乱喂东西。
I wouldn't feed that thing.

384
00:41:59,400 --> 00:42:03,027
它套有轭具，是被驯养的动物。
It's got a harness! It's domesticated!

385
00:42:08,800 --> 00:42:09,519
该死。
Damn it.

386
00:42:09,894 --> 00:42:11,402
松开绳子！
Let go of it!

387
00:42:21,857 --> 00:42:24,275
救命…
Help me...

388
00:42:32,223 --> 00:42:33,535
救命！
Help me!

389
00:43:03,520 --> 00:43:04,393
停下了。
Stop it.

390
00:43:13,284 --> 00:43:14,044
没事吧，杰克逊？
You okay, Jackson?

391
00:43:20,374 --> 00:43:21,003
卡瓦斯基。
Kawalsky.

392
00:43:21,003 --> 00:43:22,208
你掉了这些。
You dropped these.

393
00:43:22,590 --> 00:43:23,042
布朗。
Brown.

394
00:43:28,257 --> 00:43:28,930
离我远点。
Get away from me.

395
00:44:41,747 --> 00:44:42,521
放轻松。
Easy.

396
00:45:07,732 --> 00:45:10,347
好，杰克逊，看你的了。
All right, Jackson. You're on.

397
00:45:12,403 --> 00:45:12,844
我？
Me?

398
00:45:15,162 --> 00:45:17,434
你是语言学家，试着和他们交流下。
You're the linguist. Try to talk to 'em.

399
00:45:26,062 --> 00:45:26,532
嘿。
Hi.

400
00:45:58,596 --> 00:45:59,604
你跟他们说了什么？
What the hell did you say to him?

401
00:45:59,604 --> 00:46:00,100
什么也没说。
Nothing.

402
00:46:17,034 --> 00:46:17,548
嗨，
Hey.

403
00:46:20,805 --> 00:46:21,458
没事的。
It's okay.

404
00:46:24,092 --> 00:46:27,550
不用害怕，懂吗？明白吗？
It's okay. It's okay. See? See? Yeah.

405
00:46:46,920 --> 00:46:49,200
主要成分：石英。
Quartz, primary element.

406
00:47:46,599 --> 00:47:47,409
我也不知道是什么意思，
I can't make it out.

407
00:47:47,409 --> 00:47:49,438
听起来很耳熟，有点类似柏柏尔语,
It sounds familiar... a bit like Berber.

408
00:47:50,477 --> 00:47:52,284
又像其他语言。
Maybe Chadic or Omotic.

409
00:48:19,882 --> 00:48:20,494
谢谢。
Thank you.

410
00:48:28,543 --> 00:48:28,966
看。
Here.

411
00:49:06,977 --> 00:49:07,576
这是什么意思?
What's that mean?

412
00:49:08,474 --> 00:49:09,592
我一无所知。
I have no idea.

413
00:49:12,515 --> 00:49:13,866
他邀请我们跟他走。
He's inviting us to go with him.

414
00:49:14,758 --> 00:49:15,636
你怎么能肯定？
How can you be so sure?

415
00:49:18,050 --> 00:49:20,144
因为他就是在邀请我们跟他走。
Because he's inviting us to go with him.

416
00:49:23,800 --> 00:49:25,226
我们本来就要寻找文明，
We were looking for signs of civilization.

417
00:49:25,226 --> 00:49:26,412
很明显，我们已经找到了。
Obviously, we found it.

418
00:49:27,908 --> 00:49:30,026
要想回去，这是最好的机会。
You want me to get us back home, this is our best shot.

419
00:49:30,375 --> 00:49:31,142
上校，他说的没错，
Colonel, he's right. 

420
00:49:31,559 --> 00:49:33,725
我分析了一下他们开采的矿物，
I took some readings on what they were mining back there.

421
00:49:35,624 --> 00:49:37,108
和星际之门的成分完全一样。
It's the same material as the Stargate.

422
00:49:42,287 --> 00:49:43,210
联系营地，
Radio base camp.

423
00:49:45,128 --> 00:49:47,633
告诉他们注意警戒，直到我们回去。
Tell 'em to keep that area secured until we get back.

424
00:49:49,114 --> 00:49:49,758
是，长官
Yes, sir.

425
00:49:52,141 --> 00:49:52,917
营地，回话。
Base camp, come in.

426
00:49:53,120 --> 00:49:53,512
等一等，
Hold on.

427
00:49:53,600 --> 00:49:55,195
费瑞提，找到他们了！过来！
Feretti, I've got 'em! Come on!

428
00:49:57,970 --> 00:49:58,672
是，长官。
Yes, Sir.

429
00:50:00,870 --> 00:50:02,070
长官, 你能再说一遍吗？
Can you repeat that, sir?

430
00:50:02,901 --> 00:50:05,319
奥尼尔上校说保护好营地。
Colonel O'Neil has requested that you secure base camp.

431
00:50:05,404 --> 00:50:06,804
看来我们要在这里呆一段时间了。
Looks like we're gonna be Here for a while.

432
00:50:06,804 --> 00:50:07,398
是，长官。
Okay, sir.

433
00:50:08,046 --> 00:50:08,530
明白吗？
You understand?

434
00:50:08,530 --> 00:50:09,086
是，长官。
Yes, sir.

435
00:50:11,201 --> 00:50:12,211
怎么回事?
So what's the story?

436
00:50:12,211 --> 00:50:12,886
他们发现了什么？
Did they find something?

437
00:50:12,887 --> 00:50:15,061
我们不回去了。
They're not coming back, Okay?

438
00:50:15,061 --> 00:50:16,912
这不太好。
This is not good. I'm telling you guys.

439
00:52:35,743 --> 00:52:36,704
拉之眼。
The eye of Ra.

440
00:52:41,018 --> 00:52:42,250
那是埃及的太阳神。
It's the Egyptian sun god.

441
00:52:44,730 --> 00:52:45,840
他们以为我们是他的使者。
They think he sent us here.

442
00:52:46,815 --> 00:52:50,270
是的，可能就是这玩意才使他们这么想的吧。
Yeah. I wonder what could've given them that idea?

443
00:52:53,156 --> 00:52:56,376
拉，拉？
Ra. Ra?

444
00:53:04,208 --> 00:53:05,137
他们这是要到哪儿去？
Where they all goin'?

445
00:53:09,112 --> 00:53:11,718
请回答，费瑞提，我听不见你的话。
Come in. Come in. Feretti, I can't hear you.

446
00:53:12,250 --> 00:53:13,256
长官，没办法听清。
Sir, I can't make this out.

447
00:53:15,631 --> 00:53:16,422
费瑞提，请重复。
Feretti, say again.

448
00:53:18,180 --> 00:53:19,880
我们必须放弃主营地！
We have to abandon the base camp!

449
00:53:20,849 --> 00:53:23,668
重复，我们必须放弃主营地！
Repeat, we have to abandon base camp!

450
00:53:23,894 --> 00:53:25,410
没有用，没有用的！
It's useless! It won't work in this!

451
00:53:26,432 --> 00:53:28,064
弗里曼，快走，快！
Freeman, let's go! Let's move!

452
00:53:28,350 --> 00:53:30,381
全体进入里面掩蔽，
Everybody, back inside. Come on!

453
00:53:30,578 --> 00:53:31,712
尽量多带物品！
Just take what you can carry!

454
00:53:33,031 --> 00:53:34,320
电池包！带上它！
The battery pack! Grab it!

455
00:53:44,657 --> 00:53:46,363
我们立刻回去。
All right. We're goin' back right now.

456
00:53:46,516 --> 00:53:47,080
走！
Let's go.

457
00:53:49,127 --> 00:53:49,972
等一下！
Wait. Wait!

458
00:53:51,797 --> 00:53:52,921
让一让。
Move it. Move it.

459
00:53:55,092 --> 00:53:56,256
回去，让一让。
Get back. Move it.

460
00:53:59,264 --> 00:54:00,178
让一让路。
Move out of the way.

461
00:54:16,574 --> 00:54:17,032
离开这。
Get over here.

462
00:54:41,346 --> 00:54:42,066
待在这里。
Stay here.

463
00:55:00,282 --> 00:55:01,520
是什么，上校？
What is it, Colonel?

464
00:55:02,075 --> 00:55:03,533
大沙暴，正往这里来。
Sandstorm comin' this way.

465
00:55:06,565 --> 00:55:08,463
真是一个开枪的绝妙理由。
That would've been an excellent reason to shoot everyone.

466
00:55:09,534 --> 00:55:10,700
在沙暴结束之前，我们将待在这里。
We'll stay until it's over.

467
00:55:22,386 --> 00:55:23,930
对不起。
I'm sorry. All right?

468
00:55:36,818 --> 00:55:39,156
回到金字塔里去！
Get back into the pyramid!

469
00:55:42,166 --> 00:55:43,110
这沙暴是从哪里冒出来的？
The hell did that come from?

470
00:55:49,750 --> 00:55:51,196
卡瓦斯基，布朗，收到了吗？
Kawalsky? Brown? Do you read?

471
00:56:11,251 --> 00:56:14,326
杰克逊，我们不该乱吃这儿的东西。
Hey, Jackson. I don't think we should eat any food here.

472
00:56:14,824 --> 00:56:17,178
不吃的话，他们也许会认为这是一种侮辱。
I don't know. They might consider that an insult.

473
00:56:28,299 --> 00:56:30,394
好吧，我们现在不能冒犯他们。是吗，丹尼尔？
Well, we don't want to offend them, now, do we, Daniel?

474
00:56:46,139 --> 00:56:46,880
味道像鸡肉，
Tastes like chicken.

475
00:56:48,230 --> 00:56:50,116
很像鸡肉，味道好极了。
Tastes like chicken. It's good.

476
00:56:53,231 --> 00:56:53,646
味道…
Tastes...

477
00:56:59,651 --> 00:57:02,446
味道像鸡肉，不错！
Tastes like chicken. Good!

478
00:57:06,795 --> 00:57:10,324
杰克逊，你说那是个埃及符号。
Jackson. You said that was an Egyptian symbol.

479
00:57:10,579 --> 00:57:11,666
没错，拉之眼。
Yeah, the eye of Ra.

480
00:57:12,363 --> 00:57:14,272
那么理所当然的
Would you say then that it might stand to reason

481
00:57:14,939 --> 00:57:17,053
他们是否也使用埃及象形文字？
that if they know one Egyptian symbol...

482
00:57:18,296 --> 00:57:19,104
是的。
Yes.

483
00:57:45,906 --> 00:57:46,932
出了什么事？
What the hell's goin' on?

484
00:57:50,869 --> 00:57:52,422
看来写字对他们是禁忌。
It seems like writing is forbidden to them.

485
00:58:00,672 --> 00:58:01,754
怎么？干什么？
What? What?

486
00:58:08,220 --> 00:58:09,518
他们要我跟他们一起去。
They want me to go with them.

487
00:58:09,981 --> 00:58:10,825
要不要去？
Should I stay?

488
00:58:12,259 --> 00:58:15,171
我还是跟他们走好了。我去，不会有事的。
I'll go with them. I'll go. I'll be fine.

489
00:58:22,901 --> 00:58:26,441
好的，很好，够了，够了。
Okay. That's good. All right. All right.

490
00:58:26,988 --> 00:58:28,027
什么味道？
What is that smell?

491
00:58:29,241 --> 00:58:32,034
够了，真的够了。
It's... Okay. That's good.

492
00:58:32,118 --> 00:58:33,912
好了，我认为够干净了。
I think that's good. My hands are pretty clean.

493
00:58:34,108 --> 00:58:35,407
非常感谢。
Thank you very, very much.

494
00:58:36,122 --> 00:58:37,653
非常感谢，真是太好了。
Thank you very... That was very nice.

495
00:58:38,917 --> 00:58:40,186
谢谢，很好。
Thank you. That was great.

496
00:58:41,628 --> 00:58:43,767
我闻起来好多了。
I smell much better, now that...

497
00:58:44,814 --> 00:58:45,615
是的，谢谢。
Yes, thank you.

498
00:58:47,968 --> 00:58:51,469
老天，我闻起来像头牦牛。
Oh, christ. I smell like a yak.

499
00:58:54,891 --> 00:58:56,612
不，不，够了。
No, No. please, no more. Please.

500
00:58:58,019 --> 00:59:00,721
拜托，不要了，我很干净。
Please, no more. I'm fine. I'm clean.

501
00:59:04,414 --> 00:59:08,720
我想你又是一位帮我梳洗的人…
I thought you were one of the other cleaning...

502
00:59:23,962 --> 00:59:26,398
不，不，你无须这样。
No. You don't have to do that. Please.

503
00:59:27,455 --> 00:59:29,369
你还是出去的好，好吗？
Maybe you should go. Okay?

504
00:59:30,135 --> 00:59:31,934
没事的，也许你应该离开。
It's okay. Maybe you should go.

505
00:59:33,179 --> 00:59:35,912
没事，没事，来吧。
No, No. It's okay. It's okay. It's all right. Here.

506
00:59:36,546 --> 00:59:37,778
让我来处理。
Let me grab this.

507
00:59:49,580 --> 00:59:53,380
不不，这是我的意思，我想要…谢谢你。
No, no, no, no. It's me. I wanted to... thank you.

508
00:59:53,825 --> 00:59:56,195
我想…我非常高兴。
I wanted to... I'm very happy.

509
00:59:58,462 --> 00:59:59,265
谢谢。
Thank you.

510
01:00:09,466 --> 01:00:10,271
丹尼尔。
Daniel.

511
01:00:11,894 --> 01:00:12,706
丹尼尔。
Daniel.

512
01:00:12,886 --> 01:00:14,979
不，是我的名字，
No, I'm...

513
01:00:18,767 --> 01:00:21,219
丹尼尔，我叫丹尼尔。
Daniel. I'm Daniel.

514
01:00:23,620 --> 01:00:24,232
莎拉。
Sha'uri.

515
01:00:33,698 --> 01:00:34,205
我们来自…
We came...

516
01:00:38,745 --> 01:00:44,085
这个金字塔。明白吗？我们从金字塔来。
Pyramid. See, we came from the pyramid.

517
01:00:46,544 --> 01:00:47,368
没关系，
It's okay.

518
01:00:48,832 --> 01:00:49,482
别介意。
Never mind.

519
01:00:52,759 --> 01:00:53,357
没关系。
It's okay.

520
01:01:24,582 --> 01:01:25,178
地球？
Earth?

521
01:01:27,755 --> 01:01:29,515
你懂象形文？
You know this symbol?

522
01:01:30,162 --> 01:01:31,152
你懂象形文？
You know this symbol?

523
01:01:32,179 --> 01:01:34,130
你见过这个符号？
You've seen this symbol?

524
01:01:38,805 --> 01:01:40,948
带我去看，你带我去看看。
Show me. You show me.

525
01:01:46,348 --> 01:01:48,381
卡瓦斯基，基地呼叫，收到了吗？
Kawalsky, this is base. Do you copy?

526
01:01:49,235 --> 01:01:50,459
你这是在浪费电池，
You're wasting the battery.

527
01:01:52,360 --> 01:01:53,867
这样的沙暴里什么也不会收到，
We'll never get anything in this storm.

528
01:01:53,867 --> 01:01:55,195
等沙暴过去了再试。
You'll have to wait till it passes.

529
01:01:55,280 --> 01:01:58,490
好吧，若它能过去的话。
Yeah, right. If it passes.

530
01:02:00,548 --> 01:02:01,973
我曾经在中东驻扎，
You know, I was stationed in the Middle East.

531
01:02:02,081 --> 01:02:03,510
也没有见过这么大的沙暴。
I've never seen anything like it.

532
01:02:03,645 --> 01:02:04,737
对，对。
Yeah, Yeah.

533
01:02:05,540 --> 01:02:06,104
我不明白，
I don't understand. 

534
01:02:06,104 --> 01:02:08,310
我们为什么不自己开门回去？
Why don't we just turn the gate back on ourselves?

535
01:02:09,029 --> 01:02:10,196
是啊这又有多难？
Yeah, how hard can it be?

536
01:02:10,604 --> 01:02:12,471
太难了！
That would be great. Yeah.

537
01:02:12,471 --> 01:02:14,042
我们将会因为错误的开启顺序…
We could turn the thing in the wrong order...

538
01:02:14,042 --> 01:02:17,510
在外太空丧命。
and materialize in the vacuum of outer space.

539
01:02:17,510 --> 01:02:21,150
你知道排列顺序有多少种组合？
Do you have any idea how many possible combinations there are on that thing?

540
01:02:21,639 --> 01:02:23,240
不知道，多少种？
No. How many?

541
01:02:25,101 --> 01:02:25,805
闭嘴！
Shut up.

542
01:03:31,167 --> 01:03:32,197
出了什么事？
What the hell is goin' on?

543
01:04:35,148 --> 01:04:36,089
大家散开。
All right. Spread out.

544
01:04:38,151 --> 01:04:38,944
来吧，继续。
Come on. Let's move.

545
01:05:18,775 --> 01:05:19,740
让我们出去。
Let's move out.

546
01:06:25,508 --> 01:06:26,552
没事的，这只是个打火机。
Okay. It's just a lighter.

547
01:06:27,635 --> 01:06:28,077
看。
See?

548
01:06:29,929 --> 01:06:30,768
看着。
Look.

549
01:06:32,481 --> 01:06:33,056
看到了吗？
See?

550
01:06:37,861 --> 01:06:38,489
给你。
Here.

551
01:06:51,236 --> 01:06:52,284
是啊，很不可思议。
Yeah, It's pretty fabulous.

552
01:07:01,252 --> 01:07:01,767
是的。
Yeah.

553
01:07:46,464 --> 01:07:47,138
是的，你做的很对，
Yeah, You're right.

554
01:07:48,196 --> 01:07:49,686
抽烟确实很愚蠢。
It's pretty stupid.

555
01:07:55,992 --> 01:07:57,950
你留着吧。
No, You keep it.

556
01:08:01,249 --> 01:08:01,901
送给你了。
It's yours.

557
01:08:15,052 --> 01:08:15,413
不，
No.

558
01:08:19,789 --> 01:08:20,310
这样很危险！
Dangerous!

559
01:08:44,605 --> 01:08:45,501
这是什么地方？
What is this place?

560
01:08:50,632 --> 01:08:51,115
来吧。
Here.

561
01:09:17,388 --> 01:09:17,919
什么？
What?

562
01:10:50,798 --> 01:10:51,566
还是没有任何信号？
No signal at all?

563
01:10:52,487 --> 01:10:53,029
完全没有。
Nothing.

564
01:10:56,904 --> 01:10:57,611
干扰太多？
More interference?

565
01:10:59,573 --> 01:11:02,332
不是，他们好像不在那里。
No. They're simply not there.

566
01:11:28,189 --> 01:11:29,972
我怎么也找不到杰克逊，长官。
I haven't been able to locate Jackson, sir.

567
01:11:49,292 --> 01:11:50,417
我们在找杰克逊。
We're looking for Jackson.

568
01:11:53,002 --> 01:11:54,390
杰克逊，穿夹克的那家伙。
Jackson. The guy who wears this jacket.

569
01:11:55,004 --> 01:11:58,757
他有长长的、披下来的头发…
He's got, like, long hair that comes down...

570
01:11:59,824 --> 01:12:01,340
不是，不是。
No, no, no.

571
01:12:02,748 --> 01:12:04,787
他戴一付眼镜，不戴就看不清楚。
He wears glasses, so he can see.

572
01:12:12,146 --> 01:12:14,046
我就知道我身处某个神秘星球，
Guess the word "Dweeb" doesn't mean anything to you guys, does it?

573
01:12:15,927 --> 01:12:19,679
要寻找一个穿夹克的白痴。
Yeah. Why not? I'm on planet X, looking for a dweeb who wears green fatigues.

574
01:12:19,779 --> 01:12:23,032
他穿一件夹克衫，头发长得遮住了眼睛，
He wears this jacket. He's got long hair. It comes over his eyes.

575
01:12:23,407 --> 01:12:26,663
戴眼镜，还打喷嚏。
He wears glasses and... sneezes.

576
01:12:34,130 --> 01:12:36,188
小鸡！小鸡！
Chicken. Chicken.

577
01:12:37,052 --> 01:12:39,491
对，是鸡，你们明白了。
Chicken. Chicken man! You got it.

578
01:12:48,641 --> 01:12:49,288
你想要这个?
You want this?

579
01:13:24,343 --> 01:13:25,868
我还以为你不会说他们的语言。
Thought you couldn't speak their language.

580
01:13:26,614 --> 01:13:27,610
你吓了我一跳。
You scared me.

581
01:13:29,204 --> 01:13:30,630
这是一种古埃及方言，
It's an ancient Egyptian dialect.

582
01:13:31,433 --> 01:13:33,970
自成一体，是独立进化的一系，
I mean, like the rest of their culture, it's evolved completely independently...

583
01:13:34,031 --> 01:13:36,432
但是只要掌握了元音…
But once you know the vowels...

584
01:13:36,939 --> 01:13:38,036
你只要回答我的问题。
Just answer the question.

585
01:13:40,442 --> 01:13:42,418
我不过学会如何发音而已，
I mean, I just had to learn how to pronounce it.

586
01:13:42,567 --> 01:13:46,138
这种语言一千多年前就失传了。
I mean, it hasn't been a living, spoken language in more than 1,000 years.

587
01:13:47,451 --> 01:13:51,767
这个说的是：“一个来自遥远星球的旅行者…
I mean, look at this. It says "A traveller from distant stars...

588
01:13:52,204 --> 01:13:56,083
从正在毁灭的行星上逃离，寻找使他延续生命的办法。
Escaped from a dying world, looking for a way to extend his own life.

589
01:13:57,083 --> 01:14:00,475
他的身体日渐衰弱，却没有办法阻止。”
His body decaying and weak, he couldn't prevent his own demise."

590
01:14:00,504 --> 01:14:03,128
显然他的族人正面临灭亡。
Apparently his whole species was becoming extinct.

591
01:14:03,720 --> 01:14:06,360
“因此他在星系中探索…
"So he travelled or...

592
01:14:06,635 --> 01:14:09,796
寻求逃脱死亡的办法。”
searched the Galaxies, looking for a way to cheat death."

593
01:14:11,223 --> 01:14:12,674
看这里。
And look here.

594
01:14:13,350 --> 01:14:16,306
“他来到一个富饶而充满生机的世界，
"He came to a world rich with life...

595
01:14:16,685 --> 01:14:18,936
在那儿他遇到原始的种族。”
where he encountered a primitive race."

596
01:14:19,434 --> 01:14:19,969
人类。
Humans.

597
01:14:21,191 --> 01:14:24,121
“让他的力量和知识，
"A species which, with all his powers and knowledge...

598
01:14:24,125 --> 01:14:26,295
能永远保持的寄生体。
He could maintain indefinitely.

599
01:14:26,655 --> 01:14:29,957
他知道，利用人类的身体，就可以获得新生命。”
He realized within a human body he had a chance for a new life."

600
01:14:30,922 --> 01:14:33,933
接下来，他找到了一个年青人。
Now, he apparently found a young boy.

601
01:14:34,204 --> 01:14:38,401
上面说：“受惊的村民四散逃跑，黑夜成为白昼，
It says, "as the frightened villagers ran, night became day.

602
01:14:39,168 --> 01:14:43,131
被好奇心驱使，抛开恐惧，他朝那光走去。”
Curious, and without fear, he walked towards the light."

603
01:14:47,009 --> 01:14:49,736
拉带走了他，占据了他的身体，
Ra took him and possessed his body...

604
01:14:50,236 --> 01:14:53,417
就像是寄生虫找到了宿主。
Like some kind of a parasite looking for a host.

605
01:14:55,111 --> 01:14:56,912
在这人类的躯壳下，
And inhabiting this human form...

606
01:14:57,202 --> 01:14:59,060
他自封为统治者。
he appointed himself ruler.

607
01:15:01,124 --> 01:15:04,345
他通过星际之门，将上千人带到这个星球上，
He used the Stargate to bring thousands of people here to this planet...

608
01:15:04,652 --> 01:15:06,861
为他开采矿物，
as workers for the mines.

609
01:15:07,506 --> 01:15:08,557
就如我们所见的那个矿场。
Just like the one we saw.

610
01:15:09,141 --> 01:15:12,158
那种矿物明显是他科技的基础，
This mineral is clearly the building block of all his technology.

611
01:15:12,242 --> 01:15:14,343
由此，他就能维持永恒的生命。
With this, he can sustain eternal life.

612
01:15:15,788 --> 01:15:18,768
此时，地球上也有事发生…
Now something happened... where is it... back on Earth...

613
01:15:19,169 --> 01:15:21,768
在一次起义中，星际之门被掩埋。
A rebellion or uprising... and the Stargate was buried there.

614
01:15:22,836 --> 01:15:24,463
为了防止这儿的人也叛变，
Fearful of a rebellion here...

615
01:15:25,097 --> 01:15:26,515
拉就禁止了人们读写，
Ra outlawed reading and writing.

616
01:15:28,175 --> 01:15:29,696
他不希望人们了解真相。
He didn't want the people to remember the truth.

617
01:15:31,123 --> 01:15:33,407
杰克逊，你最好来这儿看看。
Jackson. I think you better take a look at this.

618
01:15:41,730 --> 01:15:43,933
是了，这就是我们要找的。
That's it. That's what we're looking for.

619
01:15:44,560 --> 01:15:45,775
我就知道肯定藏在这儿，
They must have hidden it here...

620
01:15:45,859 --> 01:15:47,863
他们希望地球上的星际之门有一天被重新打开。
In hopes that one day the gate on Earth could be reopened.

621
01:15:49,363 --> 01:15:51,093
我就知道他们一定有这东西，在某处留存下来。
I knew they'd have it written down someplace.

622
01:15:54,144 --> 01:15:54,677
等等。
Wait a minute.

623
01:15:55,887 --> 01:15:56,739
第七坐标呢？
Where's the seventh symbol?

624
01:15:57,958 --> 01:15:58,761
一定是破碎了。
It must have broken.

625
01:15:59,732 --> 01:16:01,332
肯定还在附近。
It's gotta be here somewhere.

626
01:16:03,106 --> 01:16:04,529
找到了。
I got it here.

627
01:16:09,719 --> 01:16:10,519
已经被风化了。
It's worn off.

628
01:16:12,190 --> 01:16:13,850
没有第七坐标我也无能为力。
I can't make it work without the seventh symbol.

629
01:16:16,557 --> 01:16:17,583
好了，算了吧。
All right. That's it.

630
01:16:18,427 --> 01:16:19,827
卡瓦斯基，布朗。
Kawalsky. Brown.

631
01:16:33,389 --> 01:16:34,187
快跟上，杰克逊！
Come on, Jackson!

632
01:17:20,746 --> 01:17:21,831
那是怎么回事？
What the hell is that?

633
01:17:29,713 --> 01:17:30,180
给。
Here.

634
01:17:31,860 --> 01:17:32,645
也许你用的上。
You might need this.

635
01:18:52,198 --> 01:18:52,527
小心！
Look out!

636
01:18:56,160 --> 01:18:56,882
我们要去哪儿？
Where are we going?

637
01:18:59,678 --> 01:19:00,934
为什么要到星际之门那里去？
Why are we going to the Stargate?

638
01:19:00,934 --> 01:19:01,812
我又没办法启动它。
I can't make it work.

639
01:19:04,308 --> 01:19:06,726
给我守住斜道口，只要有东西过来就开枪。
Stay right here and shoot anything that comes down that ramp.

640
01:19:07,038 --> 01:19:07,586
你要干什么？
What are you doing?

641
01:19:08,114 --> 01:19:08,852
掩护我就行了。
Just cover me.

642
01:19:17,593 --> 01:19:18,156
那是什么？
What is that?

643
01:19:20,550 --> 01:19:21,310
你在找什么？
What are you looking for?

644
01:19:21,996 --> 01:19:22,545
不见了。
It's gone.

645
01:19:57,328 --> 01:19:58,342
把枪放下，杰克逊。
Put it down, Jackson.

646
01:22:03,908 --> 01:22:06,661
你们想来这里消灭我。

647
01:22:09,743 --> 01:22:10,312
那是什么?
What is that?

648
01:22:17,226 --> 01:22:19,629
是个炸弹，是你之前寻找的东西？
It's a bomb, isn't it? That's what you were looking for.

649
01:22:20,796 --> 01:22:22,004
你到底在想些什么？
What the hell were you thinking?

650
01:22:23,452 --> 01:22:24,408
你到这里来是干什么的?
What'd you come here for?

651
01:23:15,142 --> 01:23:16,392
等等！不要！
Wait! No!

652
01:23:17,519 --> 01:23:20,699
奥尼尔，等等，不要！
O'Neil! Wait! No! No! 

653
01:24:19,497 --> 01:24:21,140
上校，是我。
Colonel! It's me.

654
01:24:22,459 --> 01:24:22,853
你没事吧？
You all right?

655
01:24:35,053 --> 01:24:35,578
杰克逊呢？
Where's Jackson?

656
01:26:36,009 --> 01:26:36,762
莎拉。
Sha'uri.

657
01:26:38,057 --> 01:26:40,935
莎拉，这里发生了什么事？

658
01:26:41,185 --> 01:26:43,396
太阳神惩罚了我们。

659
01:26:43,646 --> 01:26:45,356
为什么？

660
01:26:45,607 --> 01:26:47,859
丹尼尔怎样？

661
01:26:49,861 --> 01:26:51,654
丹尼尔怎么了？

662
01:27:13,468 --> 01:27:17,555
儿子，我们不应该帮助陌生人。

663
01:30:06,015 --> 01:30:07,433
我不是已经死了吗？

664
01:30:11,854 --> 01:30:14,565
这就是我为什么选择你们人类，

665
01:30:14,816 --> 01:30:17,443
你们的身体非常容易修理。

666
01:30:23,408 --> 01:30:28,705
你们进步了许多，已经掌握原子能了。

667
01:30:29,872 --> 01:30:31,416
你打算干什么？

668
01:30:35,003 --> 01:30:39,924
你们不应该重新打开这扇门。

669
01:30:44,929 --> 01:30:49,142
过会，我将把你们的武器送回到你们的世界，

670
01:30:49,392 --> 01:30:54,480
并且加入我们的矿物，

671
01:30:54,731 --> 01:30:58,276
这将使它的毁灭力

672
01:30:58,526 --> 01:31:00,612
提升百倍。

673
01:31:00,862 --> 01:31:03,031
你为什么这么做？

674
01:31:03,281 --> 01:31:05,950
我创造了你们的文明。

675
01:31:06,200 --> 01:31:09,996
现在我将亲手毁灭它。

676
01:31:27,805 --> 01:31:32,352
不过在奴隶质疑我的威权之前，

677
01:31:32,602 --> 01:31:36,439
你要证明我是他们唯一的神，

678
01:31:36,689 --> 01:31:40,485
杀死你的同伴来为我证明。

679
01:31:41,736 --> 01:31:43,613
如果我拒绝？

680
01:31:43,863 --> 01:31:47,075
那我就杀了你，

681
01:31:47,325 --> 01:31:49,202
以及所有接触过你的人。

682
01:31:51,829 --> 01:31:56,000
这里只能有一个太阳神！

683
01:32:14,143 --> 01:32:17,522
莎拉，太阳神要召见所有人。

684
01:32:18,940 --> 01:32:20,358
是一个死刑示众。

685
01:32:21,776 --> 01:32:26,406
斯嘎拉，纳贝，你们听我说。

686
01:32:31,411 --> 01:32:34,038
我们必须阻止这一切。

687
01:32:34,289 --> 01:32:36,749
我要转述丹尼尔告诉我的事情，

688
01:32:37,000 --> 01:32:40,545
关于我们的历史，我们从何而来，

689
01:32:41,713 --> 01:32:45,008
以及我们怎样才能不再当别人的奴隶。

690
01:34:28,657 --> 01:34:29,168
过来！
Come on!

691
01:34:29,837 --> 01:34:30,981
快走，伙计们！
Let's go, guys!

692
01:34:45,122 --> 01:34:46,164
弗里曼！
Freeman!

693
01:34:48,501 --> 01:34:51,211
弗里曼！弗里曼！
Freeman! Freeman!

694
01:34:53,923 --> 01:34:54,983
杰克逊，快跟上！
Jackson, keep going!

695
01:34:55,633 --> 01:34:57,876
快走！卡瓦斯基！
Over there! Come on! Kawalsky!

696
01:35:08,741 --> 01:35:09,118
上来！
Come on!

697
01:35:51,814 --> 01:35:52,200
杰克逊！
Jackson!

698
01:35:53,858 --> 01:35:55,817
赶快，赶快！
Come on! Come on!

699
01:36:48,459 --> 01:36:51,504
胜利万岁！

700
01:36:54,882 --> 01:36:57,343
我们研究了你们的武器。

701
01:37:00,800 --> 01:37:01,443
给，上校。
Here, Colonel.

702
01:37:06,055 --> 01:37:06,684
你怎么看？
So, what do you think?

703
01:37:08,645 --> 01:37:10,434
他们的确不是正规军，
They're not exactly special forces,

704
01:37:10,607 --> 01:37:12,659
但他们渴望加入我们。
but they sure were eager to join up.

705
01:37:13,020 --> 01:37:15,744
把枪收好，中尉，免的他们伤了自己。
Take these guns away, Lieutenant, before they hurt themselves.

706
01:37:18,943 --> 01:37:19,303
长官？
Sir?

707
01:37:19,532 --> 01:37:20,730
听我说，送他们回去。
You heard me. Send 'em all home.

708
01:37:22,178 --> 01:37:23,563
但他们现在无家可归了，
There's no place for these kids to go.

709
01:37:24,907 --> 01:37:26,581
而且现在我们还需要他们帮忙。
Anyway, we could sure use their help right now.

710
01:37:26,687 --> 01:37:27,297
帮什么？
For what?

711
01:37:30,203 --> 01:37:31,015
帮什么忙？
To do what?

712
01:37:42,585 --> 01:37:43,920
为什么你不告诉他们？
Why don't you just tell 'em everything?

713
01:37:46,887 --> 01:37:48,226
为什么你不告诉他们关于核弹的事情？
Why don't you tell them about the bomb?

714
01:37:50,701 --> 01:37:51,505
他在说什么？
What's he talking' about?

715
01:37:57,231 --> 01:37:58,608
我的任务很简单，
My orders were simple.

716
01:38:01,902 --> 01:38:04,037
看看是否有任何潜在的危险，
Track down signs of any possible danger.

717
01:38:05,406 --> 01:38:07,073
若有发现，就炸毁星门。
If I found any, blow up the Stargate.

718
01:38:08,492 --> 01:38:09,524
现在，我发现了危险。
Well, I found some.

719
01:38:10,789 --> 01:38:12,042
现在，你的炸弹落在对方手里了，
Well, your bomb is his now.

720
01:38:13,080 --> 01:38:14,753
明天他就要将之送返地球，
And tomorrow he's gonna send it back to Earth...

721
01:38:15,455 --> 01:38:17,406
还添加了这里的矿石。
Along with a shipment of that mineral they mine here.

722
01:38:18,183 --> 01:38:20,753
等到爆炸时，
And when that thing goes off, it's gonna cause an explosion...

723
01:38:20,838 --> 01:38:22,628
威力更胜之前千百倍，
a hundred times more destructive 

724
01:38:22,628 --> 01:38:24,149
就此一颗也能毁灭我们的世界。
than that bomb alone is capable of.

725
01:38:26,528 --> 01:38:28,682
我会在传送之前阻止他。
I'll intercept that bomb before he can send it through.

726
01:38:29,422 --> 01:38:30,380
之前为什么没人告诉我？
Why wasn't I told of this?

727
01:38:31,106 --> 01:38:33,237
因为没有告诉你们的理由，卡瓦斯基，
Because there wasn't any reason to tell you, Kawalsky.

728
01:38:33,283 --> 01:38:34,636
你们本不该在这里，
You weren't even supposed to be here.

729
01:38:34,636 --> 01:38:36,527
原计划你们早该和丹尼尔返回了。
You were all gonna go right back through with Daniel.

730
01:38:38,211 --> 01:38:40,231
我自愿留下来，并将星门炸毁，
I was gonna stay behind alone and blow up the Stargate...

731
01:38:40,316 --> 01:38:41,589
这正是我将要做的。
And that's exactly what I'm gonna do.

732
01:38:42,072 --> 01:38:44,029
既然此门存在于地球上是个威胁，
It's the gate on Earth that poses a threat.

733
01:38:44,043 --> 01:38:45,721
那把它关闭即可。
That's the one that we have to shut down.

734
01:38:46,280 --> 01:38:47,655
你说的也许没错，
You're absolutely right.

735
01:38:48,782 --> 01:38:50,497
可正因你也不知道如何回去，
But since you don't know how to get us back...

736
01:38:52,088 --> 01:38:53,608
我们才没有选择了，不是吗？
We don't have that option, do we?

737
01:39:13,396 --> 01:39:15,398
他们在哪里？

738
01:39:18,693 --> 01:39:20,445
回答！

739
01:39:20,695 --> 01:39:24,991
我们已经找了所有的地方。

740
01:39:25,241 --> 01:39:27,035
有人在帮他们。

741
01:39:54,905 --> 01:39:56,189
其实来之前你就已经很清楚，
You had accepted the fact that,

742
01:39:56,189 --> 01:39:58,768
不管实际上发生何事，你都不会回家了。
No matter what happened, you would not be going home.

743
01:40:02,248 --> 01:40:03,734
难道没有任何人牵挂你吗？
Don't you have people who care about you?

744
01:40:04,847 --> 01:40:05,674
你有家人吗？
Do you have a family?

745
01:40:07,987 --> 01:40:08,944
曾经有过，
I had a family.

746
01:40:12,741 --> 01:40:15,463
丧子之痛已经使我无所牵挂。
No one should ever have to outlive their own child.

747
01:40:17,413 --> 01:40:18,163
我还不想死，
I don't want to die.

748
01:40:19,725 --> 01:40:20,864
你的手下也不想死，
Your men don't want to die.

749
01:40:21,667 --> 01:40:23,505
这儿的人更不想死。
And these people here don't want to die.

750
01:40:25,796 --> 01:40:27,366
你却这样急着死去，不感到羞愧吗？
It's a shame you're in such a hurry to.

751
01:41:14,267 --> 01:41:16,269
你竟然让他们逃走了？

752
01:41:28,364 --> 01:41:31,200
我不需要失败者！

753
01:42:10,031 --> 01:42:11,532
你们为什么取笑我？

754
01:42:11,783 --> 01:42:13,743
丈夫是不用做这种事的。

755
01:42:17,157 --> 01:42:17,757
丈夫？
Husband?

756
01:42:46,567 --> 01:42:47,694
我们已经结婚了？

757
01:42:49,612 --> 01:42:51,114
你不要生气。

758
01:42:53,366 --> 01:42:55,535
我还没有告诉他们。

759
01:42:55,785 --> 01:42:57,078
告诉他们什么？

760
01:43:03,501 --> 01:43:06,296
告诉他们你没有要我。

761
01:43:47,462 --> 01:43:49,172
你在画什么？

762
01:43:52,675 --> 01:43:54,302
我们今天的胜利。

763
01:44:15,543 --> 01:44:16,686
把月亮连起来。
Connect the moons.

764
01:44:21,949 --> 01:44:23,425
那就是这个星球的标记。
This is the symbol for this planet.

765
01:44:24,222 --> 01:44:24,734
没错。
That's it.

766
01:44:27,287 --> 01:44:28,105
这就是起点。
The point of origin.

767
01:44:32,429 --> 01:44:33,111
你在干什么？
What are you doing?

768
01:44:34,790 --> 01:44:35,435
我找到了。
I found it.

769
01:44:36,429 --> 01:44:37,217
你在说什么？
What are you talking' about?

770
01:44:38,146 --> 01:44:38,819
第七个坐标。
The seventh symbol.

771
01:44:42,231 --> 01:44:43,038
我们可以回家了。
We're goin' home.

772
01:45:09,156 --> 01:45:09,859
我们走。
Let's go.

773
01:45:13,506 --> 01:45:16,175
儿子，你这样做会带来灾难。

774
01:45:16,429 --> 01:45:19,220
爸爸，我们不能当一辈子奴隶！

775
01:45:25,239 --> 01:45:25,933
卡萨夫。
Kasuf.

776
01:45:29,355 --> 01:45:31,357
看看这个所谓的神吧！

777
01:45:39,198 --> 01:45:40,366
好好看清楚！

778
01:46:04,557 --> 01:46:06,517
矿石已经运来了。

779
01:46:09,562 --> 01:46:11,773
把炸弹放到星际之门那里。

780
01:47:14,454 --> 01:47:15,445
上面是怎么回事？
What's happening up there?

781
01:47:41,347 --> 01:47:42,011
你好。
How you doin'?

782
01:47:56,371 --> 01:47:58,091
该死！上，费瑞提！
Damn! Come on, Feretti!

783
01:48:10,077 --> 01:48:10,545
上啊！
Come on!

784
01:48:12,345 --> 01:48:13,227
冲进那扇门！
Get that door!

785
01:48:40,123 --> 01:48:41,665
你们没事吧？有受伤吗？
Hey. You okay? You all right?

786
01:48:49,739 --> 01:48:50,373
大家散开！
Spread out!

787
01:48:58,767 --> 01:48:59,328
我们走！
Let's go!

788
01:49:05,148 --> 01:49:05,693
我们死定了！
We're dead!

789
01:49:05,947 --> 01:49:06,732
别那样说。
Quit talking like that, man.

790
01:49:06,952 --> 01:49:07,915
不然该怎么办？
What are we gonna do?

791
01:49:08,563 --> 01:49:09,078
掩护我。
Cover me.

792
01:49:09,960 --> 01:49:10,603
掩护你？
Cover you?

793
01:49:12,280 --> 01:49:13,302
卡瓦斯基！
Kawalsky!

794
01:49:24,459 --> 01:49:25,169
过来，费瑞提！
Come on, Feretti!

795
01:49:25,169 --> 01:49:26,069
来帮我把这推开！
Help me push this thing over!

796
01:49:38,396 --> 01:49:40,106
现在就把炸弹送到地球去！

797
01:49:40,356 --> 01:49:42,609
我亲自去完成！

798
01:50:01,569 --> 01:50:02,235
你在干什么？
What are you doing?

799
01:50:02,746 --> 01:50:03,653
完成这次任务。
Completing this mission.

800
01:50:05,469 --> 01:50:07,618
我们不是说好了是将门从另一端关闭吗。
I thought we agreed to dismantle the gate on the other side.

801
01:50:07,965 --> 01:50:08,765
那将由你来完成，
And you will.

802
01:50:09,963 --> 01:50:10,809
现在那是你的工作了，
That's your job now.

803
01:50:12,257 --> 01:50:14,353
我要留在这里，摧毁这扇门。
I'm gonna stay here and make sure this goes off.

804
01:50:24,060 --> 01:50:25,084
你还有七分钟的时间。
You got seven minutes.

805
01:50:30,051 --> 01:50:30,515
丹尼尔！
Daniel!

806
01:51:17,909 --> 01:51:18,686
你在干什么？
What are you doing?

807
01:51:21,916 --> 01:51:22,416
杰克逊！
Jackson.

808
01:51:23,375 --> 01:51:24,097
等着我。
Wait for me.

809
01:53:08,224 --> 01:53:10,285
纳贝！
Nabeh!

810
01:53:32,244 --> 01:53:33,881
你还有子弹吗，费瑞提？
You got any rounds at all, Feretti?

811
01:53:33,923 --> 01:53:34,941
已经没有了。
We're all out of ammo!

812
01:53:35,210 --> 01:53:36,005
过来了！
Incoming!

813
01:54:06,241 --> 01:54:07,782
卡瓦斯基，我们得想个办法。
Kawalsky, we gotta do somethin'.

814
01:54:09,953 --> 01:54:10,649
该死。
Damn.

815
01:54:13,456 --> 01:54:15,012
喂！
Hey!

816
01:54:15,375 --> 01:54:17,233
停火！喂！
Stop! Hey!

817
01:55:09,018 --> 01:55:11,062
我不再拥有欢乐。

818
01:55:31,916 --> 01:55:34,294
你们全都要死!

819
01:55:49,617 --> 01:55:52,123
代我向你的国王致敬，混蛋。
Give my regards to king tut, asshole.

820
01:59:11,879 --> 01:59:13,304
我们还剩下多少时间？
How much time do we have left?

821
01:59:13,504 --> 01:59:14,484
45秒。
Forty-five seconds.

822
01:59:14,841 --> 01:59:16,148
他已经逃了，快把这关掉。
He's leaving. Turn it off.

823
01:59:16,592 --> 01:59:18,405
我无法解除设定。
I'm trying to. I can't disarm It.

824
01:59:18,873 --> 01:59:19,400
什么？
What?

825
01:59:19,995 --> 01:59:21,915
我无法停止炸弹，被他们改装了。
I can't stop it. They got it rigged.

826
01:59:37,520 --> 01:59:38,535
- 我想到办法了。 - 我想到办法了。
- I've got an idea. - I've got an idea.

827
02:00:40,927 --> 02:00:42,386
看，我说的吧？
See? Did I Tell Ya?

828
02:01:12,750 --> 02:01:13,205
是的。
Right.

829
02:02:03,408 --> 02:02:05,075
我就知道，你有办法带我们回去。
I always knew you'd get us back.

830
02:02:05,344 --> 02:02:06,185
是的，没错。
Yeah, Right.

831
02:02:06,269 --> 02:02:06,753
后会有期。
Later.

832
02:02:09,448 --> 02:02:10,141
谢了，丹尼尔。
Thanks, Daniel.

833
02:02:19,525 --> 02:02:20,858
你真决定要留下？
You sure you wanna do this?

834
02:02:21,535 --> 02:02:22,583
是的，决定了。
Yes, I'm sure.

835
02:02:24,365 --> 02:02:25,330
你能适应这里吗？
Are you gonna be all right?

836
02:02:29,500 --> 02:02:30,343
我肯定可以的。
I'm gonna be all right.

837
02:02:32,003 --> 02:02:32,619
那你呢？
How about you?

838
02:02:37,543 --> 02:02:37,938
我也会好的，
Yeah.

839
02:02:41,505 --> 02:02:42,576
我想应该会的。
Yeah. I think so.

840
02:02:50,931 --> 02:02:52,297
告诉凯瑟琳，这真的带给了我好运。
Tell Catherine this brought me luck.

841
02:02:58,105 --> 02:02:58,433
我会的。
I will.

842
02:03:04,391 --> 02:03:05,429
后会有期了…
I'll be seeing you around...

843
02:03:08,282 --> 02:03:09,089
杰克逊博士。
Dr. Jackson.

