1
00:10:33,964 --> 00:10:37,134
是贝克派你来的吗？
You're from Baker?

2
00:10:47,686 --> 00:10:50,397
告诉他我把知道的都说出来了
Tell Baker I told him all I know already.

3
00:10:50,481 --> 00:10:54,610
我现在只想安度余年，你懂吗？ 这样折磨我一点用也没有
Tell him I want to live in peace, that it's no use to go on tormenting me.

4
00:10:54,693 --> 00:10:57,613
我对那笔钱的事一点都不知道
I know nothing about that case of coins.

5
00:10:57,696 --> 00:11:03,076
若在钱失踪前他能听我的话 就不会有现在这种事发生
Now that gold has disappeared, but if he'd listened we could have avoided this.

6
00:11:03,160 --> 00:11:06,788
我到军事法庭去查过 根本没有人证
I went to the army court. There were no witnesses.

7
00:11:06,872 --> 00:11:09,124
所以他们什么也查不出来
They couldn't uncover any more.

8
00:11:09,208 --> 00:11:12,085
钱的事我真的一无所知
I can't tell Baker what happened to the money.

9
00:11:12,169 --> 00:11:15,631
请你照着我的话告诉他
Go back and tell him that.

10
00:11:16,715 --> 00:11:20,427
听说有人来看过你
Word's around you had a visitor.

11
00:11:20,511 --> 00:11:23,138
贝克也知道这件事
And Baker knows it.

12
00:11:24,556 --> 00:11:27,059
他的名字叫杰克森
Name of Jackson.

13
00:11:29,728 --> 00:11:31,271

Well?

14
00:11:31,355 --> 00:11:33,815
杰克森到底来过没有
Jackson was here.

15
00:11:35,275 --> 00:11:38,403
还是贝克搞错了
Or Baker's got it all wrong.

16
00:11:45,202 --> 00:11:47,538
他没搞错
He's not wrong.

17
00:11:47,621 --> 00:11:52,376
也许他也想知道 你们所谈论
Maybe Baker would like to know just what you and Jackson had to say...

18
00:11:52,459 --> 00:11:55,587
有关钱箱的事情
about the cash box.

19
00:11:58,340 --> 00:12:01,510
不过他并没有付钱让我查钱箱的事
That's not what I'm being paid for.

20
00:12:05,055 --> 00:12:09,643
所以我只想知道杰克森的化名是什么
I'm only interested in what name Jackson's hiding under now.

21
00:12:12,145 --> 00:12:14,982
为什么你认为杰克森有化名
Why do you think Jackson is assuming another name?

22
00:12:15,065 --> 00:12:18,026
否则我早就找到他了
I would have found him already.

23
00:12:18,110 --> 00:12:21,488
当我开始去找人的时候 就一定能找到他
When I start off to find somebody, I find 'em.

24
00:12:21,571 --> 00:12:24,658
所以他们才愿意花钱雇我
That's why they pay me.

25
00:12:29,121 --> 00:12:31,331
贝克付你多少？
What is Baker paying you?

26
00:12:34,626 --> 00:12:37,754
那是你的家人？
That your family?

27
00:12:45,929 --> 00:12:47,472
是的
Yes.

28
00:12:47,973 --> 00:12:51,059
很幸福的家庭
Nice family.

29
00:12:52,352 --> 00:12:55,355
他付你多少钱来杀我？
What does he pay you for murdering me?

30
00:12:57,858 --> 00:13:02,112
找出杰克森的化名 他付我五百美金
500 dollars, to get the name.

31
00:13:08,368 --> 00:13:10,454
告诉我他的化名
The name.

32
00:13:19,379 --> 00:13:22,090
是卡森，比尔卡森
Carson... Bill Carson.

33
00:13:22,966 --> 00:13:25,719
那就是他现在的化名
That's what he calls himself now.

34
00:13:55,707 --> 00:13:58,627
这里有一千美金
It's a lot of money. One thousand.

35
00:14:02,589 --> 00:14:05,091
一千美金？
A thousand dollars?

36
00:14:06,927 --> 00:14:11,097
居然还有黄金，数目真不小
And some in gold. It's a tidy sum.

37
00:14:14,559 --> 00:14:17,103
可惜当我收了钱后，
But when I'm paid...

38
00:14:17,187 --> 00:14:20,315
就一定会完成任务
I always see the job through.

39
00:15:32,053 --> 00:15:35,473
原来是你 有消息吗？
It's you. Any information?

40
00:15:37,767 --> 00:15:40,437
他说了不少
Too much.

41
00:15:40,520 --> 00:15:43,481
其中有许多你会有兴趣
He said quite a bit that should interest you.

42
00:15:43,565 --> 00:15:46,276
但有一、两件倒引起我的兴趣
And one or two things that interested me.

43
00:15:46,359 --> 00:15:48,528
像什么？
Such as?

44
00:15:48,611 --> 00:15:52,532
杰克森的化名是比尔卡森
The name Jackson's hiding under is Bill Carson.

45
00:15:55,410 --> 00:15:58,413
那是你想知道的
That's your bit.

46
00:15:59,664 --> 00:16:01,750
继续讲
Keep talking.

47
00:16:01,833 --> 00:16:05,712
他还提到钱箱之类的事
He also mentioned something about a certain cash box

48
00:16:05,795 --> 00:16:08,757
一个失踪的钱箱
which just happened to disappear.

49
00:16:08,840 --> 00:16:10,759
这引起我的兴趣
That's my bit.

50
00:16:10,842 --> 00:16:12,969
还有别的吗？
Anything else?

51
00:16:13,053 --> 00:16:15,305
这还不够呀
Not enough for you, eh?

52
00:16:15,388 --> 00:16:19,476
你放心，他不会再讲话了
Well, you don't have to worry. He'll never say anything to anybody again.

53
00:16:20,060 --> 00:16:22,270
喔，干得好
Oh, yeah. Perfect.

54
00:16:22,937 --> 00:16:25,565
这给你
Here... Here you are.

55
00:16:25,648 --> 00:16:29,110
这是付给你的钱，干得不错
Here, this is for you. You did a good job for me.

56
00:16:29,194 --> 00:16:31,696
的确值五百美金
Worth 500 dollars.

57
00:16:33,990 --> 00:16:37,202
哎呀，我几乎忘了
Yeah. I almost forgot.

58
00:16:37,285 --> 00:16:39,746
他付了我一千美金
He gave me a thousand.

59
00:16:39,829 --> 00:16:42,999
想必是想让我杀了你
I think his idea was that I kill you.

60
00:16:49,589 --> 00:16:54,969
问题是，只要我收了钱就一定会完成任务
But you know, the pity is, when I'm paid I always follow my job through.

61
00:16:55,053 --> 00:16:56,846
这点你最清楚
You know that.

62
00:16:56,930 --> 00:16:59,724
不！天使眼…
No! AngeI Eyes!

63
00:17:43,685 --> 00:17:46,020
朋友，别拿枪了
No. No pistoI, amigo.

64
00:17:46,104 --> 00:17:50,275
对你没好处的 我们有三个人
It won't do you any good. There are three of us.

65
00:18:04,455 --> 00:18:06,124
朋友，
Hey, amigo...

66
00:18:06,207 --> 00:18:11,462
你知道你至少值两千美金吗？
You know you got a face beautifuI enough to be worth 2,000 dollars?

67
00:18:13,423 --> 00:18:16,301
没错
Yeah...

68
00:18:16,384 --> 00:18:20,555
但你却不像是能领赏金的人
But you don't look like the one who'll collect it.

69
00:18:27,020 --> 00:18:29,731
向后退几步
A couple of steps back.

70
00:19:23,534 --> 00:19:25,620
谢谢你
Thank you.

71
00:19:34,378 --> 00:19:36,714
你现在值多少？
How much are you worth now?

72
00:19:36,798 --> 00:19:38,800
你说多少？
How much?

73
00:19:39,217 --> 00:19:41,719
当然是两千美金罗
2,000 dollars.

74
00:19:43,387 --> 00:19:45,890
没错，是两千美金
That's right, 2,000 dollars.

75
00:19:45,973 --> 00:19:48,684
两千块
2,000 dollars.

76
00:19:54,315 --> 00:19:58,444
生养你的是个狗杂种 你会付出代价的
!Hijo de puta que te pari? You'll pay for this!

77
00:19:58,528 --> 00:20:01,030
我希望你染上霍乱、狂犬病
I hope you end up in a graveyard,

78
00:20:01,114 --> 00:20:04,117
和瘟疫，最后痛苦的死掉
with the cholera and the rabies and the plague!

79
00:20:04,200 --> 00:20:09,080
放开我，你这个混蛋 让我下来
Cut me loose! Cut me loose, you filthy bastard! Put me down!

80
00:20:09,163 --> 00:20:12,125
我希望你老妈变成廉价妓女
I hope your mother ends up in a two-dollar whorehouse!

81
00:20:12,208 --> 00:20:14,627
放开我！
Cut me loose!

82
00:20:15,670 --> 00:20:20,633
你仍能救你自己 放我走，我会原谅你的
You can still save yourself. Let me go and I'll pardon you.

83
00:20:20,716 --> 00:20:22,802
让我走！
Let me go.

84
00:20:22,885 --> 00:20:27,640
我有点不舒服，血液往上冲…
I feeI sick. The blood is rushing to my...

85
00:20:27,723 --> 00:20:32,645
金发小子，我口渴 给我水
I'm dry, Blondie. Agua... Water...

86
00:20:38,317 --> 00:20:39,944
你这只猪！你是个杂种
You swine!

87
00:20:40,027 --> 00:20:43,489
放我走！
You son of a bitch! Let me go!

88
00:20:43,573 --> 00:20:47,118
欺负双手被绑的人 能叫英雄好汉吗？
You're brave with a man who's tied up. Come back.

89
00:20:47,201 --> 00:20:49,954
回来，我们公平的打一场
Come back and fight.

90
00:20:50,037 --> 00:20:51,914
你这个杂种
You bastard.

91
00:20:52,874 --> 00:20:56,752
怎么搞的，一个混蛋进去另一个混蛋又出来
Who the hell is that? One bastard goes in, another comes out.

92
00:20:56,836 --> 00:21:00,506
- 闭嘴！ - 我是个诚实的农夫
- Cut it out. - I'm an honest farmer.

93
00:21:00,590 --> 00:21:02,884
 我是被冤枉…
I'm innocent of everything.

94
00:21:04,677 --> 00:21:06,721
好，你是个诚实的农夫 
So you're an honest farmer?

95
00:21:06,804 --> 00:21:09,348
认识这个人吗？是我？
You recognise this man?

96
00:21:09,432 --> 00:21:12,310
就是你
Yeah, it's you.

97
00:21:12,393 --> 00:21:16,397
谁说是我，你连字都不认识
Me? Who says so? You can't even read.

98
00:21:16,480 --> 00:21:20,776
卷起来，快卷起来 我还能建议你把它藏到哪里去
Roll it up. I'll give you a good idea where you can put it.

99
00:21:20,860 --> 00:21:24,405
我咒你们这些警长、副警长和生养你们的人全下地狱
To hell with all you sheriffs and all who gave birth to you.

100
00:21:24,488 --> 00:21:27,908
大家快看 他居然给那家伙肮脏钱
Hey, everybody, look! He's giving him the filthy money!

101
00:21:27,992 --> 00:21:33,372
犹大，你出卖我！ 但你享受不了这些肮脏钱
Judas! You sold my hide. But you won't enjoy that money, not a penny.

102
00:21:33,456 --> 00:21:37,543
世上若有公理的话 这些钱应该交给殡仪馆
If there's justice in the world, that money will go to the undertaker.

103
00:21:37,627 --> 00:21:39,503
你知道你是谁吗？
You know who you are?

104
00:21:39,587 --> 00:21:41,964
你知道你是谁的儿子吗？
Want to know whose son you are?

105
00:21:42,048 --> 00:21:44,508
你当然知道，大家都知道
You don't. I do. Everybody does.

106
00:21:44,592 --> 00:21:48,137
你有成千个老爸 而且都和你一样是杂种
You're the son of a thousand fathers, all bastards like you.

107
00:21:48,220 --> 00:21:51,015
还有你老妈…你老妈
And your mother, she's...

108
00:21:51,098 --> 00:21:53,476
她是…你这个混蛋
You bastard!

109
00:21:53,559 --> 00:21:58,189
你老妈…最好别谈她 我从没伤过人
Your mother, it's better not to talk of her! I never hurt anybody!

110
00:21:58,272 --> 00:22:04,362
被本州十四个郡通缉中
Wanted in 14 counties of this state, the condemned is found guilty

111
00:22:04,445 --> 00:22:11,535
这个死刑犯被判谋杀罪 武装抢劫市民、银行和邮局
of the crimes of murder, armed robbery of citizens, state banks and post offices,

112
00:22:11,619 --> 00:22:15,539
偷窃宗教奉献金，在州立监狱纵火
the theft of sacred objects, arson in a state prison,

113
00:22:15,623 --> 00:22:20,419
做伪证、重婚 抛弃发妻和孩子们
perjury, bigamy, deserting his wife and children,

114
00:22:20,503 --> 00:22:23,005
逼女为娼、绑架、敲诈
inciting prostitution, kidnapping,

115
00:22:23,089 --> 00:22:27,593
收赃货、卖赃货
extortion, receiving stolen goods, selling stolen goods,

116
00:22:27,676 --> 00:22:32,765
使用伪钞，并且违反本州法律
passing counterfeit money, and, contrary to the laws of this state,

117
00:22:32,848 --> 00:22:37,311
使用做记号的纸牌 和灌铅的骰子赌博
the condemned is guilty of using marked cards...

118
00:22:37,395 --> 00:22:41,482
所以根据既定的法律
Therefore, according to the powers vested in us,

119
00:22:41,565 --> 00:22:44,568
我们宣判被告
we sentence the accused here before us,

120
00:22:44,652 --> 00:22:48,447
杜可班尼帝多派西非可 黄玛利亚拉美尼斯 Tuco Benedicto Pac韋ico
Tuco Benedicto Pac韋ico Juan-Maria Ramirez...

121
00:22:48,531 --> 00:22:51,659
又名“鼠仔”
Known as "The Rat".

122
00:22:53,410 --> 00:22:55,496
以吊刑处死 
.. to hang by the neck untiI dead.

123
00:22:55,579 --> 00:22:59,125
愿上帝怜悯他的灵魂 开始
May God have mercy on his souI. Proceed.

124
00:23:25,151 --> 00:23:27,194
五百给你，一、二
Five for you.

125
00:23:27,278 --> 00:23:31,448
三、四、五百给我
One, two, three, four... five for me.

126
00:23:33,367 --> 00:23:37,997
五百给你，五百给我
Five for you and five for me.

127
00:23:38,080 --> 00:23:40,416
知道你现在值多少吗？
Know how much you're worth now?

128
00:23:40,499 --> 00:23:43,961
- 多少？ - 三千美金
- No. How much? - 3,000 dollars.

129
00:23:47,798 --> 00:23:50,718
世界上有两种人
There are two kinds of people in the world, my friend:

130
00:23:50,801 --> 00:23:55,306
一种是被吊的人 一种是切断吊索的人
those with a rope around their neck and the people who do the cutting.

131
00:23:55,389 --> 00:24:00,269
你听着，我是被吊的人 是拿着老命去冒险的人
The neck at the end of the rope is mine. I run the risks.

132
00:24:00,352 --> 00:24:04,064
所以下一次我要多分一点
So the next time I want more than half.

133
00:24:04,148 --> 00:24:08,777
你或许在冒险 但我可是切绳子的人
You may run the risks, my friend, but I do the cutting.

134
00:24:09,820 --> 00:24:14,074
如果少分给我的话
If we cut down my percentage...

135
00:24:14,158 --> 00:24:16,410
要雪茄吗？
Cigar?

136
00:24:17,453 --> 00:24:19,872
我的瞄准就不会那么准
.. liable to interfere with my aim.

137
00:24:22,291 --> 00:24:26,003
那就干脆瞄得非常不准
But if you miss, you had better miss very well.

138
00:24:26,086 --> 00:24:30,090
否则谁若害了我 又没把我杀死的话
Whoever double-crosses me and leaves me alive,

139
00:24:30,174 --> 00:24:34,136
那他对杜可的个性 可以说是一点也不了解
he understands nothing about Tuco.

140
00:24:34,219 --> 00:24:36,305
毫无所知
Nothing.

141
00:24:39,433 --> 00:24:41,602
被本州十五个郡通缉中
Wanted in 15 counties of this state,

142
00:24:41,685 --> 00:24:45,397
在我们面前的死刑犯
the condemned standing before us... sitting before us,

143
00:24:45,481 --> 00:24:48,942
杜可班尼帝多派西非可 黄玛利亚拉美尼斯 Tuco Benedicto Pac韋ico
Tuco Benedicto Pac韋ico Juan-Maria Ramirez,

144
00:24:49,026 --> 00:24:53,030
被第三区巡回审判法庭 判决以下罪状
has been found guilty by the circuit court of the following crimes:

145
00:24:53,113 --> 00:24:58,118
谋杀、攻击治安法官 强奸白种处女
murder, assaulting a justice of the peace, raping a virgin of the white race,

146
00:24:58,202 --> 00:25:01,580
强奸未成年黑种女孩
statutory rape of a minor of the black race,

147
00:25:01,664 --> 00:25:03,248
使火车出轨以便抢劫乘客
derailing a train...

148
00:25:03,332 --> 00:25:05,959
抢劫银行、抢劫公路
Hey, AngeI Eyes.

149
00:25:11,840 --> 00:25:15,469
- 你有什么发现？  - 你可是问对人了
- What d'you find out, Shorty? - If you ask me, it seems like a book.

150
00:25:15,552 --> 00:25:19,765
一个武装小组护送一箱金币 遇到北军的埋伏
A unit escorting a cash box of gold coins meets a Yankee ambush

151
00:25:19,848 --> 00:25:24,770
有三个人被救活 史帝芬、贝克和杰克森
and only three of 'em are saved - Stevens, Baker, and Jackson.

152
00:25:24,853 --> 00:25:27,398
可惜钱没有被发现
What wasn't saved was the coins.

153
00:25:27,481 --> 00:25:31,443
后来军方听取杰克森的报告后 就将他无罪释放了
But the army holds a hearing, and Jackson's acquitted.

154
00:25:31,527 --> 00:25:34,363
他失踪后化名为比尔卡森
He disappears and becomes Bill Carson.

155
00:25:34,446 --> 00:25:38,617
- 我知道他的化名 - 但你不知道怎么去找他 只有我知道
- I know his name. - But not who you're looking for. I do.

156
00:25:38,700 --> 00:25:43,497
他如果被找到的话 必定不会有好下场
And when he's found, I'd be scared to be put in his shoes.

157
00:25:44,915 --> 00:25:46,375
卡森在哪里？
Where is Carson?

158
00:25:46,458 --> 00:25:49,670
我只知道他再度从军 而且少了一只眼睛
AII I know is Carson re-enlisted. The poor guy's minus an eye.

159
00:25:49,753 --> 00:25:54,091
他和玛丽亚住在一起 她会告诉你的 她是新来的妓女
He lives with a girI called Maria. She's a fresh young whore in the territory.

160
00:25:54,174 --> 00:25:57,428
- 她在哪里？ - 那个城叫什么来着？
- Where is she? - Now, what's the name of that town?

161
00:25:57,511 --> 00:25:59,304
好像就在附近
Someplace fairly near.

162
00:26:01,723 --> 00:26:03,142
是圣塔安那
Santa Ana.

163
00:26:06,270 --> 00:26:09,398
再见啦 收容，贩卖潜逃奴隶，焚毁…
Adios, half-soldier.

164
00:26:12,943 --> 00:26:15,028
嘿，陆克，给我一杯威士忌
Hey, Luke, hand me down a whiskey.

165
00:26:15,112 --> 00:26:17,364
…以及尚诺奈警长办公室
.. and the sheriff's office in Sonora.

166
00:26:17,447 --> 00:26:20,534
死刑犯曾当蓬车队的向导
He then hired himself out as guide to a wagon train,

167
00:26:20,617 --> 00:26:22,870
在收到报酬后他就逃之夭夭
and, after receiving payment in advance,

168
00:26:22,953 --> 00:26:26,415
把蓬车队留在苏族印地安人的狩猎区
deserted the wagon train on the hunting grounds of the Sioux Indians.

169
00:26:26,498 --> 00:26:30,335
好在他们抓到这个恶棍
I'm glad they got him. A man guilty of all those crimes.

170
00:26:30,419 --> 00:26:35,007
- 有些人虽然被吊但不会死 - 你是什么意思？
- Convicted people don't always hang. - What do you mean?

171
00:26:36,049 --> 00:26:39,178
就算是那种下流的人也都有守护天使
Even a filthy beggar like that has got a protecting angeI.

172
00:26:46,101 --> 00:26:50,022
有一个金发天使在照顾他
A golden-haired angeI watches over him.

173
00:26:50,105 --> 00:26:53,942
以上罪状被告已自动承认
For all these crimes, the accused has made a full confession.

174
00:26:54,026 --> 00:26:57,571
因此我们判决以吊刑处死
Therefore, we condemn him to be hung by the neck untiI dead.

175
00:26:57,654 --> 00:27:00,532
求上帝怜悯他的灵魂 开始！
May the Lord have mercy on his souI. Proceed.

176
00:27:16,048 --> 00:27:19,176
咱们快离开这里
Let's get the hell out of here!

177
00:27:49,623 --> 00:27:52,501
你想说 任何人都有失手的时候吗
What are you trying to say? Anybody can miss a shot?

178
00:27:52,584 --> 00:27:54,628
但在吊我脖子的时候 谁都不准失手
Nobody misses when I'm at the end of the rope.

179
00:27:54,711 --> 00:27:58,090
你没有被吊的经验 让我告诉你
You never had a rope round your neck. Let me tell you something.

180
00:27:58,173 --> 00:28:03,470
当吊索收紧的那一刻 真有到了鬼门关的感觉
When that rope starts to pull tight, you can feeI the deviI bite your ass.

181
00:28:05,389 --> 00:28:07,557
你说的不错，
Yeah. You're right.

182
00:28:07,641 --> 00:28:10,310
是越来越难了
It's getting tougher.

183
00:28:10,894 --> 00:28:16,983
我想你这小矮子 将来也没什么前途
The way I figure, there's really not too much future with a sawn-off runt like you.

184
00:28:17,067 --> 00:28:18,360
这是什么意思？
What do you mean?

185
00:28:18,443 --> 00:28:22,364
我不认为你的身价会超过三千美金
I don't think you'll ever be worth more than 3,000 dollars.

186
00:28:23,198 --> 00:28:25,409
你到底在说什么？
What do you mean?

187
00:28:25,492 --> 00:28:28,328
我说咱们的合伙关系到此为止
I mean our partnership is untied.

188
00:28:29,413 --> 00:28:31,415
对不起，
Oh, no, not you.

189
00:28:31,498 --> 00:28:33,291
你的手仍要绑住
You remain tied.

190
00:28:33,375 --> 00:28:36,378
钱我留下来 绳索就留给你吧
I'll keep the money and you can have the rope.

191
00:28:36,461 --> 00:28:40,590
你这个下流无耻的混蛋 又脏又臭…
You filthy, double-crossing bastard. Of all the stinking, dirty tricks...

192
00:28:40,674 --> 00:28:43,677
回城去是七十哩
The way back to town is only 70 miles.

193
00:28:44,761 --> 00:28:47,973
如果省省力气 相信你一定能办得到
If you save your breath, I feeI a man like you could manage it.

194
00:28:48,598 --> 00:28:49,808
再见啦
Adios.

195
00:28:49,891 --> 00:28:53,103
你这个王八蛋，回来！
You filthy bastard! Come here!

196
00:28:53,520 --> 00:28:58,567
你回来，把绳索剪掉 下马呀，无耻的家伙
Come here. Cut this rope off. Get off that horse, you filthy coward.

197
00:28:58,650 --> 00:29:01,903
如果让我再碰到你 一定会吃你的心挖你的肺
If I ever catch you, Blondie, I'll rip your heart out and eat it!

198
00:29:01,987 --> 00:29:06,992
剥你的头皮，把你生切活剥 吊你的大姆指 你是蠢猪！贪心鬼
I'll skin you alive! I'll hang you up by your thumbs! You pig! You vulture!

199
00:29:07,075 --> 00:29:09,619
我会杀了你
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!

200
00:29:11,663 --> 00:29:16,042
在救过你那么多次之后 你居然还这么忘恩负义
Such ingratitude. After all the times I've saved your life.

201
00:29:20,881 --> 00:29:23,717
你到哪去？等一等 这是开玩笑吧 
Wait a minute. This is only a trick.

202
00:29:23,800 --> 00:29:26,761
你不会把我留在这里
You wouldn't leave me here. Come back.

203
00:29:26,845 --> 00:29:30,682
回来呀！等等，金发小子 你听我说…
Wait, Blondie! Listen...

204
00:29:30,765 --> 00:29:34,186
你这个狗养的杂种
!Hijo de una gran puta!

205
00:29:54,873 --> 00:29:58,084
相信女士的家到了
I believe madam is home.

206
00:29:58,168 --> 00:30:00,253
做个甜蜜的梦 第七骑兵队谢谢你的服务
Sweet dreams.

207
00:30:11,139 --> 00:30:13,850
你们这些无耻之徒
You filthy rats!

208
00:30:29,324 --> 00:30:31,785
玛丽亚！
Maria?

209
00:30:37,874 --> 00:30:40,961
甜心！  比尔，是你吗？
Is that you, Bill?

210
00:30:41,044 --> 00:30:42,963
比尔！
Bill!

211
00:30:44,130 --> 00:30:45,924

Arh!

212
00:30:52,097 --> 00:30:53,974
你是谁？
Who are you?

213
00:30:54,057 --> 00:30:56,017
你想干什么
What do you want with me?

214
00:30:56,101 --> 00:30:59,437
和你谈谈比尔卡森的事
Go on talking about Bill Carson.

215
00:30:59,521 --> 00:31:02,232
我不认识他
I don't know him.

216
00:31:02,315 --> 00:31:05,568
你在黑暗中还叫着他的名字
You were calling to him in the dark.

217
00:31:09,406 --> 00:31:10,532
他在哪儿？
Where is he?

218
00:31:10,615 --> 00:31:12,951
你想对他怎样？
What are you gonna do to him?

219
00:31:14,327 --> 00:31:16,538
是我在问你问题
I'll ask the questions.

220
00:31:18,331 --> 00:31:20,750
他在哪儿？
Where is he?

221
00:31:27,507 --> 00:31:29,384
他到底藏在哪里？
Where is he? Where?

222
00:31:29,467 --> 00:31:32,178

Where? Where?

223
00:31:32,262 --> 00:31:34,556

Where?

224
00:31:37,350 --> 00:31:39,436
够啦！
That's enough.

225
00:31:40,687 --> 00:31:43,982
我不知道他在哪里
I don't know where he is. He packed his things ten days ago

226
00:31:44,065 --> 00:31:47,402
十天前 他就和他的单位一起走了
and went away with his unit. They all left.

227
00:31:47,485 --> 00:31:49,654
是哪个连？到哪里去？
Which company? Where did they go?

228
00:31:52,407 --> 00:31:53,700

Hm?

229
00:31:53,783 --> 00:31:58,705
是席伯利将军属下的 第三骑兵队，他们去圣塔菲
3rd Cavalry. GeneraI Sibley. They left for Santa Fe.

230
00:31:59,789 --> 00:32:03,001
我发誓我只知道这么多
That's all I know. I swear.

231
00:33:28,419 --> 00:33:30,505
但是…
But... but...

232
00:33:34,634 --> 00:33:37,345
对不起，我已经打烊了
I'm very sorry, but the store is closing.

233
00:33:37,428 --> 00:33:39,097

Mm-hm.

234
00:34:15,633 --> 00:34:19,429
- 左轮手枪  - 是左轮手枪
- Revolvers! - Yeah, revolvers.

235
00:34:23,057 --> 00:34:24,934
给我看左轮手枪
Revolvers.

236
00:34:25,018 --> 00:34:29,272
这里的都是最好的
Well, here's where I keep the best ones.

237
00:34:33,401 --> 00:34:36,696
什么牌子都有 林明敦、科尔特
Here, Remington, Colt,

238
00:34:36,779 --> 00:34:39,574
鲁特、史密斯威森
a Root, Smith-Wesson,

239
00:34:39,657 --> 00:34:43,953
科尔特、奈威 约瑟林
Colt - navy, Joslyn,

240
00:34:44,036 --> 00:34:46,247
另一种林明敦
another Remington, and this one...

241
00:34:46,330 --> 00:34:47,790
够啦
That's enough.

242
00:35:31,125 --> 00:35:33,461
给我子弹
Cartridges.

243
00:35:41,260 --> 00:35:45,515
- 要试枪的话，外面有靶子 - 我们走
- You wanna try the pistoI, step out back. - Let's go.

244
00:35:50,561 --> 00:35:52,647
快走
Move, move.

245
00:37:07,471 --> 00:37:09,557
子弹
Cartridge.

246
00:37:17,440 --> 00:37:20,568
- 多少钱？   - 二十美金
- How much? - Twenty dollars.

247
00:37:21,610 --> 00:37:24,655
不对吧
No.

248
00:37:27,324 --> 00:37:30,411
五十块
Fifty dollars.

249
00:37:30,494 --> 00:37:34,957
- 多少？ - 一百块
- How much? - A hundred dollars.

250
00:37:37,084 --> 00:37:41,172
两百块，我只有这么多
Two hundred dollars. It's all I've got.

251
00:37:41,255 --> 00:37:43,340
都在这里
Here.

252
00:38:02,318 --> 00:38:04,820
你过来
Come here.

253
00:38:10,910 --> 00:38:12,578

- Aaah.. - Ahh...

254
00:38:14,997 --> 00:38:18,334

- Heh? - Mm-hm.

255
00:38:22,922 --> 00:38:28,135
既然为活命而工作为什么又为工作卖命？
If you work for a living, why do you kill yourself working?

256
00:39:05,464 --> 00:39:11,762
既然为活命而工作为什么又为工作卖命？
If you work for a living, why do you kill yourself working?

257
00:39:38,205 --> 00:39:40,291
薯仔
Potatoes.

258
00:39:41,000 --> 00:39:44,295
吃薯仔的一定是个穷鬼
You've gotta be poor to eat potatoes.

259
00:39:45,212 --> 00:39:47,339
穷到死
Really poor.

260
00:39:47,423 --> 00:39:50,968
我很有钱，但很寂寞
I'm rich. But I'm lonely.

261
00:39:53,220 --> 00:39:56,098
世上的人可以分成两大类…
The world is divided into two parts:

262
00:39:56,181 --> 00:40:02,187
一种人有朋友 另一种人很寂寞 比如可怜的图可
those who have friends, and those who are lonely, like poor Tuco.

263
00:40:03,814 --> 00:40:08,694
我以前有个朋友--佩德罗
You see, I used to have a friend - Pedro.

264
00:40:09,611 --> 00:40:13,198
他的两个兄弟 奇哥和拉蒙也是我的朋友 Chico and Ram髇, his two brothers,
Chico and Ram髇, his two brothers, were my friends too.

265
00:40:16,660 --> 00:40:19,955
但是天知道他们现在在哪里？
But who knows where they are now?

266
00:40:20,706 --> 00:40:24,501
真不幸，朋友 没能够找到你们
Ah, it's too bad, friends. Tough luck I haven't found you.

267
00:40:24,585 --> 00:40:26,879
我有一桩好买卖
I had a good deaI for you.

268
00:40:29,131 --> 00:40:33,093
有个混账家伙身上有4千元
There's a big son of a bitch who's got 4,000 dollars.

269
00:40:34,011 --> 00:40:39,516
4千 我知道哪里可以找到他
4,000 dollars. And I know where to find it.

270
00:40:41,935 --> 00:40:47,316
如果他们帮我追到他 我愿意把钱分成四份 大家情同手足
If they would help me catch him, I'd divide it four ways, like a brother.

271
00:40:47,900 --> 00:40:51,111
每个人1千元
1,000 dollars each. Hm?

272
00:41:08,337 --> 00:41:11,423
你还活着，图可，是真的吗？
You're alive, Tuco. Is it true?

273
00:41:14,218 --> 00:41:16,762
他很有钱，你们也快发财了
And rich. Like you're going to be.

274
00:41:16,845 --> 00:41:19,765
大家说你在阿布奎基被杀了
But people are saying you got killed in Albuquerque.

275
00:41:19,848 --> 00:41:22,101
他们胡说八道
And people talk bullshit.

276
00:41:25,813 --> 00:41:29,149
我活得好好的，混蛋 将来也是一样
I'm alive, you bastards, and I always will be.

277
00:41:29,233 --> 00:41:32,569
我来奉献3千元给你们
And I've come to give you 3,000 dollars.

278
00:41:32,653 --> 00:41:34,738
我们走
Vamos.

279
00:41:50,921 --> 00:41:53,048
今早我听出个所以然来
This morning I heard the whole thing.

280
00:41:53,131 --> 00:41:58,303
据他们说 北军的坎比上校正在接近中 最迟明天就会到这里
Canby's closing in with his northerners and tomorrow they'll be in the city.

281
00:41:58,387 --> 00:42:01,098
所以南军才会走
That's why these southerners are getting out.

282
00:42:01,181 --> 00:42:04,643
你看一听到北军 南军就落荒而逃
As soon as these cowards hear of blue-shirts around, they run.

283
00:42:05,686 --> 00:42:08,605
- 这些叛军根本不想打仗  - 真可怜
- These rebels have no will to fight. - Poor things.

284
00:42:08,689 --> 00:42:13,986
他们迟早会被消灭 把这些穷鬼送走马上就可以在北佬身上发财了
They'll soon be finished. Then we begin making money on those Yankees.

285
00:42:14,069 --> 00:42:16,446
他们身上只带金子 
They carry gold, not paper dollars.

286
00:42:16,530 --> 00:42:19,408
一定能击败南军
And they're going to beat the South.

287
00:42:19,491 --> 00:42:24,705
你看坐在蓬车中白胡子的那位 他是席伯利将军 看来就快死了
Look. See that one with the white beard, GeneraI Sibley? He looks dead.

288
00:42:24,788 --> 00:42:26,790
他终于滚了，南军加油！
He's finally getting out of our hair.

289
00:42:26,873 --> 00:42:31,753
南军加油！
Hooray for Dixie! Hooray, hooray for Dixie!

290
00:42:35,465 --> 00:42:38,552
那匹马的主人在哪里？
Where's the owner of that horse?

291
00:42:38,635 --> 00:42:41,805
- 先生，我心脏有毛病 - 他在哪儿？
- Please, mister... A bad heart... - Where?

292
00:42:41,888 --> 00:42:46,893
- 战争已经快把我吓死了 - 我在找那匹马的主人
- The war's frightened me already. - I'm looking for the owner of that horse.

293
00:42:46,977 --> 00:42:52,065
他蛮高的、金发、抽雪茄 还是只猪，他在哪儿？
He's tall, blond, he smokes a cigar and he's a pig. Where is he now?

294
00:42:52,149 --> 00:42:55,027
别吓他，他不知道马主是谁
He doesn't know who rides every horse.

295
00:42:55,110 --> 00:42:58,697
老母鸡，你少管闲事
You stay quiet, old hen.

296
00:42:58,780 --> 00:43:02,951
楼上，二楼四号房 Upstairs in room four, se駉r.
Upstairs in room four, se駉r.

297
00:43:08,040 --> 00:43:10,334
你们听到了吧
Hear that?

298
00:43:14,963 --> 00:43:18,967
你们这些不要脸的罪犯 怎么可以…
You rotten criminals. How dare you?

299
00:46:32,619 --> 00:46:35,205
要怪得怪你的马刺
Your spurs.

300
00:46:49,386 --> 00:46:52,222
老友，有两种马刺
There are two kinds of spurs, my friend:

301
00:46:52,305 --> 00:46:57,769
一种从房门进来 另一种从窗户进来
those that come in by the door, and those that come in by the window.

302
00:46:57,852 --> 00:47:00,980
把枪带拿下来
Take off that pistoI belt.

303
00:47:07,445 --> 00:47:08,905
那是空枪
It's empty.

304
00:47:11,533 --> 00:47:14,828
我的枪可是满满的
Mine isn't.

305
00:47:19,791 --> 00:47:23,586
犹大要上吊时 连天公都会打雷
Even when Judas hanged himself, there was a storm, too.

306
00:47:26,923 --> 00:47:29,300
那好像是大炮
That could be cannon fire.

307
00:47:29,384 --> 00:47:33,930
大炮和雷对你来说都一样
Cannon fire or storm, it's all the same to you.

308
00:47:35,431 --> 00:47:39,352
你应该见过它吧
You ever see this before, my friend?

309
00:47:47,318 --> 00:47:50,989
把它穿过横梁
Throw it over the roof beam.

310
00:47:51,656 --> 00:47:53,116
就是那条
That's it.

311
00:48:04,794 --> 00:48:06,880
你上去
Now get on that.

312
00:48:16,723 --> 00:48:18,600
就是这样
That's right.

313
00:48:18,683 --> 00:48:21,185
把绳索绑紧
Now make sure the rope is tight.

314
00:48:21,269 --> 00:48:24,397
让它能吊住一只蠢猪
It's got to hold the weight of a pig.

315
00:48:30,695 --> 00:48:34,198
把绳索套在你脖子上
Now put the rope around your neck.

316
00:48:40,038 --> 00:48:42,874
很好
That's very good.

317
00:48:42,957 --> 00:48:46,794
套索好像太大了 我马上去修改它
It's too big for your neck, huh? We fix that right away.

318
00:48:46,878 --> 00:48:51,132
其实我有我的方法 但是和你的有点不同
I have another system. A little different than yours.

319
00:48:52,050 --> 00:48:56,262
我不射绳子，只射凳子腿
I don't shoot the rope, I shoot the legs off the stooI.

320
00:49:00,808 --> 00:49:02,894
再见啦 Adi髎.
Adi髎.

321
00:52:12,375 --> 00:52:14,043
欢迎光临，朋友
Welcome, my friend.

322
00:52:14,126 --> 00:52:17,630
如果你在找夏季渡假中心 这就是你所找的地方
If you're looking for a summer vacation spot, you've found it.

323
00:52:17,713 --> 00:52:21,217
本饭店设备豪华，很是方便
Our hoteI is luxurious and filled with conveniences.

324
00:52:23,260 --> 00:52:25,388
迷人的地方还不只这些
And the attractions don't stop there.

325
00:52:25,471 --> 00:52:29,684
有各国美食 健康又营养的食物
InternationaI cuisine, healthfuI and nutritious food.

326
00:52:29,767 --> 00:52:31,852
南方风味的粟米棒
Corn cobs, Dixie-style.

327
00:52:31,936 --> 00:52:34,438
我们政府预算宽松
Our government has spared no expense.

328
00:52:34,522 --> 00:52:37,400
我们受到极佳的待遇
As you can see, we are treated very well.

329
00:52:37,483 --> 00:52:41,070
你听说过一个叫比尔卡森的人吗？
Have you ever heard of anyone by the name of Bill Carson?

330
00:52:41,153 --> 00:52:46,325
你听过一个叫甘比的人吗？没听过？
And you? Have you ever heard of someone named Canby? No?

331
00:52:46,409 --> 00:52:50,746
他是北方军的一个上校一心想将我们碎尸万段
Well, you see, he's a Yankee coloneI who decided to tear us to pieces.

332
00:52:50,830 --> 00:52:53,916
我们唯一关心的是如何保住这条命
The only thing we care about is saving our own hides.

333
00:52:53,999 --> 00:52:56,919
你却来向我打听一个人
And you ask me if I know someone.

334
00:52:57,002 --> 00:53:01,173
搞不懂你们这些流浪汉在想什么
I just don't know what you drifters could be thinking.

335
00:53:11,934 --> 00:53:16,105
卡森戴着一只眼罩原本属第三骑兵师
Carson has a patch over one eye. He's with the 3rd.

336
00:53:17,857 --> 00:53:21,902
如果是第三师的
If he's with the 3rd... They've already left.

337
00:53:21,986 --> 00:53:23,612
他们已经去葛罗耶塔了
For Glorietta.

338
00:53:23,696 --> 00:53:27,908
甘比的前锋部队已经追上他们了，可怜的年轻人
Canby's front line is right on their heels. Those poor young devils.

339
00:53:27,992 --> 00:53:33,914
前方是一片沙漠 我怀疑有没有人活得了
And the desert lies ahead of 'em. I really doubt that any of them are still alive.

340
00:53:33,998 --> 00:53:36,542
如果仍活着呢？
And what if they were still alive?

341
00:53:38,878 --> 00:53:41,130
更惨
Worse.

342
00:53:41,213 --> 00:53:44,884
你一定没听过贝特维尔
Well, then, you must not have heard anything about Batterville.

343
00:53:44,967 --> 00:53:50,848
北方佬的战俘营之一 你最好不要被关进去
It's one of those Yankee prison camps you'd better hope you never end up in.

344
00:53:50,931 --> 00:53:53,434
留着吧，送给你
Keep it. It's yours.

345
00:56:18,203 --> 00:56:22,249
我们判决被告汤姆斯来森 绰号矮子来森
We have found the accused, Thomas Larson, alias Shorty Larson,

346
00:56:22,332 --> 00:56:24,918
犯有以下罪状
guilty of the following crimes:

347
00:56:25,002 --> 00:56:29,590
偷马、偷窃北军的补给 偷窃南军的补给
horse-theft, theft of supplies belonging to the Union army...

348
00:56:44,021 --> 00:56:45,856
矮子怎么办？
And Shorty?

349
00:56:50,611 --> 00:56:51,778
我们判汤姆斯来森
No.

350
00:56:52,988 --> 00:56:55,616

No?

351
00:56:55,908 --> 00:56:59,661
绰号矮子来森以吊刑处死
.. alias Shorty Larson, to hang by the neck untiI dead.

352
00:56:59,745 --> 00:57:03,040
愿上帝怜悯他的灵魂 开始
May God have mercy on his souI. Proceed.

353
00:57:09,546 --> 00:57:11,215
抱歉啦，矮子
Sorry, Shorty.

354
00:57:12,633 --> 00:57:15,344
走，快点，我们走
Move. Come on, let's go.

355
00:57:39,952 --> 00:57:42,996
真奇怪 每次一到沙漠，我就口渴
I don't know... As soon as I hit the desert, I'm thirsty.

356
00:57:43,080 --> 00:57:48,961
皮肤灼伤了吗？一般来说 浅色皮肤的人容易灼伤
It burns, huh? They say people with fair skin can't take too much.

357
00:58:12,317 --> 00:58:16,154
我在替你减轻重量嘛
Like that, you won't have to carry so much.

358
00:58:17,155 --> 00:58:19,533
我们到哪去？
Where are we going?

359
00:58:19,616 --> 00:58:21,118

Where?

360
00:58:21,201 --> 00:58:23,662
去我要去的地方
Where I'm going, amigo.

361
00:58:23,745 --> 00:58:25,539
就是那边
Over that way.

362
00:58:25,622 --> 00:58:29,459
另一个一百哩 又美丽又干热的沙漠
Another 100 miles of beautifuI sun-baked sand.

363
00:58:29,543 --> 00:58:32,212
就连军队也不敢走
Even the armies are afraid to march through there.

364
00:58:32,295 --> 00:58:34,881
南方军队正在撤退
Sibley's men are retreating up there.

365
00:58:34,965 --> 00:58:38,135
北方军队马上就要进来
Canby's men are coming here.

366
00:58:38,218 --> 00:58:42,180
但没人会到这个鬼地方来
But no-one will set foot in this hell.

367
00:58:42,264 --> 00:58:44,975
除了你和我
Except you and me.

368
00:58:46,143 --> 00:58:49,521
一百哩够你走的
100 miles. That's a nice walk.

369
00:58:52,065 --> 00:58:55,527
上次你是怎么对我说的
What was it you told me the last time?

370
00:58:56,778 --> 00:59:01,575
“如果省省力气 相信你一定能办得到”
If you save your breath, I feeI a man like you could manage it.

371
00:59:02,743 --> 00:59:07,205
如果办不到的话 老友，你就会死
And if you won't manage it, you'll die - only slowly.

372
00:59:08,415 --> 00:59:11,918
而且会死得很慢，非常的慢
Very slowly, old friend.

373
00:59:15,964 --> 00:59:17,758
请你先走吧
After you, please.

374
00:59:17,841 --> 00:59:19,926

Start walking.

375
01:01:15,500 --> 01:01:17,836
想休息吗？
Taking a rest?

376
01:01:18,295 --> 01:01:22,674
金发小子，快点，没多远了 只剩七十哩而已
Come on, Blondie. We don't have very far to go. Only 70 miles.

377
01:01:23,925 --> 01:01:27,721
还有八个半钟头 太阳就要下山了
Only eight and a half hours more before sunset.

378
01:01:27,804 --> 01:01:30,348
不算太坏嘛
That's not too bad.

379
01:01:31,391 --> 01:01:32,726
走呀
Come on.

380
01:02:16,728 --> 01:02:18,605

Whoa...

381
01:03:23,336 --> 01:03:25,838
好吧，吃点东西
OK, let's eat.

382
01:03:25,922 --> 01:03:29,676
我的意思是，我吃
That is, I'll eat.

383
01:03:31,427 --> 01:03:35,682
你可以享受一下日光浴
Meanwhile, you can enjoy a sunbath.

384
01:03:43,606 --> 01:03:46,150
要喝水吗？
You want some water?

385
01:03:49,904 --> 01:03:51,656
喝啊，喝啊
Drink.

386
01:03:57,662 --> 01:03:59,872
来啊，加油
Come on.

387
01:04:40,872 --> 01:04:44,250
金毛小子，拜拜啦
Well, Blondie... So long.

388
01:05:51,025 --> 01:05:53,945
金发小子，看来…
And so, Blondie...

389
01:05:55,571 --> 01:05:58,074
咱们得说再见了
it's goodbye.

390
01:06:53,921 --> 01:06:56,173
停，停下来
Whoa, whoa...

391
01:07:00,970 --> 01:07:02,597
好了
Easy, easy.

392
01:07:02,680 --> 01:07:05,433
不要紧张，好马儿！
Easy. Attaboy.

393
01:09:34,415 --> 01:09:36,500
水，给我水
Water...

394
01:09:43,841 --> 01:09:48,846
给我水，二十万金币就是你的
200,000 in gold. It's yours, just get me water.

395
01:09:52,683 --> 01:09:54,727
你在说什么？
What's that you say?

396
01:09:54,810 --> 01:09:58,564
- 你是谁？ - 卡森
- Who the hell are you? - Carson.

397
01:09:58,647 --> 01:10:02,067
我现在叫比尔卡森
My name is Bill Carson now.

398
01:10:02,151 --> 01:10:04,904
遇到意外的攻击
Surprise attack...

399
01:10:04,987 --> 01:10:09,533
全军覆灭 我的真名是杰克森，不是卡森
All dead... My name is Jackson, not Carson...

400
01:10:09,617 --> 01:10:13,037
是的，卡森，很高兴遇到你 我是林肯的祖父
Carson, yeah. Glad to meet you. I'm Lincoln's grandfather.

401
01:10:13,120 --> 01:10:18,834
- 你刚刚说到钱是怎么回事 - 二十万全是我的
- What's that you said about the dollars? - 200,000, all mine.

402
01:10:18,917 --> 01:10:21,920
本来属于第三骑兵队的
It was the 3rd Cavalry's.

403
01:10:22,004 --> 01:10:24,882
贝克什么也没有
Baker has nothing.

404
01:10:24,965 --> 01:10:28,761
我把金币藏起来，藏得很隐密
The gold... I hid the gold. The gold is safe.

405
01:10:29,970 --> 01:10:32,890
在哪里？在这里吗？
Where? Here?

406
01:10:32,973 --> 01:10:37,061
- 你说话呀，是不是这里 - 在公墓里
- Talk. - In... the... cemetery.

407
01:10:37,144 --> 01:10:38,854
哪一个公墓
Which cemetery?

408
01:10:38,937 --> 01:10:42,608
伤心坡的公墓里
The one on Sad Hill.

409
01:10:42,691 --> 01:10:44,943
墓名是…
There's a grave...

410
01:10:45,027 --> 01:10:48,072
是哪个坟墓？
Which grave? Have a name?

411
01:10:48,155 --> 01:10:52,951
有名字吗？有号码吗？快点，笨蛋，快讲呀
Have a number? Come on, you dummy, talk.

412
01:10:53,035 --> 01:10:56,080
没有号码，只有名字
There's... no number.

413
01:10:56,163 --> 01:10:58,707
名字是…
There's a name.

414
01:10:58,791 --> 01:11:01,293
是什么？
It's written...

415
01:11:07,674 --> 01:11:10,594
水！
Water...

416
01:11:11,637 --> 01:11:14,515
你先说，我等会儿给你水喝
You talk first. I'll give you water later.

417
01:11:14,598 --> 01:11:17,726
在伤心坡的一个坟墓里
Sad Hill cemetery. OK. In the grave. OK.

418
01:11:17,810 --> 01:11:23,899
但应该有名字或是号码吧 那里的坟至少也有五千个
But it must have a name or a number. There must be 1,000... 5,000...

419
01:11:27,403 --> 01:11:31,448
别死，你别死，我去拿水
Don't die, uh? Don't die. I'll get you water.

420
01:11:31,532 --> 01:11:35,244
你待在这里别动，我去拿水
Stay there. Don't move. I'll get you water.

421
01:11:35,327 --> 01:11:38,288
等告诉我名字后再死
Don't die untiI later, you son of a...

422
01:12:03,355 --> 01:12:06,483
你滚开
Get away from there.

423
01:12:11,029 --> 01:12:13,198
他死了
He's dead.

424
01:12:16,493 --> 01:12:18,996
我会杀了你
I'll kill you.

425
01:12:20,956 --> 01:12:24,877
杀了我，你会穷一辈子
If you do that, you'll always be poor.

426
01:12:24,960 --> 01:12:28,088
就像现在一样
Just like the greasy rat that you are.

427
01:12:28,630 --> 01:12:32,885
若换成我的话 一定会千方百计的让我活下去
If I were you, I'd... keep me alive.

428
01:12:32,968 --> 01:12:36,096
他告诉你什么？
What did he tell you?

429
01:12:36,180 --> 01:12:38,557
一个名字
A name.

430
01:12:38,640 --> 01:12:42,936
- 一个坟墓的名字 - 什么名字？
- The name on a grave. - What name?

431
01:12:56,325 --> 01:12:58,410
你别死呀
Blondie... Don't die.

432
01:12:58,493 --> 01:13:00,579
金发小子，你千万别死 
Blondie, don't die.

433
01:13:00,662 --> 01:13:03,373
我是你的朋友
I'm your friend. Please don't die.

434
01:13:03,457 --> 01:13:06,001
求求你别死，我是你的朋友
I'm your friend. Come on.

435
01:13:06,084 --> 01:13:07,669
别这样
Come on, eh?

436
01:13:07,753 --> 01:13:11,214
我会帮你的，
Blondie, I'll help you. I'll help you.

437
01:13:11,298 --> 01:13:14,259
你别动 我马上就回来
Don't move. I'll be right back. I'll get the water.

438
01:13:14,343 --> 01:13:18,221
水在这里，别死呀
Don't die like that pig.

439
01:13:18,305 --> 01:13:20,390
喂，水来啦，水在这里
Here's water, Blondie.

440
01:13:20,474 --> 01:13:24,102
先别喝，这样对身体不好 好点了吗？
Don't drink, it's no good for you. FeeI better?

441
01:13:24,186 --> 01:13:28,398
你怎么搞的，你一定要活下去
Blondie, what's the matter? Please don't die.

442
01:13:36,698 --> 01:13:40,118
嘿，开门，开门！快
Hey, open up! Hurry!

443
01:13:40,202 --> 01:13:43,330
别慌，别慌，是谁？
Settle down. Who's there?

444
01:13:44,665 --> 01:13:49,044
什么意思？你以为我是敌人？
What do you mean, "who's there?" You think I'm the enemy?

445
01:13:51,254 --> 01:13:55,217
如果我是北方佬 你连问的时间都没有
If I were a Yankee, you wouldn't have time to ask me that.

446
01:13:55,300 --> 01:13:56,551
别叼难
Come on.

447
01:13:56,635 --> 01:14:00,180
中士，先听这位下士怎么说
Sergeant, listen to this corporaI for a moment.

448
01:14:00,263 --> 01:14:06,103
中士，这里有位弟兄身受重伤 希望他还没有断气
Sergeant, I have a gravely wounded man here, if he's not dead already.

449
01:14:07,521 --> 01:14:11,566
- 他还活着吗？ - 好像还活着
- He's still alive? - Well, he seems to be.

450
01:14:11,650 --> 01:14:13,694
-发生了什么事？ -中了圈套
- What happened? - It was a trap.

451
01:14:13,777 --> 01:14:18,615
- 只有我们两个得以逃脱 - 姓名和差旅证件
- Only the two of us got away. - Name and travelling papers.

452
01:14:19,741 --> 01:14:23,787
在这，比尔卡森下士 第三团，第二骑兵队
Here. CorporaI Bill Carson. 3rd Regiment, 2nd Cavalry Squadron,

453
01:14:23,870 --> 01:14:27,582
从圣拉菲尔过来，清楚了吧？
arriving from San RafaeI. Is that enough?

454
01:14:32,212 --> 01:14:34,673
在你看的时候，他就要死了
Are you reading when this man is dying?

455
01:14:34,756 --> 01:14:38,552
下士，我们下在撤退 而你需要的是医务室？
Why, CorporaI, we're trying to withdraw and you're looking for an infirmary?

456
01:14:38,635 --> 01:14:42,764
想就医的话 只能去当北方佬的战俘
If you want one, you'll have to make yourself a Yankee prisoner.

457
01:14:43,432 --> 01:14:47,018
- 这里是哪里？ - 接近阿帕拉契峡谷
- So where are we? - Near Apache Canyon.

458
01:14:48,353 --> 01:14:50,814
- 阿帕拉契峡谷？ - 阿帕拉契峡谷
Apache Canyon?

459
01:14:50,897 --> 01:14:53,400
圣安东尼奥医疗队在附近吗？
Is a mission San Antonio around here?

460
01:14:53,483 --> 01:14:55,652
南方18里处，带他去那里
18 miles south. Take him there.

461
01:14:55,735 --> 01:14:59,406
那儿的弟兄只要是伤者都照顾
The brothers take care of any wounded, whatever the colour of his uniform.

462
01:14:59,489 --> 01:15:02,492
小心点，那一区很多北方佬
And keep your eyes open - the area is full of Yankees.

463
01:15:02,576 --> 01:15:04,161
多谢，再见，中士
Thank you. Goodbye, Sergeant.

464
01:15:04,244 --> 01:15:06,246
保重
Take care.

465
01:15:24,931 --> 01:15:27,017

Whoa!

466
01:15:30,061 --> 01:15:33,315
- 我的同伴病得很重 - 但我们已经没有床位了
- Got a very sick man here. - But we have no more beds.

467
01:15:33,398 --> 01:15:35,901
那就把你的让出来吧
Let him have yours.

468
01:15:40,822 --> 01:15:44,951
- 巴布罗拉美尼斯在哪里？ - 拉美尼斯神父 他暂时离开一下
- Where's Padre Ramirez? - Father Ramirez is away at the moment.

469
01:15:45,035 --> 01:15:47,454
随时都会回来
He should be back any day now.

470
01:15:47,537 --> 01:15:51,708
没关系，我们反正要好好的照顾我这个朋友
It doesn't matter. For the moment, we take very good care of my friend.

471
01:15:51,791 --> 01:15:53,627
感谢主
And may God be praised.

472
01:15:53,710 --> 01:15:59,299
上帝是站在我们这边的 因为他不喜欢北方佬 对不对，金发小子
God is on our side too, because he hates the Yankees. Huh, Blondie?

473
01:16:00,675 --> 01:16:04,638
- 神父，他还在呼吸吗？ - 当然
- Father, is he still breathing? - Yes, of course.

474
01:16:04,721 --> 01:16:06,806
你可真重
You're heavy.

475
01:16:17,609 --> 01:16:19,694
在里面
There.

476
01:16:48,431 --> 01:16:51,559
给他换个新的绷带
All right. Put a fresh bandage on him.

477
01:16:52,519 --> 01:16:55,313
把他放在我的房间里
Put him in my cell.

478
01:16:55,397 --> 01:16:57,482
小心点
Easy.

479
01:16:59,859 --> 01:17:02,195
出去，你出去，快点
Out, soldier. Out you go.

480
01:17:02,278 --> 01:17:06,116
好好照顾他 他就像是我兄弟一样
Look after him, please. He's like a brother to me.

481
01:17:10,745 --> 01:17:12,747
神父，我…
Hey, Father, I...

482
01:17:25,510 --> 01:17:29,264
神父，他说话了吗？他说了些什么？
Father, did he speak? Did he say anything?

483
01:17:58,168 --> 01:18:01,129
神父，他有没有问起我？有没有说任何事？
Father, did he ask for me? Did he speak about anything?

484
01:18:01,212 --> 01:18:02,964
他还不能说话 
No, he hasn't spoken as yet.

485
01:18:03,047 --> 01:18:08,261
不过你不要担心 就因为他年轻又强壮 才能撑到现在
But don't worry, he's young and strong - that's what's kept him going.

486
01:18:08,344 --> 01:18:10,680
要不了多久他就能活蹦乱跳了
He should regain his strength in a short time.

487
01:18:10,763 --> 01:18:13,475
谢谢你，神父 这孩子对我实在太重要了
Thank you. You don't know what this boy's life means to me.

488
01:18:13,558 --> 01:18:16,186
谢谢耶稣，谢谢你们大家
Thanks be to Jesus.

489
01:19:04,984 --> 01:19:06,277
金发小子
Blondie?

490
01:19:11,824 --> 01:19:14,953
金发小子
Hey, Blondie?

491
01:19:33,137 --> 01:19:37,517
神父告诉我 过几天你就会好了
The old Father tells me you'll be up and around in a few days.

492
01:19:37,600 --> 01:19:41,437
幸好当时我在你身边
You were very lucky to have me so close when it happened.

493
01:19:41,521 --> 01:19:45,108
如果只有你一个人
Think if you'd been on your own.

494
01:19:45,191 --> 01:19:50,571
我是说，当…当一个人生病时
Look, I mean when one is... ill,

495
01:19:50,655 --> 01:19:55,868
最好能有人在身边 不管是朋友还是亲戚
it's good to have somebody close by, friends or relations.

496
01:19:55,952 --> 01:20:01,624
你父母还在吗？妈妈呢？
Do you... you have parents, Blondie? A mother?

497
01:20:02,166 --> 01:20:04,627
妈妈也不在了
Not even a mother.

498
01:20:05,169 --> 01:20:07,255
一个亲戚也没有吗？
No-one?

499
01:20:07,338 --> 01:20:10,800
只有你一个人吗？像我一样
You're all alone, huh? Like me, Blondie.

500
01:20:10,883 --> 01:20:13,636
我们全是孤魂野鬼一个
We're all alone in the world.

501
01:20:13,720 --> 01:20:16,848
我只有你，你也只有我
I have you, you have me.

502
01:20:18,558 --> 01:20:21,060
这当然只是暂时的
Only for a little while, I mean.

503
01:20:21,144 --> 01:20:26,399
但却碰巧发生了 都是命运在做怪
It had to happen now. What a dirty, rotten trick of fate.

504
01:20:26,482 --> 01:20:30,528
那些钱几乎到了我们手中
We could have all that money in our hands.

505
01:20:34,615 --> 01:20:41,122
我必须告诉你真相 换成你也会做同样的事
I... I must tell you the truth, Blondie. In my place, you would do the same thing.

506
01:20:42,790 --> 01:20:46,002
你已经没有希望了
It's all over for you now.

507
01:20:46,085 --> 01:20:49,964
没人救得了你
There's nothing anyone can do any more.

508
01:20:51,382 --> 01:20:53,342
天啊，
Oh, God, forgive me.

509
01:20:53,426 --> 01:20:56,554
这都是我的错 是我的错呀
It's my fault, mine, mine, mine, mine!

510
01:21:07,106 --> 01:21:09,692
告诉你一件事
I'll tell you one thing, Blondie.

511
01:21:09,775 --> 01:21:13,404
如果我知道只有一小时好活
If I knew that my last hour had come, I swear,

512
01:21:13,488 --> 01:21:17,742
若咱们换个位置，我发誓 一定会做同样的事
in my place... in your place I would do the same thing.

513
01:21:17,825 --> 01:21:21,370
就是告诉你金币在哪里
I would tell about the gold. Yes, yes, I would.

514
01:21:21,454 --> 01:21:23,789
我会告诉你坟墓的名字
I would tell the name on the grave.

515
01:21:23,873 --> 01:21:28,461
你是将死之人 钱生不带来死不带去
What good is the money if you're dead? I know the name of the cemetery.

516
01:21:28,544 --> 01:21:31,756
我知道公墓在哪里 但那儿有成千的坟墓
But you know how many graves there are there?

517
01:21:31,839 --> 01:21:37,720
求求你告诉我
Please. Blondie, please. Have a little...

518
01:21:40,681 --> 01:21:44,060
来喝点咖啡吧 求求你告诉我
Coffee? Please, tell me the name.

519
01:21:44,143 --> 01:21:46,729
坟墓上的名字
On... on the grave.

520
01:21:48,105 --> 01:21:52,568
如果我拿到二十万的话
If I get my hands on the 200,000 dollars,

521
01:21:52,652 --> 01:21:55,655
保证永远不会忘记你
I'll always honour your memory.

522
01:21:55,738 --> 01:22:00,034
我发誓永远记得你
I swear, I'll always honour your memory.

523
01:22:01,994 --> 01:22:03,955
靠近点
Come closer.

524
01:22:08,834 --> 01:22:10,920
快告诉我
Tell me.

525
01:22:12,296 --> 01:22:14,757
你这个恶劣的…
You dirty...

526
01:22:16,467 --> 01:22:19,053
知道身边有个好朋友
I'll sleep better...

527
01:22:19,136 --> 01:22:23,599
随时都在保护我
knowing my good friend is by my side...

528
01:22:23,683 --> 01:22:26,060
连睡觉都能睡得安稳些
to protect me.

529
01:22:34,819 --> 01:22:37,154
“杜可，给我水” 水来啦
"Tuco, water. " Well, here's water.

530
01:22:37,238 --> 01:22:41,909
如果让我知道名字的话 看我会给你什么样的水
But if I get that name from you, I'll give you water! I'll give you...

531
01:22:47,957 --> 01:22:50,793
好了，懒鬼，起床吧
All right, you dirty skunk, get your ass off the bed.

532
01:22:50,876 --> 01:22:54,672
快起来，我们得走了 蓬车已经准备好了
Come on. The party's over. The wagon is all ready to go.

533
01:22:54,755 --> 01:23:00,136
我们最好快走 看来战争就要来了
We'd better get the hell out of here, before we get caught up in the war.

534
01:23:00,219 --> 01:23:03,264
杜可，拉美尼斯神父回来了
Tuco, Father Ramirez is back.

535
01:23:03,347 --> 01:23:08,227
我得去办点事 只要几分钟，你先准备一下
This is something I have to look into. It'll only take a minute. Get moving.

536
01:23:08,310 --> 01:23:10,896
- 走这边吗？   - 是的
- Where? This way? - Yes.

537
01:23:27,496 --> 01:23:29,790
巴布罗
Hey, Pablo?

538
01:23:36,464 --> 01:23:39,091
你认不得我了吗？
Don't you recognise me?

539
01:23:40,634 --> 01:23:43,137
我是杜可，
It's me. Tuco.

540
01:23:43,220 --> 01:23:46,348
让我抱抱你
Let me embrace you...

541
01:23:48,350 --> 01:23:51,562
我不知道这样做是不对的
I don't know the right thing.

542
01:23:55,733 --> 01:24:01,989
当经过这里时，我在想“不知道我哥哥还记不记得我这个弟弟”
I was passing by and said to myself "I wonder if my brother remembers me?"

543
01:24:04,533 --> 01:24:06,869
我做错了吗？
Did I do wrong?

544
01:24:07,369 --> 01:24:09,872
反正无所谓，看到你我真高兴
It doesn't matter. I'm very happy.

545
01:24:09,955 --> 01:24:12,208
你还想到来看我
You have seen me, Tuco.

546
01:24:14,126 --> 01:24:17,087
对呀，真高兴我能来
Yeah, well, I'm very glad I came.

547
01:24:22,676 --> 01:24:24,762
喔，我这身制服吗？
Ah, my uniform.

548
01:24:24,845 --> 01:24:26,931
说来话长
It's a long story.

549
01:24:27,056 --> 01:24:30,434
让我们先谈谈你 你比较重要，看来你很不错
But let's talk about you. It's more important.

550
01:24:30,518 --> 01:24:35,189
瘦了一点，也许，但是…
You look very well. A bit thin, perhaps, but...

551
01:24:36,857 --> 01:24:40,653
你本来就很瘦嘛
You were always thin, eh, Pablito?

552
01:24:41,570 --> 01:24:44,615
爸妈好吗？
Wh... What about our parents?

553
01:24:46,116 --> 01:24:51,956
九年后的今天你才想到他们
Only now do you think of them. To begin after nine years.

554
01:24:53,874 --> 01:24:56,752
已经有九年了吗？
Nine years?

555
01:24:56,835 --> 01:24:59,547
九年就吧
So it's nine years.

556
01:24:59,630 --> 01:25:01,215
九年
Nine years.

557
01:25:01,882 --> 01:25:04,718
妈妈很久以前就死了
Our mother has been dead a long time now.

558
01:25:06,136 --> 01:25:11,684
爸爸在几天前才过世 所以我才会离开这里
Our father died only a few days ago. That's why I was away.

559
01:25:13,227 --> 01:25:15,729
他临死前想见见你
He asked for you to be there.

560
01:25:15,813 --> 01:25:18,941
可惜只有我在那儿送终
But there was only me.

561
01:25:24,822 --> 01:25:26,991
而你
And you?

562
01:25:27,074 --> 01:25:31,287
你这个野鬼，你都做了些什么
Outside of eviI, what else have you managed to do?

563
01:25:31,370 --> 01:25:36,208
我记得你曾有过太太
It seems to me you once had a wife someplace.

564
01:25:37,626 --> 01:25:39,545
不只一个，有好多个
Not one. Lots of them.

565
01:25:39,628 --> 01:25:43,424
这里一个，那里一个 只要她们愿意，我就照单全收
One here, one there, wherever I found them.

566
01:25:43,507 --> 01:25:47,928
说呀，向我说教呀
Go on, preach me a sermon, Pablo.

567
01:25:48,012 --> 01:25:51,348
那有什么用
What good would that be?

568
01:25:51,432 --> 01:25:54,101
你仍然照做不误，
Just keep on the way you're going.

569
01:25:54,184 --> 01:25:56,603
你走吧
Go away.

570
01:25:56,687 --> 01:25:59,273
- 愿上帝怜悯你的灵魂 - 好，我走！
- The Lord have mercy on your souI. - Sure, I'll go.

571
01:25:59,356 --> 01:26:02,151
但当我在等上帝的时候
While I'm waiting for the Lord to remember me!

572
01:26:02,234 --> 01:26:07,531
让我杜可 就是巴布罗的弟弟，说几句话
I, Tuco Ramirez, brother of Brother Ramirez, will tell you something.

573
01:26:07,614 --> 01:26:10,034
你一直认为你比我好
You think you're better than I am.

574
01:26:10,117 --> 01:26:15,039
在我们生长的那个鬼地方 如果不想饿死 除了当神父就是当土匪
Where we came from, one became a priest or a bandit.

575
01:26:15,122 --> 01:26:19,501
你选择你的路，我也选择我的 我的路比你要艰难得多
You chose your way, I chose mine. Mine was harder.

576
01:26:19,585 --> 01:26:21,879
说到爸爸和妈妈
You talk of our mother and father -

577
01:26:21,962 --> 01:26:24,631
当初你去当神父时是我留守家园
when you left to become a priest, I stayed behind.

578
01:26:24,715 --> 01:26:28,844
我不记得当时几岁 十、十二岁吧，但我留下来了
I must have been 10, 12, I don't remember. But I stayed.

579
01:26:28,927 --> 01:26:33,057
我曾努力试过，但没有用 让我告诉你
I tried, but it was no good. Now I'll tell you something.

580
01:26:33,140 --> 01:26:39,146
你之所以会去做神父 是因为你懦弱没胆量
You became a priest because you were too much of a coward to do what I do.

581
01:26:56,580 --> 01:26:58,248
杜可
Tuco.

582
01:27:08,759 --> 01:27:11,011
弟弟，请你原谅我
Please forgive me, brother.

583
01:27:22,272 --> 01:27:24,191

Haa!

584
01:27:40,040 --> 01:27:43,961
哇，我肚子胀得要命
Ah, my belly's full.

585
01:27:44,044 --> 01:27:46,296
我哥哥是个好人
Nice guy, my brother.

586
01:27:46,380 --> 01:27:48,924
我没告诉你 我哥哥是这里的主持吧
I didn't tell you my brother was in charge here?

587
01:27:49,007 --> 01:27:53,387
很伟大，几乎和教皇一样 教皇是罗马的主持
Everything. Like the Pope, almost. He's in charge in Rome.

588
01:27:53,470 --> 01:27:58,725
还有，我哥哥对我说“弟弟，不要走 否则我们再也见不到面了”
My brother, he say to me "Stay, brother, we never see each other. "

589
01:27:58,809 --> 01:28:02,729
“在这里有吃有喝让你的朋友也留下来”
"There's plenty to eat and drink. Bring your friend too. "

590
01:28:02,813 --> 01:28:06,984
每次我们一见面 他就不让我走
Whenever we see each other, he never lets me go.

591
01:28:08,026 --> 01:28:11,154
我哥哥对我好得不得了
My brother, he's crazy about me.

592
01:28:14,658 --> 01:28:19,746
你看像我这种流浪汉 不管发生了什么事
That's so. Even a tramp like me, no matter what happens,

593
01:28:19,830 --> 01:28:24,918
只要到我哥哥那儿去 一天三餐绝对不用愁
I know there's a brother somewhere who'll never refuse me a bowI of soup.

594
01:28:26,461 --> 01:28:29,131
没错
Sure.

595
01:28:29,214 --> 01:28:34,011
酒足饭饱后，来根雪茄吧
Well, after a meaI there's nothing like a good cigar.

596
01:29:23,810 --> 01:29:26,980
这里是穆德兰纳山脊
Here's the Sierra Magdalena.

597
01:29:27,064 --> 01:29:30,275
走这里，我们将渡过大河
Going this way, we cross the Rio Grande.

598
01:29:30,358 --> 01:29:33,403
这段路很遥远
That sure is a long way.

599
01:29:33,487 --> 01:29:37,616
朝西北方走可以横越整个德州
Here to the northwest, through all of Texas...

600
01:29:37,699 --> 01:29:39,868
- 然后… - 然后呢？
- After that... - Then what?

601
01:29:41,953 --> 01:29:46,750
然后抵达这里 你不会害怕吧？
When we get there, I'll tell you. You're not worried, are you?

602
01:29:48,794 --> 01:29:53,173
这些死人什么都不必害怕了 不是吗？
Those men aren't worried about anything any more, are they?

603
01:29:55,008 --> 01:30:01,264
因为我还活着，我注意到了 我们要跨过北方佬和南方同盟的前线好几次
But since I'm alive and I've noticed we'll be crossing enemy lines a few times,

604
01:30:01,348 --> 01:30:04,601
我还以为你会告诉我我们要去哪里
I thought you might tell me where we're going.

605
01:30:04,684 --> 01:30:08,772
朝20万迈进，这还不够吗？
Towards 200,000 dollars. Is that good enough for you?

606
01:30:17,614 --> 01:30:19,699
你看
Whoa.

607
01:30:28,166 --> 01:30:30,043
喂，你醒醒
Wake up, you.

608
01:30:30,126 --> 01:30:33,588
- 有军队过来了 - 蓝色还是灰色
- There are troops coming. - Blue or grey?

609
01:30:40,011 --> 01:30:43,723
和我们一样的灰色 咱们和他们打个招呼吧
They're grey, like us. Let's say hello to them, then get going.

610
01:30:43,807 --> 01:30:47,686
加油！南军加油
Hurrah! Hurrah for the Confederacy!

611
01:30:47,769 --> 01:30:51,147
加油！为格兰特将军加油
Hurrah! Down with GeneraI Grant!

612
01:30:51,231 --> 01:30:53,066
加油…
Hurrah for GeneraI...

613
01:30:53,149 --> 01:30:54,860
- 另外一个是什么将军 - 李将军
- What's his name? - Lee.

614
01:30:54,943 --> 01:30:56,444
李将军加油
.. Lee!

615
01:30:56,820 --> 01:31:01,908
上帝和我们同在 因为他讨厌北军
God is with us because he hates the Yanks, too! Hurrah!

616
01:31:01,992 --> 01:31:05,745
上帝换边了，因为他讨厌白痴
God's not on our side, cos he hates idiots also.

617
01:31:18,008 --> 01:31:22,095
踏步走、二、三、四
Hup, two, three, four. Hup, two, three, four.

618
01:31:22,178 --> 01:31:25,890

Hup, two, three, four. Hup, two, three four...

619
01:31:25,974 --> 01:31:29,227
战俘们向前走
Prisoners of war, forward...

620
01:31:30,353 --> 01:31:32,105
前进！
march.

621
01:31:32,188 --> 01:31:35,358

Hup, two, three, four...

622
01:32:28,495 --> 01:32:31,164
向左转！
Left face.

623
01:32:34,000 --> 01:32:38,546
成一路纵队，快！
Form a single file. Move.

624
01:33:19,420 --> 01:33:22,799
- 强那森罗斯   - 在
- Jonathan Broad. - Present.

625
01:33:28,930 --> 01:33:31,641
- 理察包尔   - 在
- Richard Mobiley. - Present.

626
01:33:31,724 --> 01:33:35,645
- 奈森尼苏利文  - 在
- NathanieI Sullivan. - Present.

627
01:33:36,104 --> 01:33:39,232
- 罗伯克拉克  - 在
- Robert Clark. - Present.

628
01:33:39,858 --> 01:33:42,735
- 山姆理察曼  - 在
- Sam Richmond. - Present.

629
01:33:45,905 --> 01:33:47,991
比尔卡森
Bill Carson.

630
01:33:50,702 --> 01:33:53,204
比尔卡森
Bill Carson?

631
01:33:53,663 --> 01:33:56,124
我在叫比尔卡森
I said Bill Carson.

632
01:33:56,207 --> 01:33:59,002
金发小子 那个人不就是天使眼吗？
Hey, Blondie, isn't that AngeI Eyes?

633
01:33:59,836 --> 01:34:05,884
他在干什么，打瞌睡吗？比尔卡森
All right, what's he doing, sleeping? Bill Carson!

634
01:34:05,967 --> 01:34:08,845
对，你最好装成比尔卡森
Yeah. You better be Bill Carson.

635
01:34:08,928 --> 01:34:10,597
比尔卡森
Bill Carson!

636
01:34:10,680 --> 01:34:13,808
是的，那是我
Yeah, yeah... That's me.

637
01:34:21,816 --> 01:34:24,027
卡森，当你回答时
Please, Carson...

638
01:34:25,069 --> 01:34:27,155
请说“在”
answer "present".

639
01:34:28,531 --> 01:34:31,326
你聋了吗？
What, are you deaf?

640
01:34:36,205 --> 01:34:38,708
你现在该说“在”
Now suppose you say "present", Carson.

641
01:34:40,752 --> 01:34:45,840
我喜欢你这种大胖子跌倒时声音特别大
I like big fat men like you - when they fall, they make more noise.

642
01:34:45,923 --> 01:34:49,010
甚至有时候跌倒了就起不来
And sometimes they never get up.

643
01:34:49,802 --> 01:34:51,262
华历斯
Wallace.

644
01:34:52,764 --> 01:34:54,515
够啦
That's enough.

645
01:34:57,393 --> 01:34:58,645
中士！
Sergeant.

646
01:35:00,772 --> 01:35:04,942
上尉马上要见你
The captain wants to see you right away.

647
01:35:06,694 --> 01:35:10,239
好好对待这两位
Be sure these two get good treatment.

648
01:35:19,248 --> 01:35:23,211
你听到了吗？好好对待我们
Hey, Blondie, did you hear that? Good treatment.

649
01:35:25,505 --> 01:35:27,590
听到了
Yeah.

650
01:35:30,051 --> 01:35:33,596
我再警告你一次
For the last time, Sergeant, I'm telling you,

651
01:35:33,679 --> 01:35:37,600
你要用正确的方法对待战俘
I want the prisoners treated as prisoners.

652
01:35:37,683 --> 01:35:40,645
不能使用暴力
No more brutality.

653
01:35:40,728 --> 01:35:44,440
我们有好几百个战俘 但只有几个守卫
There's hundreds of prisoners and only a few men to guard 'em.

654
01:35:44,524 --> 01:35:46,609
你说我该怎么办？我必须要得到他们的敬重
I have to have respect.

655
01:35:46,692 --> 01:35:51,697
若对他们好一点 更容易得到他们的敬重
I think you'll manage to gain their respect by treating them better.

656
01:35:52,990 --> 01:35:55,576
安德森维尔战俘营 对我们的人好吗？
Are our men treated that well in Andersonville camp?

657
01:35:55,660 --> 01:35:58,538
我不管他们怎么做
I don't give a goddamn what they do in Andersonville.

658
01:35:58,621 --> 01:36:05,294
当我负责时 不希望看到战俘被拷打被欺骗或被谋杀
While I'm in charge, the prisoners are not to be tortured or cheated... or murdered.

659
01:36:06,003 --> 01:36:07,797
你在指控我吗？
That an accusation?

660
01:36:07,880 --> 01:36:13,094
中士，我的腿虽然得了坏疽病 但眼睛并没有瞎
Sergeant, gangrene is eating my leg away, not my eyes.

661
01:36:13,594 --> 01:36:17,098
我知道战俘们被有计划的抢劫
I know the prisoners here are being robbed systematically.

662
01:36:17,181 --> 01:36:20,351
也知道那些渣滓们露宿战俘营外
I know there's scum around, bivouacked near the camp,

663
01:36:20,434 --> 01:36:23,646
就等着里面的人送掠夺品出去
waiting for someone to deliver this loot.

664
01:36:23,729 --> 01:36:28,734
但只要我当指挥官一天就不准这种奸计得逞
But as long as I'm commandant, I won't permit any such trickery. Am I clear?

665
01:36:31,028 --> 01:36:32,572
是的，长官
Yes, sir.

666
01:36:32,655 --> 01:36:35,032
只要你仍是指挥官
Just as long as you're the commandant.

667
01:36:36,701 --> 01:36:38,786
没错，中士
Yes, Sergeant.

668
01:36:40,913 --> 01:36:44,667
我知道我活不了多久
I know this leg means I won't last very long,

669
01:36:44,750 --> 01:36:51,424
只求有足够的时间收集证据 把那些败坏名声
but I pray I have enough time to amass evidence and bring to a court martiaI

670
01:36:51,507 --> 01:36:57,555
使我们军队声誉受损的那些人告到军事法庭去
all those who discredit and dishonour the uniform of the Union.

671
01:37:01,809 --> 01:37:04,520
祝你好运
I wish you luck.

672
01:37:38,220 --> 01:37:42,558
你们最近要收敛一点
You and the others better lay low for a few days.

673
01:37:42,642 --> 01:37:46,896
我把这个留下来，你走吧 华历斯会通知你们的
I'll keep this. You go. Wallace will let you know.

674
01:37:56,739 --> 01:38:01,285
- 把卡森带进来 - 好
- Wallace, bring me Carson. - Right.

675
01:38:14,757 --> 01:38:18,844
天使眼要我们最近收敛点
AngeI Eyes said for us to lay low for a few days.

676
01:38:18,928 --> 01:38:24,225
但要守在附近随时注意情况 走，给马装鞍吧
We'll keep close enough to keep an eye on things. Saddle your horses.

677
01:38:24,725 --> 01:38:26,811
进去
Get in.

678
01:38:34,860 --> 01:38:38,072
杜可，进来，不要害羞
Come on in, Tuco. Don't be bashfuI.

679
01:38:39,365 --> 01:38:42,493
我这里不拘形式
There's no formalities here.

680
01:38:52,920 --> 01:38:55,548
好久没见了
It's been a long time.

681
01:38:58,551 --> 01:39:00,761
你饿了吧，
You're hungry.

682
01:39:00,845 --> 01:39:03,556
坐下来吃饭
Sit down. Eat.

683
01:39:21,991 --> 01:39:25,453
我就知道
I knew it, I knew it!

684
01:39:25,536 --> 01:39:31,667
我一见到你就对自己说“天使眼那家伙”
The minute I saw you, I said to myself "Look at that pig, AngeI Eyes. "

685
01:39:32,668 --> 01:39:36,130
“肯定找了份轻松的差事”
"I bet he got himself an easy job. "

686
01:39:38,549 --> 01:39:41,260
“而且绝不会忘记朋友”
"And he never forgets a friend. "

687
01:39:41,343 --> 01:39:44,471
我是不会忘记老朋友的
I never forget old friends, Tuco.

688
01:39:45,890 --> 01:39:47,474
对
Right.

689
01:39:47,558 --> 01:39:50,895
很高兴能见到你这个老朋友
It's good to see old friends again.

690
01:39:50,978 --> 01:39:52,521
很好
Good.

691
01:39:52,605 --> 01:39:56,025
尤其是来自远方的朋友
Especially when they've come from so far away.

692
01:39:56,108 --> 01:39:59,653
一定有很多话要说
And have so much to talk about.

693
01:39:59,737 --> 01:40:03,115
相信你一定有很多话要说
And you do have a lot to talk about, haven't you?

694
01:40:05,409 --> 01:40:09,205
你是在葛瑞堡被俘的
You were captured near Fort Craig?

695
01:40:13,375 --> 01:40:19,882
若你跟着席伯利的军队走 那表示你是从圣塔菲过来的
If you were with Sibley, that means you were coming from Santa Fe.

696
01:40:31,268 --> 01:40:36,815
- 穿过沙漠不是很困难吗？ - 非常困难
- Was it hard crossing the desert? - Mm-hm. Very hard.

697
01:40:36,899 --> 01:40:40,110
尤其是没东西喝的时候
Especially if you don't have anything to drink.

698
01:40:42,196 --> 01:40:48,035
为什么你用比尔卡森这个名字
Why are you going under the name of Bill Carson now?

699
01:40:50,746 --> 01:40:53,499
什么名字还不都一样
One name is as good as another.

700
01:40:53,582 --> 01:40:56,502
只要不用真名就行了
Not wise to use your own name.

701
01:40:56,585 --> 01:41:00,965
像你，也不会用天使眼吧
Like you. I bet they don't call you AngeI Eyes.

702
01:41:01,048 --> 01:41:04,009
天使眼中士
Sergeant AngeI Eyes!

703
01:41:11,976 --> 01:41:15,062
你在吃饭时喜欢听音乐吗？
Like a little music with your meaI, Tuco?

704
01:41:15,145 --> 01:41:21,151
音乐？当然好，对消化有帮助
Music? Yes, it's very good. Very good for the digestion.

705
01:41:32,913 --> 01:41:35,207
这么说
So...

706
01:41:35,290 --> 01:41:39,336
比尔卡森是个假名罗
Bill Carson's a fake name, huh?

707
01:41:43,298 --> 01:41:46,635
那这个也是假的吗？
That fake, too?

708
01:41:46,719 --> 01:41:50,931
比尔卡森的名字就写在上面
Bill Carson's name's written on it.

709
01:41:51,014 --> 01:41:55,853
来一点，那是他的烟叶
Have some. It's Bill Carson's tobacco.

710
01:41:58,272 --> 01:42:00,149

Aarh!

711
01:43:18,727 --> 01:43:23,148
当你发现他时，他是死是活？
Was Carson dead or alive when you found him?

712
01:43:28,070 --> 01:43:30,364
有关钱的事他都说了些什么？
What did he tell you about the money?

713
01:43:30,447 --> 01:43:33,075
我不…
I don't...

714
01:43:33,158 --> 01:43:35,869
我不知道你在说什么
I... I don't know what you're talking about.

715
01:43:54,262 --> 01:43:56,181
多加点感情进去
More feeling.

716
01:44:14,616 --> 01:44:18,286
你的运气比你朋友要好得多
You can sure consider yourself much luckier than your paI.

717
01:44:18,370 --> 01:44:21,331
只要音乐不停 华历斯就会一直揍你的朋友
Wallace will punch your friend as long as the song goes.

718
01:44:21,415 --> 01:44:24,960
我们几乎都经历过那种拷打
So many of us have had a session in there.

719
01:44:45,564 --> 01:44:48,984
消化的怎么样呀？
How's your digestion now?

720
01:44:51,695 --> 01:44:57,075
- 你最好实话实说 - 我没什么好说的
- You'd better talk. - I have nothing to tell you.

721
01:45:23,435 --> 01:45:26,146
你！继续拉小提琴
Play that fiddle, you.

722
01:46:09,731 --> 01:46:11,942
够了，我说
I'll talk... I'll talk...

723
01:46:21,409 --> 01:46:24,204
他是怎么说钱的事？
What did he say about the money?

724
01:46:24,287 --> 01:46:27,749
埋…
It's bu...

725
01:46:27,832 --> 01:46:31,336
在坟墓里
It's buried in a grave.

726
01:46:31,419 --> 01:46:33,129
在哪里？
Where?

727
01:46:33,213 --> 01:46:34,631
伤心坡
Sad Hill...

728
01:46:34,714 --> 01:46:37,217
伤心坡公墓
Sad Hill cemetery.

729
01:46:39,928 --> 01:46:41,888
哪一个坟墓
Which grave?

730
01:46:41,972 --> 01:46:45,892
不知道，我是真的不知道
I don't know. I don't know, I tell you.

731
01:46:47,519 --> 01:46:49,479
去问金发小子
Blondie...

732
01:46:49,562 --> 01:46:54,359
他知道墓名
Ask Blondie. He knows the name of the grave.

733
01:47:11,042 --> 01:47:14,170
对你来说战争已经结束
The war's over for you.

734
01:47:16,131 --> 01:47:19,259
把衣服穿上
Put those clothes on.

735
01:47:22,470 --> 01:47:24,222
为什么？
Why?

736
01:47:24,305 --> 01:47:27,267
我们出去走走
We're going for a ride.

737
01:47:27,350 --> 01:47:31,354
- 去哪儿？ - 去找二十万美金
- Where? - To find 200,000 dollars.

738
01:47:31,438 --> 01:47:34,649
我知道公墓在哪里
I know the name of the cemetery now.

739
01:47:34,733 --> 01:47:38,236
而你知道是哪个坟墓
And you know the name of the grave.

740
01:47:57,297 --> 01:48:00,425
难道你不给我同样的待遇吗？
You're not going to give me the same treatment?

741
01:48:03,845 --> 01:48:05,805
你会招吗？
Would you talk?

742
01:48:06,639 --> 01:48:08,391
可能不会
No. Probably not.

743
01:48:10,143 --> 01:48:12,729
正如我预料的
That's what I thought.

744
01:48:12,812 --> 01:48:15,190
不是说你比杜可勇敢
Not that you're any tougher than Tuco,

745
01:48:15,273 --> 01:48:18,651
而是你知道一说就会没命了
but you're smart enough to know that talking won't save you.

746
01:48:22,363 --> 01:48:25,575
那杜可…他…
And Tuco? Is he...

747
01:48:27,660 --> 01:48:30,747
还没有
No. Not yet.

748
01:48:30,830 --> 01:48:33,416
不过有人会好好照顾他的
But he's in very good hands.

749
01:48:34,125 --> 01:48:37,629
你的合伙人虽然不一样 但交易仍旧不变
You've changed partners, but you've still got the same deaI.

750
01:48:37,712 --> 01:48:40,256
我并不贪心，只拿一半就好
I'm not greedy. I'm only taking half.

751
01:48:41,591 --> 01:48:45,553
两个人比一个人要好办事
There's two of us. Should make it easier than just one.

752
01:48:50,391 --> 01:48:52,477
对
Yeah.

753
01:49:11,746 --> 01:49:13,206
保持这个样子
Hold it.

754
01:49:13,289 --> 01:49:16,084
很好，不要动
That's it. Don't move.

755
01:49:16,167 --> 01:49:21,714
不要呼吸，不要动 保持这个样子
Now, don't breathe. Still... that's it.

756
01:49:21,798 --> 01:49:25,093
好了，谢谢你们
Got it. Thank you.

757
01:49:39,691 --> 01:49:43,444
下士，你怕他会逃吗？这个叛徒要到哪里去
Hey, CorporaI, afraid he'll get lost? Where's the rebeI going?

758
01:49:43,528 --> 01:49:47,156
下地狱，带着悬赏金去吊死
To hell, with a rope around his neck and a price on his head.

759
01:49:47,240 --> 01:49:52,370
老兄，三千块呀 我的脑袋可值不少钱
3,000 dollars, friend. That's a lot of money for a head.

760
01:49:52,453 --> 01:49:56,207
我赌你这条断臂 他们连一毛也没付
I'll bet they didn't even pay you a penny for your arm.

761
01:50:01,337 --> 01:50:03,089
告诉你，下次若被我
I told you once, friend.

762
01:50:03,172 --> 01:50:08,011
逮到机会把你揍倒在地上 你就别想再起来
If I ever get you down, you're gonna need a lot of help to get up again.

763
01:50:27,947 --> 01:50:30,158
你比那家伙要幸运多了
You're a lot luckier than that one.

764
01:50:30,241 --> 01:50:32,827
“南方联盟的间谍”一根绳子就让你呜呼哀哉
You get some grub, a rope, and you're finished.

765
01:50:32,910 --> 01:50:36,789
死得干净俐落 而且不会有人来救你
And there isn't any partner this time to shoot you down.

766
01:52:17,890 --> 01:52:22,895
你朋友如果继续留在湿地里 就算不会感冒…
If your friends stay out in the damp, they're liable to catch a cold, aren't they?

767
01:52:22,979 --> 01:52:25,356
也会挨子弹
Or a bullet.

768
01:52:29,485 --> 01:52:32,863
听到没有？出来吧
Hear that, boys? Come on out here.

769
01:52:44,083 --> 01:52:49,005
既然走的方向一样 就干脆一起走吧
Since we're all going in the same direction, might as well go together.

770
01:52:49,088 --> 01:52:51,549
1…2…
One, two,

771
01:52:51,632 --> 01:52:53,676
3…4…
three, four,

772
01:52:54,176 --> 01:52:56,554
5…6…
five, six.

773
01:52:57,013 --> 01:53:00,182
6，完美的数字
Six... Perfect number.

774
01:53:01,475 --> 01:53:04,437
3才是完美数字吧？
Isn't three the perfect number?

775
01:53:05,563 --> 01:53:10,026
没错，但我的枪里还有6颗子弹
Yeah. But I got six more bullets in my gun.

776
01:54:12,421 --> 01:54:17,093
你真以为偷得到吗？
Sure would like to put your paw on it, huh?

777
01:54:17,176 --> 01:54:21,889
我要小便，憋不住了 在火车上已经折腾了将近十个小时
I would like to piss. It's rough. I've been on this train nearly ten hours.

778
01:54:21,972 --> 01:54:24,767
你闻起来和猪一样
You smell like a pig already.

779
01:54:24,850 --> 01:54:27,686
你最好收敛点，别惹事
Let's try not to make things any worse.

780
01:54:29,980 --> 01:54:32,066
走吧
Get going.

781
01:54:40,282 --> 01:54:43,953
你看着我就小不出来
I can't while you're watching me.

782
01:54:54,964 --> 01:54:56,924

Aaaarh!

783
01:55:06,392 --> 01:55:10,145
你吵得要死
You made a lot of noise, my friend, huh?

784
01:55:30,457 --> 01:55:34,420
既然你不想破坏我们的友情 那就让我来破坏好了
You don't want to break our friendship? Well, I'll break it.

785
01:57:18,565 --> 01:57:21,401
停
Squad, halt.

786
01:57:21,485 --> 01:57:24,363
大家就位
Take your places.

787
01:57:34,540 --> 01:57:36,458
准备！
Ready.

788
01:57:36,542 --> 01:57:38,043
瞄准！
Aim.

789
01:57:38,127 --> 01:57:40,212
开枪
Fire.

790
01:57:55,936 --> 01:57:59,231
瘦子，你来照顾马匹
Clem, take care of the horses.

791
02:02:14,736 --> 02:02:18,239
我找你找了八个月
I've been looking for you for eight months.

792
02:02:18,323 --> 02:02:22,911
每次当我想用右手拿枪时就会想到你
Whenever I should have had a gun in my right hand, I thought of you.

793
02:02:22,994 --> 02:02:26,956
老天帮忙 居然让我在澡盆里找到你
Now I find you in exactly the position that suits me.

794
02:02:27,040 --> 02:02:32,879
我花了很多时间 练习用左手开枪
And I had lots of time to learn how to shoot with my left.

795
02:02:46,851 --> 02:02:51,481
要开枪就开枪 何必废话那么多
When you have to shoot, shoot. Don't talk.

796
02:02:53,108 --> 02:02:56,194
每支枪都有它们自己的声音
Every gun makes its own tune.

797
02:02:56,277 --> 02:02:59,739
你真会选时间
It's perfect timing, large one.

798
02:03:16,589 --> 02:03:19,134
克蓝，你去跟着他
Clem, follow him.

799
02:04:16,191 --> 02:04:19,194
等一下，我马上就来
Just a minute. I'll be right there.

800
02:04:19,277 --> 02:04:23,031
给我一点时间穿衣服 马上就来开门
Just give me time to get dressed and I'll open up.

801
02:04:43,259 --> 02:04:46,804
把枪拿下来，把衣服穿上去
Put your drawers on and take your gun off.

802
02:04:55,146 --> 02:04:56,940
嗨，金发小子
Hey...

803
02:04:57,023 --> 02:05:01,694
你是怎么逃离那个猪舍的
Hey, Blondie, how the hell did you get out of that pigsty?

804
02:05:03,196 --> 02:05:07,617
我自有方法 我和你的朋友天使眼一起来的
My own way. I'm here with your old friend AngeI Eyes.

805
02:05:08,117 --> 02:05:11,537
你招了，你居然告诉他了
You talked, you traitor. You talked.

806
02:05:12,163 --> 02:05:16,918
我没说 倘若说出来，我早就死了
No, I didn't talk. If I did, I probably wouldn't be here now.

807
02:05:18,211 --> 02:05:20,838
你、我…
You... me...

808
02:05:20,964 --> 02:05:23,800
所以只有你知道你那半个秘密吗？
So only you know your half of the secret?

809
02:05:24,550 --> 02:05:26,094

Mm-hm.

810
02:05:27,220 --> 02:05:30,848

Ah, Blondie...

811
02:05:30,932 --> 02:05:35,311
真高兴你、我站在一条阵线上而且再度合作
I'm very happy you're working with me, and we're together again.

812
02:05:35,395 --> 02:05:38,982
我把衣服穿上 杀了他后，马上回来
- I get dressed, I kill him, be right back. - Oh, listen...

813
02:05:39,065 --> 02:05:43,111
喔，对了，我忘了一件事
I forgot to mention.

814
02:05:43,194 --> 02:05:47,949
他不是一个人，一共是五个人
He's not alone. There's five of them.

815
02:05:48,032 --> 02:05:51,411
- 五个人？ - 是的，一共五个人
- Five? - Yeah. Five of them.

816
02:05:53,746 --> 02:05:57,458
所以你才来找我吗？
So that's why you came to Tuco.

817
02:05:59,544 --> 02:06:02,255
没关系 反正我会把他们全部杀光
It doesn't matter. I'll kill them all.

818
02:06:13,891 --> 02:06:17,103
他被近距离杀死的
They shot him at close range.

819
02:06:35,580 --> 02:06:40,543
- 哇，看是谁来了 - 另一个随后也会跟来
- Well, look who's here. - The other one will be along.

820
02:06:42,545 --> 02:06:46,132
他们是来找我们的
They'll come looking for us.

821
02:06:46,215 --> 02:06:48,426
大家小心
Watch out.

822
02:06:48,509 --> 02:06:51,554
他们一共有两个人
There's two of them.

823
02:06:51,637 --> 02:06:53,890
我要活捉金发小子
I want that blond alive.

824
02:07:02,732 --> 02:07:06,444
你们走那边，动身吧
You, back there. Come on, let's go.

825
02:07:40,102 --> 02:07:42,438
你想一个人去送死吗？
Were you going to die alone?

826
02:09:32,798 --> 02:09:34,091

Ho!

827
02:09:59,158 --> 02:10:02,244
喂，天使眼是我的
Hey, Blondie. AngeI Eyes is mine.

828
02:10:02,328 --> 02:10:03,913
没问题
All right.

829
02:10:43,244 --> 02:10:48,040
“等会儿见…”
"See you soon, i... idi.. "

830
02:10:48,123 --> 02:10:50,709
“白痴”
"Idiots. "

831
02:10:50,793 --> 02:10:53,087
是给你的
It's for you.

832
02:11:17,319 --> 02:11:20,281
这里既平静又美丽
How peacefuI and quiet, amigo.

833
02:11:20,364 --> 02:11:24,034
就像墓地一样，是吗？
Like a cemetery, for instance?

834
02:11:24,118 --> 02:11:27,037
应该有座桥横跨那条河
There should be a bridge across that river.

835
02:11:27,121 --> 02:11:32,751
- 最好等晚上再行动 - 相信我
- We better wait for nightfall. - Trust in me, Blondie.

836
02:11:32,835 --> 02:11:35,587
我对要去的地方 有一种很好的感觉
I got a good sense of where I'm going.

837
02:11:35,671 --> 02:11:39,717
既然能把你带到这里来 就能把你带到目的地
Tuco has taken you this far, I will take you all the way to...

838
02:11:44,763 --> 02:11:47,850
- 去告诉上尉  - 是的，长官
- Tell the captain. - Yes, sir.

839
02:11:47,933 --> 02:11:51,270
你们跟我走
Come along, now. Follow me.

840
02:12:36,940 --> 02:12:40,486
我们在阵地附近发现他们
We found them near the perimeter, sir.

841
02:12:53,957 --> 02:12:56,168
你们来自何处？
Where do you haiI from?

842
02:12:56,251 --> 02:12:57,669
伊利诺州
Illinois.

843
02:13:00,088 --> 02:13:01,965
你呢？
And you?

844
02:13:02,049 --> 02:13:03,926
我和他一道
I'm with him.

845
02:13:09,890 --> 02:13:13,268
来这里有什么原因吗？
Any reason for being around here?

846
02:13:13,352 --> 02:13:16,313
将军，我们想从军
We want to enlist, GeneraI.

847
02:13:18,857 --> 02:13:21,193
你最好学会认军阶
You'd better learn to distinguish rank.

848
02:13:21,276 --> 02:13:23,362
我是上尉
I'm a captain.

849
02:13:24,696 --> 02:13:27,491
你们可以走了
Get the hell out.

850
02:13:27,574 --> 02:13:30,577
也许今天性命就不保 去写遗嘱吧
It sure as hell might be you today, so go write your will.

851
02:13:30,661 --> 02:13:32,746
是的，长官
Yes, sir.

852
02:13:37,543 --> 02:13:39,795
你们想从军
So you want to enlist?

853
02:13:40,712 --> 02:13:44,466
首先得看你们合不合格
You've got to take a test to prove it.

854
02:13:52,432 --> 02:13:54,935
你敢喝吗？
Well, show me.

855
02:14:12,869 --> 02:14:15,956

Hey...

856
02:14:17,708 --> 02:14:22,129
你没问题，至少能做到上校
You've got a career. At the least, I'd say you'll make coloneI.

857
02:14:22,212 --> 02:14:25,007
- 真的吗？   - 当然
- Really? - Sure.

858
02:14:25,090 --> 02:14:27,217
就像手册中所说的
Like it says in the manuaI,

859
02:14:27,301 --> 02:14:32,681
“你已合格成为使用武器的专家”
you've got every qualification to become an expert in the use of weapons.

860
02:14:32,764 --> 02:14:37,894
这家伙就是最有力的武器
For this, sir, is the most potent weapon in war.

861
02:14:39,646 --> 02:14:43,275
瓶子里的就是战斗的精神
The fighting spirit's in this bottle.

862
02:14:44,401 --> 02:14:46,486
自愿者
Volunteers.

863
02:14:47,946 --> 02:14:52,409
你们想从军是吗？咱们走
You want to enlist, hm? Let's go.

864
02:14:52,492 --> 02:14:55,620
你们来呀
Come on, gentlemen, come on.

865
02:14:57,080 --> 02:15:00,542
攻击还没开始
The shooting hasn't begun yet. You're in time.

866
02:15:09,009 --> 02:15:10,552

Eh?

867
02:15:16,224 --> 02:15:19,144
谁的酒比较多可以灌醉士兵
Whoever has the most liquor to get the soldiers drunk

868
02:15:19,227 --> 02:15:23,273
然后送上战场当炮灰…他就是赢家
and send them to be slaughtered... is the winner.

869
02:15:23,356 --> 02:15:29,780
我们和河对岸那些人只有一个共同点…
We and the ones over on the other side of the river only have one thing in common.

870
02:15:29,863 --> 02:15:32,240
都发出浓浓的酒臭味
All of us reek of alcohoI.

871
02:15:40,040 --> 02:15:42,709
你说你叫什么名字？
What did you say your name was?

872
02:15:42,793 --> 02:15:44,127

Uh...

873
02:15:44,961 --> 02:15:47,089
你呢？
And you?

874
02:15:47,881 --> 02:15:48,965

Uh...

875
02:15:49,049 --> 02:15:51,051
不说
"Uh. " No.

876
02:15:56,056 --> 02:15:58,767
名字无关紧要
Names don't matter.

877
02:15:58,850 --> 02:16:04,439
所以你们正好赶上成为布朗史东大桥战役中的英雄
Yes, because soon you can join the gallant heroes of Branston Bridge.

878
02:16:04,523 --> 02:16:06,817
我们在一天中进攻了两次
We have two attacks a day.

879
02:16:06,900 --> 02:16:09,569
一天攻两次？
- Two attacks a day? - Sure.

880
02:16:09,653 --> 02:16:14,825
南军认为桥梁是占领这个地区的关键
The rebs have decided that damn bridge is the key to this whole area.

881
02:16:14,908 --> 02:16:18,036
又笨又没用的桥
Stupid, useless bridge.

882
02:16:18,119 --> 02:16:21,373
它只不过是总部地图上的一个小苍蝇屎
Flyspeck on headquarters' maps.

883
02:16:22,415 --> 02:16:27,921
但总部却下令一定要占领这座桥
Headquarters has declared we must take that ridiculous flyspeck.

884
02:16:28,964 --> 02:16:31,132
即使全军覆没也在所不惜
Even if all of us are killed.

885
02:16:31,216 --> 02:16:36,805
否则兵家必争之地反成为无用武之地
Otherwise the key'll get rusty and just be a spot on the wall.

886
02:16:36,888 --> 02:16:41,601
而且不止如此 双方都不希望桥梁受损
And that's not all. Both sides want the bridge intact.

887
02:16:41,685 --> 02:16:46,940
南军希望它完整无缺 我们也希望如此
Intact is how the South wants it, and we want it intact, too.

888
02:16:48,775 --> 02:16:53,113
你们全将面临死亡 但有件事我绝对肯定
You'll all turn to dust, but one thing is sure, boys:

889
02:16:53,196 --> 02:16:57,576
就是布朗史东大桥将永恒存在
Branston Bridge will stand unbroken.

890
02:16:57,659 --> 02:17:02,872
我这样对自愿者讲话 会不会吓坏你们？
Is it bad to speak the way I do to volunteers?

891
02:17:02,956 --> 02:17:06,251
我以前更吓人
I've done a lot worse.

892
02:17:09,421 --> 02:17:13,925
我想把它炸掉 想把它全毁
I've done it. I've blown it up. Boom!

893
02:17:14,009 --> 02:17:17,220
可惜只能在这里想
In here, I've destroyed it all.

894
02:17:18,179 --> 02:17:23,393
你知道炸掉它的罪有多大吗 将来一定会面临军事法庭的审判
It's a court-martiaI offence to dream of blowing it up. A serious crime.

895
02:17:23,476 --> 02:17:29,107
即使在脑袋里想想也会…
Even to think of destroying that bridge is just...

896
02:17:30,567 --> 02:17:32,819
为什么不真的去炸掉它
Why not really blow it up, Captain?

897
02:17:34,487 --> 02:17:37,866
对呀，这么简单 又会吓得他们屁滚尿流
Yeah, Captain, it's nothing. Let's scare the hell out of them.

898
02:17:41,286 --> 02:17:44,414
说实话，我连做梦都想
I've been dreaming about it.

899
02:17:46,916 --> 02:17:50,378
甚至还想出个计划来
I've even worked out a plan.

900
02:17:50,462 --> 02:17:52,464
没骗你们
I sure have.

901
02:17:53,381 --> 02:17:56,676
最好的时机是在攻击过后
The best time is after the attack,

902
02:17:56,760 --> 02:18:00,638
去救受伤者而暂时休战的时刻
when there's a truce to get the wounded.

903
02:18:00,722 --> 02:18:05,727
如果那时去炸桥就会救了上千人的性命
If I could do it, I could save many thousands of men.

904
02:18:10,690 --> 02:18:13,818
可是我却缺乏胆量
But what I lack is the guts.

905
02:18:19,032 --> 02:18:22,285
他们开始攻击了
They're beginning the daily slaughter right on time.

906
02:18:22,369 --> 02:18:25,747
上尉，所有的连都准备好了 就等你的命令
Captain, all companies are awaiting your orders.

907
02:18:25,830 --> 02:18:28,541
马上就来
Be right there.

908
02:18:41,054 --> 02:18:43,181
咱们走吧
Let's go.

909
02:18:43,264 --> 02:18:45,183
好啦，朋友们
All right, friends.

910
02:18:45,266 --> 02:18:48,520
享受这个壮观的场面吧
Come along and enjoy the spectacle.

911
02:19:18,842 --> 02:19:21,344
所有的连开始报告
Companies, report.

912
02:19:21,427 --> 02:19:24,222
B连准备好了
Company B ready.

913
02:19:24,305 --> 02:19:27,100
E连准备好了
Company E ready.

914
02:19:27,183 --> 02:19:30,311
D连准备好了
Company D ready.

915
02:19:35,191 --> 02:19:38,945
所有的连，进攻呀！
Companies, forward!

916
02:19:59,883 --> 02:20:03,845
看来上尉好像要我们帮他去炸桥
Hey, Blondie. Looks like the captain is asking for a bullet in his guts.

917
02:20:03,928 --> 02:20:06,014
对
Yeah.

918
02:20:58,274 --> 02:21:02,653
从没看过死伤这么惨重的场面
I've never seen so many men wasted so badly.

919
02:21:22,256 --> 02:21:26,636
看来这场战役将会又臭又长
I have a feeling it's really going to be a good, long battle.

920
02:21:29,931 --> 02:21:32,141
金发小子
Blondie...

921
02:21:32,225 --> 02:21:34,852
钱是在河的那一边
The money's on the other side of the river.

922
02:21:34,936 --> 02:21:37,855
在哪里？
Oh? Where?

923
02:21:40,191 --> 02:21:44,112
告诉你在对岸已经够多了
Amigo, I said the other side, and that's enough.

924
02:21:44,195 --> 02:21:48,741
若南军守在那里我们就过不去
But while the Confederates are there, we can't get across.

925
02:21:48,825 --> 02:21:53,955
如果桥被炸掉的话会怎样呢？
What would happen if somebody were to blow up that bridge?

926
02:21:54,038 --> 02:22:00,044
没错 那他们就得到别的地方去打仗
Yeah. Then these idiots would go somewhere else to fight.

927
02:22:00,128 --> 02:22:02,213
"炸药”
Maybe.

928
02:22:39,375 --> 02:22:43,379
医生，快来，上尉受伤了
Get a doctor, quick! The captain's wounded!

929
02:22:44,672 --> 02:22:47,550
快拿担架来
Hurry, a stretcher.

930
02:22:48,634 --> 02:22:51,470
慢慢来
Easy. Easy now.

931
02:22:55,349 --> 02:22:56,767

Arh!

932
02:23:01,397 --> 02:23:04,108
快把用具准备好
Get things ready.

933
02:23:23,961 --> 02:23:26,797
喝点酒会有点帮助的
A little of this will help.

934
02:23:32,386 --> 02:23:34,847
你先喝一大口
Take a slug of this, Captain.

935
02:23:34,930 --> 02:23:36,932
然后就留心的听着
And keep your ears open.

936
02:24:25,606 --> 02:24:29,443
你们想干嘛？别伤我
What are you doing? No... Leave me alone...

937
02:26:07,833 --> 02:26:11,921
你知道我们有丧命的可能吗？
Blondie, hey. You realise we might be risking our lives?

938
02:26:12,463 --> 02:26:18,218
当然知道，但是万一我死了 你就永远找不到金币
Yeah. And if I get killed, you'll never get your hands on all that beautifuI money.

939
02:26:18,302 --> 02:26:20,137
杜可，你想想看
Yeah, Tuco.

940
02:26:21,055 --> 02:26:23,390
是不是太可惜了
Sure would be a pity.

941
02:26:53,295 --> 02:26:54,463
医生
Doc...

942
02:26:56,715 --> 02:27:01,512
医生 请你让我支持久一点好吗？
Doctor... Can you help me live a little longer?

943
02:27:01,595 --> 02:27:04,556
我正在等个好消息
I expect good news.

944
02:27:50,436 --> 02:27:53,188

Eh... Eh...

945
02:27:54,565 --> 02:27:57,693
我们干脆把知道的告诉对方 好不好？
Why don't we tell each other our half of the secret?

946
02:27:57,776 --> 02:28:00,279
好主意
Why don't we?

947
02:28:01,321 --> 02:28:03,365
你先说
You go first.

948
02:28:05,117 --> 02:28:09,955
不，我认为你先说
No, I think it's better that...

949
02:28:10,038 --> 02:28:12,416
比较好
you start.

950
02:28:15,586 --> 02:28:18,297
好啦
All right.

951
02:28:19,131 --> 02:28:23,719
公墓的名字是…
The name of the cemetery is...

952
02:28:39,610 --> 02:28:41,820
伤心坡，现在该你了
Sad Hill. Now it's your turn.

953
02:28:50,078 --> 02:28:52,873
坟墓上的名字是…
The name on the grave is...

954
02:28:56,335 --> 02:28:58,378
奥奇·史坦顿
Arch Stanton.

955
02:28:58,462 --> 02:29:01,965
是奥奇·史坦顿，
Ar... Arch Stanton?

956
02:29:02,049 --> 02:29:04,301
你确定？
Are you sure?

957
02:29:04,384 --> 02:29:06,553
我当然确定
Yeah. Sure I'm sure.

958
02:40:54,844 --> 02:40:58,430
用那个会容易得多
It'll be a lot easier with that.

959
02:41:37,511 --> 02:41:39,680
两个人挖比一个人挖要快得多
Two can dig a lot quicker than one.

960
02:41:40,306 --> 02:41:42,391
快挖
Dig.

961
02:41:44,393 --> 02:41:46,103
你怎么不挖
You're not digging.

962
02:41:58,574 --> 02:42:02,953
如果杀了我 你一毛钱也看不到
If you shoot me, you won't see a cent of that money.

963
02:42:03,829 --> 02:42:05,164
为什么？
Why?

964
02:42:08,083 --> 02:42:10,711
我告诉你为什么
I'll tell you why.

965
02:42:10,794 --> 02:42:13,297
因为钱不在那里
Cos there's nothing in there.

966
02:42:21,388 --> 02:42:24,641
- 你这个狗杂… - 你以为我会相信你
- Why, you son of a... - You thought I'd trust you?

967
02:42:28,020 --> 02:42:31,648
别忘了二十万是笔大数目
200,000 dollars is a lot of money.

968
02:42:31,732 --> 02:42:34,860
我们必须去赚取它
We're gonna have to earn it.

969
02:42:37,446 --> 02:42:39,740
怎么赚法？
How?

970
02:42:49,708 --> 02:42:52,544
我把名字写在这个石头下面
I'll write the name on the bottom of this stone.

971
02:42:56,340 --> 02:42:58,467
然后比枪
The gun?

972
02:49:04,332 --> 02:49:08,503
你这只猪，居然陷害我 你是什么时候把子弹拿出来的
You pig! You wanted to get me killed! When did you unload it?

973
02:49:10,505 --> 02:49:12,715
昨晚
Last night.

974
02:49:12,799 --> 02:49:17,512
在这个世界上有两种人
You see, in this world, there's two kinds of people, my friend:

975
02:49:17,595 --> 02:49:22,267
一种人的枪装满子弹 一种人只会掘坟
those with loaded guns and those who dig.

976
02:49:22,350 --> 02:49:24,310
你去挖坟吧
You dig.

977
02:49:24,394 --> 02:49:26,521
挖哪里？
Where?

978
02:49:36,322 --> 02:49:38,700
这里
Here.

979
02:49:39,617 --> 02:49:41,494
“无名者之墓”
Unk... Un...

980
02:49:41,578 --> 02:49:44,497
可是这个没有名字
There's no name on it.

981
02:49:44,581 --> 02:49:47,292
石头上也没名字
And there's no name here, either.

982
02:49:48,585 --> 02:49:51,588
当初比尔·卡森告诉我
You see, that's what Bill Carson told me.

983
02:49:51,671 --> 02:49:56,467
钱是在奥奇·史坦顿之墓旁边的无名冢里
It was the grave marked "unknown", right beside Arch Stanton.

984
02:50:03,266 --> 02:50:05,768
挖吧
Go ahead.

985
02:51:02,533 --> 02:51:06,287
金发小子，这全是我们的
Blondie! It's all ours, Blondie!

986
02:51:22,261 --> 02:51:27,433
你在开玩笑吧 你总不会和我开这种玩笑
You're joking, Blondie. You wouldn't... You wouldn't play a joke on me like that.

987
02:51:27,517 --> 02:51:30,853
不是玩笑，这是吊索
It's no joke. It's a rope, Tuco.

988
02:51:30,937 --> 02:51:34,315
你站上去，把头伸进套索里
I want you to stand up there and put your head in that noose.

989
02:52:41,466 --> 02:52:45,511
好啦，就像以前一样
Well, now... Seems just like old times.

990
02:52:50,099 --> 02:52:52,810
四份给你
Four for you.

991
02:52:54,020 --> 02:52:57,148
四份
And four...

992
02:52:58,316 --> 02:53:00,818
四份给我
Four for me.

993
02:53:26,844 --> 02:53:28,262

Hey, Blon...

994
02:53:28,346 --> 02:53:29,680

Blon...

995
02:53:38,814 --> 02:53:41,192
金发小子
Hey, Blondie...

996
02:53:42,443 --> 02:53:45,154
杜可，抱歉啦
Sorry, Tuco.

997
02:53:48,157 --> 02:53:49,533
金毛小子…
Blondie...

998
02:53:58,668 --> 02:54:01,003
金发小子！
Blondie!

999
02:54:08,844 --> 02:54:11,013

Blondie!

1000
02:54:20,773 --> 02:54:21,857

Blondie...

1001
02:54:32,493 --> 02:54:34,370

Blondie...

1002
02:54:49,552 --> 02:54:52,221
金发小子！
Blondie!

1003
02:55:13,409 --> 02:55:16,287
你这个杂种
You son of a bitch...

1004
02:55:18,622 --> 02:55:21,083
金发小子
Blondie...

1005
02:55:41,937 --> 02:55:44,315
“小人”
Aaaarhh!

1006
02:56:20,226 --> 02:56:23,395
喂，金发小子
Hey, Blondie!

1007
02:56:24,271 --> 02:56:27,566
你知道你是什么东西吗？
You know what you are?

1008
02:56:30,778 --> 02:56:32,655
一个下流无耻的杂种！
Just a dirty son of a...
